<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Military and Security Affairs on The Zombie Fridge Journal</title>
    <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/tags/military-and-security-affairs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Military and Security Affairs on The Zombie Fridge Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:18:20 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://theZFJ.github.io/tags/military-and-security-affairs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>US, South Korea, and Japan agree to increase defense, economic cooperation at summit</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/foreign-affairs/asia-pacific/2023/us-kr-jp-summit-camp-david/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:18:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/foreign-affairs/asia-pacific/2023/us-kr-jp-summit-camp-david/</guid>
      <description>Aug. 21 (ZFJ) — President Joe Biden, South Korea’s President Yoon Suk Yeol, and Japan’s Prime Minister Fumio Kishida agreed to increase defense and economic cooperation among their countries at a Camp David summit on Friday, Aug. 18.
This meeting is the first-ever standalone summit between the leaders of Japan, South Korea, and the United States.
Japan and South Korea continue to have disputes over former Imperial Japan’s colonial rule from 1910-1945.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Navy commissions littoral combat ship USS Canberra in Australia</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/foreign-affairs/asia-pacific/2023/uss-canberra-commissioned-australia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 21:46:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/foreign-affairs/asia-pacific/2023/uss-canberra-commissioned-australia/</guid>
      <description>July 24 (ZFJ) — The U.S. Navy commissioned Independence-class littoral combat ship USS Canberra (LCS 30) at the Royal Australian Navy’s Fleet Base East in Sydney on Saturday, July 22, marking the first time a U.S. ship entered service at a foreign port.
It is the second American ship named for Australia’s capital. The first was a Baltimore-heavy class cruiser, renamed in honor of the Australian heavy cruiser HMAS Canberra, which was lost at the Battle of Savo Island in WWII when defending U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US completes destruction of its declared chemical weapons stockpile</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/us-destroys-chemical-weapons-stockpile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 19:34:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/us-destroys-chemical-weapons-stockpile/</guid>
      <description>July 10 (ZFJ) — The last possessor state, America, announced that it finished destroying its declared chemical weapons stockpile on Friday, July 7, marking the first time an international body verified the destruction of an entire category of declared weapons of mass destruction.
The stockpile was declared to the Organisation for the Prohibition of Chemical Weapons, the international body responsible for implementing the Chemical Weapons Convention. The 1997 arms control treaty prohibits its 193 members from developing or stockpiling chemical weapons.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
