<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Climate Change on The Zombie Fridge Journal</title>
    <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/tags/climate-change/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Climate Change on The Zombie Fridge Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 12:18:31 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://theZFJ.github.io/tags/climate-change/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>July 2023 confirmed hottest month on record globally</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2023/july-2023-breaks-heat-records/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 12:18:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2023/july-2023-breaks-heat-records/</guid>
      <description>Aug. 14 (ZFJ) — July 2023 was the hottest month on record globally, confirmed the Copernicus Climate Change Service.
The monthly average temperature worldwide was 16.95 degrees Celsius (62.51 degrees Fahrenheit), exceeding July 2019’s previous record of 16.63 C (61.93 F) and meeting the Paris Agreement threshold of 1.5 C (2.7 F) warming above preindustrial levels.
The 29 days from July 3-31 were the hottest days on record, exceeding the previous daily global mean surface air temperature record of 16.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>66% chance world exceeds warming threshold before 2027, WMO says</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2023/66-chance-world-exceeds-warming-threshold-before-2027/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 21:32:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2023/66-chance-world-exceeds-warming-threshold-before-2027/</guid>
      <description>May 18 (ZFJ) — There is a 66% chance that the annual global surface temperature will exceed 1.5 degrees Celsius (2.7 degrees Fahrenheit) above pre-industrial levels before 2027, said the World Meteorological Organization on Wednesday.
The UN weather agency also predicted that there is a 98% chance that one of the next five years will be the warmest on record.
“These new highs will be fuelled almost completely by the rise of heat-trapping greenhouse gases in the atmosphere, but the anticipated development of the naturally-occurring El Niño event will also release heat from the tropical Pacific,” said Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
