<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Domestic Affairs on The Zombie Fridge Journal</title>
    <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/categories/domestic-affairs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Domestic Affairs on The Zombie Fridge Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 15:28:26 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://theZFJ.github.io/categories/domestic-affairs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Grand jury clears Edison cops for April 2022 fatal shooting</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/grand-jury-no-charges-edison-police-deadly-force-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 15:28:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/grand-jury-no-charges-edison-police-deadly-force-2022/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Oct. 15 (ZFJ) — A state grand jury declined to criminally charge two Edison police officers who shot Merrill Rambarose, 49, of Edison on April 12, 2022.
Witness interviews, photographs, video footage of the shooting, and autopsy results were presented to the grand jury, which concluded deliberations on Sept. 25 and voted “no bill”—meaning Officers Daniel Bradley and Joseph Elqumos will not have criminal charges filed against them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raritan Valley EMS rebrands to Edison EMS</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/rvrems-rebranding-edison-ems/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 00:50:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/rvrems-rebranding-edison-ems/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Oct. 7 (ZFJ) — Edison Emergency Medical Services has officially rebranded from Raritan Valley Regional EMS, the agency announced in a Sept. 28 Instagram post.
Edison EMS is the non-profit volunteer first aid squad serving Edison and its surrounding areas for free.
RVREMS was formed in 2009 when Edison First Aid &amp;amp; Rescue Squad #1, Edison First Aid Squad #2, and Clara Barton First Aid Squad merged.
Edison EMS continues to operate out of the original stations, which have been renamed to Edison EMS Station 1, 2, and 3, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FEMA to conduct nationwide emergency alert test</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/fema-emergency-alert-test-october-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 16:55:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/fema-emergency-alert-test-october-2023/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Oct. 2 (ZFJ) — The federal government will test two national emergency alert systems on Wednesday, Oct. 4, starting at about 14:20 (2:20 p.m.) EDT.
The Federal Emergency Management Agency, in conjunction with the Federal Communications Commission, will conduct the two-part test.
The first portion will test Wireless Emergency Alerts, which are directed at cell phones.
For 30 minutes, cell towers will broadcast the message “THIS IS A TEST of the National Wireless Emergency Alert System.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NJ requires schools to provide students grades 6-12 free menstrual products</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/nj-schools-6-12-must-provide-free-menstrual-products/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 00:49:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/nj-schools-6-12-must-provide-free-menstrual-products/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Sept. 10 (ZFJ) — School districts in New Jersey are now required to provide menstrual products for free in public schools that teach students of any grade from six through twelve.
Applicable schools will have to provide tampons and sanitary napkins (pads) in at least half of all their female and gender-neutral bathrooms. The state government will shoulder the costs for doing so.
The law addresses period poverty—one in four students in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DOJ: Menlo Park, Paramus veterans homes violated civil rights with inadequate medical care</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/doj-menlo-park-veterans-home-civil-rights-investigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 23:38:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/doj-menlo-park-veterans-home-civil-rights-investigation/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Sept. 12 (ZFJ) — State-run veterans homes at Menlo Park and Paramus have failed to adequately respond to the COVID-19 pandemic and provide medical care to their residents, announced the Justice Department on Thursday, Sept. 7.
The feds said that the conditions at the veterans homes, which provide long-term nursing care to veterans and their families and are under the New Jersey Department of Military and Veterans Affairs (DMAVA), violate the Fourteenth Amendment right to reasonable safety when in the state’s care.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NYC authorities identify two new 9/11 victims</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/nyc-identifies-two-new-9-11-victims/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 21:05:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/nyc-identifies-two-new-9-11-victims/</guid>
      <description>Sept. 11 (ZFJ) — The 1,648th and 1,649th victims from the World Trade Center attacks on Sept. 11, 2001, have been identified, announced the New York City Office of Chief Medical Examiner on Friday, Sept. 8.
These two victims are the first new identifications of 9/11 victims since September 2021. About 1,104 victims, or 40% of the 2,753 who died, remain unidentified.
This year, the OCME also identified 60 human remains connected to previously identified individuals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cecilia Birge appointed Princeton High principal</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/princeton-high-school-new-principal-birge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 20:39:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/princeton-high-school-new-principal-birge/</guid>
      <description>Sept. 10 (ZFJ) — Cecilia Xie Birge was appointed principal of Princeton High School on Thursday, Aug. 31.
The Princeton Board of Education voted unanimously for her at a special meeting. Board member Michele Tuck-Ponder was not present.
“With Cecilia’s appointment tonight, we are turning a page and we are looking with excitement to the future,” said Dafna Kendal, president of the school board.
Birge thanked the board and search committee for entrusting her with the position and recognized the school staff’s work for Princeton High.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Edison middle school teacher charged with possession of child pornography</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/edison-middle-school-teacher-charged-child-porn-possession/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 22:01:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/edison-middle-school-teacher-charged-child-porn-possession/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Aug. 30 (ZFJ) — Edison middle school teacher Julius Coaccioli, 55, was arrested and charged with third-degree possession of child pornography on Wednesday, Aug. 30, announced Middlesex County Prosecutor Yolanda Ciccone and Woodbridge Police Department Director Robert Hubner.
Coaccioli has taught science at Woodrow Wilson Middle School since 2013, according to Edison Board of Education personnel resolutions.
Coaccioli was charged with possessing under 1,000 child sexual abuse images after the New Jersey State Police referred a cyber tip to Ciccone’s office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US federal district court judge rules AI art not copyrightable</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/dc-district-judge-ai-art-not-copyrightable/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 14:45:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/dc-district-judge-ai-art-not-copyrightable/</guid>
      <description>Aug. 23 (ZFJ) — AI art generated “absent human involvement” is not eligible for copyright, ruled U.S. District Judge Beryl A. Howell on Aug. 18, Friday.
In her ruling for the federal district court in Washington, D.C., Howell upheld the U.S. Copyright Office’s denial of registration to computer scientist Stephen Thaler for the work he calls A Recent Entrance to Paradise.
BACKGROUND
Thaler, the plaintiff, owns an AI called the “Creativity Machine” that can generate visual works of art.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pittsburgh synagogue shooter sentenced to death</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/pittsburgh-synagogue-shooter-death-sentence/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 23:54:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/pittsburgh-synagogue-shooter-death-sentence/</guid>
      <description>Aug. 7 (ZFJ) — Robert Bowers, 50, was sentenced to death by U.S. District Judge Robert J. Colville on Thursday, Aug. 3, for killing 11 congregants, wounding two others, and injuring five police officers at the Tree of Life Synagogue in Pittsburgh.
“I have nothing specific that I care to say to Mr. Bowers,” Colville said, according to The Associated Press. “I am however convinced there is nothing I could say to him that might be meaningful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backup driver pleads guilty for first death caused by fully autonomous car</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/backup-driver-pleads-guilty-fully-autonomous-car-first-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 23:50:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/backup-driver-pleads-guilty-fully-autonomous-car-first-death/</guid>
      <description>Aug. 3 (ZFJ) — Rafaela Vasquez, 49, pled guilty to endangerment on Friday, July 28, for failing to stop a fully self-driving car from hitting and killing a 49-year-old woman.
Maricopa County Superior Court Judge David W. Garbarino sentenced her to three years of supervised probation. Her charge will be designated a misdemeanor once she completes her sentence.
On March 18, 2018, Vasquez was the backup driver for a test vehicle belonging to Uber’s Advanced Technologies Group (ATG).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Edward Aldarelli appointed Edison schools superintendent</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/aldarelli-appointed-edison-superintendent/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 23:10:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/aldarelli-appointed-edison-superintendent/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., July 29 (ZFJ) — Dr. Edward Aldarelli was appointed superintendent of Edison Township Public Schools on Thursday, July 27.
The Edison Board of Education voted unanimously for him after four hours of candidate interviewing at a special meeting.
“Definitely, no doubt, absolutely yes,” said Board President Shannon Peng, topping off board member Mohin Patel’s “absolutely yes” and Jerry Shi’s “absolutely, absolutely yes.”
Aldarelli was “overwhelmed” that the board chose him to lead the district, which has over 16,000 students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Middlesex County man admits to threatening attack on synagogue</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/middlesex-man-threat-synagogue-guilty-plea/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 00:01:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/middlesex-man-threat-synagogue-guilty-plea/</guid>
      <description>July 16 (ZFJ) – A Middlesex County man admitted to threatening to attack a synagogue and Jewish people via the internet.
19-year-old Omar Alkattoul pleaded guilty to one count of transmitting a threat in interstate and foreign commerce on Wednesday, July 12, regarding a crime committed around November 1, 2021.
Alkattoul used social media to share a link of his manifesto titled “When Swords Collide.” The document detailed his plans to attack a synagogue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US completes destruction of its declared chemical weapons stockpile</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/us-destroys-chemical-weapons-stockpile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 19:34:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/us-destroys-chemical-weapons-stockpile/</guid>
      <description>July 10 (ZFJ) — The last possessor state, America, announced that it finished destroying its declared chemical weapons stockpile on Friday, July 7, marking the first time an international body verified the destruction of an entire category of declared weapons of mass destruction.
The stockpile was declared to the Organisation for the Prohibition of Chemical Weapons, the international body responsible for implementing the Chemical Weapons Convention. The 1997 arms control treaty prohibits its 193 members from developing or stockpiling chemical weapons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court strikes down affirmative action in college admissions</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/supreme-court-ruling-affirmative-action-harvard-admissions-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 23:05:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/supreme-court-ruling-affirmative-action-harvard-admissions-case/</guid>
      <description>July 3 (ZFJ) — Affirmative action in college admissions violates the Equal Protection Clause of the Fourteenth Amendment, ruled the Supreme Court in Students for Fair Admissions v. Harvard (20-1199) and SFFA v. University of North Carolina (21-707) on Thursday, June 29. The EPC prohibits racial discrimination by the government.
Reversing the lower courts’ decisions, the Court struck down the admissions programs used by Harvard and UNC by a 6-2 and 6-3 vote, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canadian wildfire smoke descends on US East Coast</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/canadian-wildfire-smoke-descends-on-us-east-coast/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 23:01:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/canadian-wildfire-smoke-descends-on-us-east-coast/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., June 7 (ZFJ) — Smoke from Canadian wildfires drifted into the eastern and central U.S., tinting the sky orange and triggering air quality alerts on Wednesday.
Canadian authorities are battling “one of the worst wildfire seasons on record,” said Steven Guilbeault, Canadian minister of environment and climate change. The country is currently facing over 400 wildfires, with over half out of control, according to the Canadian Interagency Forest Fire Centre.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court limits federal authority over wetlands with stricter test</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/supreme-court-limits-federal-wetlands-authority-sackett/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 15:08:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/supreme-court-limits-federal-wetlands-authority-sackett/</guid>
      <description>May 28 (ZFJ) — The federal government can only regulate wetlands with “a continuous surface connection” to adjacent “waters of the United States” under the Clean Water Act (1972), ruled the Supreme Court on Thursday, May 25, in Sackett v. EPA (21-454).
The CWA is the primary federal law regulating water pollution and prohibits the “discharge of any pollutant,” including “chemical wastes,” “rock,” and “sand,” into “navigable waters,” defined as “the waters of the United States, including the territorial seas.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
