<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>New Jersey on The Zombie Fridge Journal</title>
    <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/tags/new-jersey/</link>
    <description>Recent content in New Jersey on The Zombie Fridge Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 15:28:26 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://theZFJ.github.io/tags/new-jersey/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Grand jury clears Edison cops for April 2022 fatal shooting</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/grand-jury-no-charges-edison-police-deadly-force-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 15:28:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/grand-jury-no-charges-edison-police-deadly-force-2022/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Oct. 15 (ZFJ) — A state grand jury declined to criminally charge two Edison police officers who shot Merrill Rambarose, 49, of Edison on April 12, 2022.
Witness interviews, photographs, video footage of the shooting, and autopsy results were presented to the grand jury, which concluded deliberations on Sept. 25 and voted “no bill”—meaning Officers Daniel Bradley and Joseph Elqumos will not have criminal charges filed against them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raritan Valley EMS rebrands to Edison EMS</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/rvrems-rebranding-edison-ems/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 00:50:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/rvrems-rebranding-edison-ems/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Oct. 7 (ZFJ) — Edison Emergency Medical Services has officially rebranded from Raritan Valley Regional EMS, the agency announced in a Sept. 28 Instagram post.
Edison EMS is the non-profit volunteer first aid squad serving Edison and its surrounding areas for free.
RVREMS was formed in 2009 when Edison First Aid &amp;amp; Rescue Squad #1, Edison First Aid Squad #2, and Clara Barton First Aid Squad merged.
Edison EMS continues to operate out of the original stations, which have been renamed to Edison EMS Station 1, 2, and 3, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NJ requires schools to provide students grades 6-12 free menstrual products</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/nj-schools-6-12-must-provide-free-menstrual-products/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 00:49:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/nj-schools-6-12-must-provide-free-menstrual-products/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Sept. 10 (ZFJ) — School districts in New Jersey are now required to provide menstrual products for free in public schools that teach students of any grade from six through twelve.
Applicable schools will have to provide tampons and sanitary napkins (pads) in at least half of all their female and gender-neutral bathrooms. The state government will shoulder the costs for doing so.
The law addresses period poverty—one in four students in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DOJ: Menlo Park, Paramus veterans homes violated civil rights with inadequate medical care</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/doj-menlo-park-veterans-home-civil-rights-investigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 23:38:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/doj-menlo-park-veterans-home-civil-rights-investigation/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Sept. 12 (ZFJ) — State-run veterans homes at Menlo Park and Paramus have failed to adequately respond to the COVID-19 pandemic and provide medical care to their residents, announced the Justice Department on Thursday, Sept. 7.
The feds said that the conditions at the veterans homes, which provide long-term nursing care to veterans and their families and are under the New Jersey Department of Military and Veterans Affairs (DMAVA), violate the Fourteenth Amendment right to reasonable safety when in the state’s care.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cecilia Birge appointed Princeton High principal</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/princeton-high-school-new-principal-birge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 20:39:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/princeton-high-school-new-principal-birge/</guid>
      <description>Sept. 10 (ZFJ) — Cecilia Xie Birge was appointed principal of Princeton High School on Thursday, Aug. 31.
The Princeton Board of Education voted unanimously for her at a special meeting. Board member Michele Tuck-Ponder was not present.
“With Cecilia’s appointment tonight, we are turning a page and we are looking with excitement to the future,” said Dafna Kendal, president of the school board.
Birge thanked the board and search committee for entrusting her with the position and recognized the school staff’s work for Princeton High.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Edison middle school teacher charged with possession of child pornography</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/edison-middle-school-teacher-charged-child-porn-possession/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 22:01:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/edison-middle-school-teacher-charged-child-porn-possession/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Aug. 30 (ZFJ) — Edison middle school teacher Julius Coaccioli, 55, was arrested and charged with third-degree possession of child pornography on Wednesday, Aug. 30, announced Middlesex County Prosecutor Yolanda Ciccone and Woodbridge Police Department Director Robert Hubner.
Coaccioli has taught science at Woodrow Wilson Middle School since 2013, according to Edison Board of Education personnel resolutions.
Coaccioli was charged with possessing under 1,000 child sexual abuse images after the New Jersey State Police referred a cyber tip to Ciccone’s office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taco Bell will fund your Taco Tuesday—unless you’re in NJ</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/business/2023/taco-bell-taco-tuesday-promo-nj-excluded/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 22:34:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/business/2023/taco-bell-taco-tuesday-promo-nj-excluded/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Aug. 12 (ZFJ) — To celebrate its trademark battle win, Taco Bell will fund Taco Tuesday celebrations in all U.S. states except New Jersey, the company announced on Tuesday, Aug. 8.
On Tuesday, Sept. 12, Taco Bell, partnering with DoorDash, will spend $5 million to cover orders from participating Mexican food vendors.
“Taco Tuesday belongs to all who make, sell, eat, and celebrate tacos, and this Free-For-All will not only thank taco fans who supported the cause, but also spotlight local restaurants and vendors who can now embrace Taco Tuesdays without fear of legal action,” said Taco Bell U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Edward Aldarelli appointed Edison schools superintendent</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/aldarelli-appointed-edison-superintendent/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 23:10:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/aldarelli-appointed-edison-superintendent/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., July 29 (ZFJ) — Dr. Edward Aldarelli was appointed superintendent of Edison Township Public Schools on Thursday, July 27.
The Edison Board of Education voted unanimously for him after four hours of candidate interviewing at a special meeting.
“Definitely, no doubt, absolutely yes,” said Board President Shannon Peng, topping off board member Mohin Patel’s “absolutely yes” and Jerry Shi’s “absolutely, absolutely yes.”
Aldarelli was “overwhelmed” that the board chose him to lead the district, which has over 16,000 students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Middlesex County man admits to threatening attack on synagogue</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/middlesex-man-threat-synagogue-guilty-plea/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 00:01:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/middlesex-man-threat-synagogue-guilty-plea/</guid>
      <description>July 16 (ZFJ) – A Middlesex County man admitted to threatening to attack a synagogue and Jewish people via the internet.
19-year-old Omar Alkattoul pleaded guilty to one count of transmitting a threat in interstate and foreign commerce on Wednesday, July 12, regarding a crime committed around November 1, 2021.
Alkattoul used social media to share a link of his manifesto titled “When Swords Collide.” The document detailed his plans to attack a synagogue.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
