<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Domestic-Affairs on The Zombie Fridge Journal</title>
    <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Domestic-Affairs on The Zombie Fridge Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 23:24:18 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Glen Rock Starbucks sign vandalized with red paint, police investigating as bias crime</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/glen-rock-starbucks-vandalism-red-paint-police-bias-crime/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 23:24:18 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/glen-rock-starbucks-vandalism-red-paint-police-bias-crime/</guid>
      <description>Feb. 20 (ZFJ) — Glen Rock police are investigating vandalism of the Glen Rock Starbucks’ sign as a bias incident.&#xA;At 8:05 a.m. on Monday, Feb. 19, the manager of the Starbucks at 224 Rock Road in the borough’s Central Business District notified police that red paint had been splashed over the café’s sign at the corner of Rock Road and Glen Avenue.&#xA;The responding officer also found stickers on the sign with messages related to the Israel-Hamas war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metuchen Planning Board approves drive-thru marijuana dispensary plan</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/metuchen-planning-board-dasco-marijuana-drive-thru-approval/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 18:44:17 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/metuchen-planning-board-dasco-marijuana-drive-thru-approval/</guid>
      <description>METUCHEN, N.J., Feb. 18 (ZFJ) — The Metuchen Planning Board adopted a resolution at its reorganization meeting on Jan. 4 to approve Dasco Solutions’ drive-thru marijuana dispensary plan.&#xA;Dasco intends to convert a 3,037 square foot former bank building at 700 Middlesex Avenue into a cannabis dispensary. It presented its proposal to the board on Nov. 2, 2023, and the resolution reflects the board’s actions on that date.&#xA;RESOLUTION 23-1368 VOTE RESULTS</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recovered firearm in Union Catholic High School leads to lockdowns, student arrested</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/union-catholic-high-school-gun-lockdowns-arrest/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 22:41:56 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/union-catholic-high-school-gun-lockdowns-arrest/</guid>
      <description>SCOTCH PLAINS, N.J., Feb. 7 (ZFJ) — The discovery of a firearm in Union Catholic High School on Monday, Jan. 22, resulted in lockdowns at nearby schools and the arrest of one student.&#xA;The Scotch Plains Police Department said in a press release that it received a call at about 10:45 a.m. from a Union Catholic administrator concerning a handgun that had been recovered in the school.&#xA;The school was placed on lockdown, and Scotch Plains police officers recovered the weapon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gas odor prompts evacuation at J.P. Stevens High School</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/jps-suspected-gas-leak-evacuation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 17:05:19 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/jps-suspected-gas-leak-evacuation/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Feb. 1 (ZFJ) — A suspected gas leak resulted in the evacuation of J.P. Stevens High School students and staff on Thursday, Feb. 1, according to the school district.&#xA;An odor of gas near the art and music wing and in the back of the building caused the evacuation, which, according to a ZFJ reporter, began around the start of third period.&#xA;The Edison Fire Department and Elizabethtown Gas Company concluded that a construction crew hit an inactive gas line that still had residual gas remaining in it, resulting in the odor, according to a statement by Edison Township Public Schools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YESTERcades of Metuchen to open on Friday, Feb. 2</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/yestercades-announces-metuchen-opening-date/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 23:34:31 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/yestercades-announces-metuchen-opening-date/</guid>
      <description>METUCHEN, N.J., Jan. 30 (ZFJ) — YESTERcades of Metuchen will have its ribbon cutting and opening on Friday, Feb. 2, at 4:00 p.m., according to its announcement on social media.&#xA;Patrons are asked not to line up outside the building at 442 Main Street, Metuchen, before 3:30 p.m.&#xA;YESTERcades is a retro video game venue known for its focus on “golden age” arcade classics.&#xA;The arcade has at least 82 games moved into the Metuchen building, according to a social media post.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edison’s first Asian American police officer, Joseph Vincent Luistro, dies after battling ALS</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-police-joseph-vincent-luistro-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 01:14:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-police-joseph-vincent-luistro-death/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Jan. 21 (ZFJ) — Sgt. Joseph Vincent Luistro, 55, Edison Township’s first Asian American and Filipino American police officer, died on Thursday, Jan. 18, after battling ALS.&#xA;“Sergeant Luistro touched the lives of many with his selfless spirit,” said the Edison Police Department, calling him a “trailblazer” for his role in “actively fostering inclusivity in law enforcement careers.”&#xA;Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis, also known as Lou Gehrig’s disease, is a neurological disorder in which motor neurons progressively die, causing loss of control of muscle movement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edison police charge van driver with leaving disabled person in vehicle overnight</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-police-private-van-driver-neglect-disabled-person/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 22:20:37 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-police-private-van-driver-neglect-disabled-person/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Jan. 13 (ZFJ) — Winnie Raini, 53, of Edison, has been charged with leaving an adult female with a developmental disability in a van overnight while employed as a private transportation driver, announced Middlesex County Prosecutor Yolanda Ciccone and Chief Thomas Bryan of the Edison Police Department.&#xA;Authorities began investigating allegations of neglect on Jan. 3, according to the criminal complaint against Raini.&#xA;According to the aide for the developmentally delayed female, the woman is transported by van back to her residence twice a week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edison Board of Education and Township Council swear in new officials</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/2024-edison-council-boe-reorganization/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 01:44:05 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/2024-edison-council-boe-reorganization/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Jan. 6 (ZFJ) — The Edison Board of Education held its reorganization meeting on Tuesday, Jan. 2, while the Edison Township Council held it on Thursday, Jan. 4.&#xA;The candidates who won the general election on Nov. 7, 2023, were sworn in as elected officials at these meetings.&#xA;EDISON BOARD OF EDUCATION REORGANIZATION MEETING&#xA;Virginia White, first elected in 2020, and newcomers Christopher Lugo and Anjana R. Patel were sworn in as board of education members.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buses with migrants bound for New York arrive at NJ Transit stations</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/nyc-nj-migrant-buses-transit-stations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 17:47:05 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/nyc-nj-migrant-buses-transit-stations/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Jan. 1 (ZFJ) — Buses carrying migrants bound for New York City have been arriving at multiple NJ Transit stations, said local authorities across the state.&#xA;The Jersey City Office of Emergency Management said on X (formerly Twitter) that about 10 buses from Texas and one from Louisiana with approximately 397 migrants arrived at train stations in Secaucus, Fanwood, Edison, Trenton, and Jersey City since Saturday, Dec. 30.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military air defense command NORAD tracks Santa in annual tradition</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/norad-tracks-santa-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 21:37:04 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/norad-tracks-santa-2023/</guid>
      <description>Dec. 24 (ZFJ) — NORAD, with 68 years of experience following Santa, is once again tracking the jolly good man.&#xA;Anyone interested can view Santa’s location on noradsanta.org or call in to the North American Aerospace Defense Command at 1-877-HI-NORAD. If they can’t reach a human on the line due to the volume of calls, they’ll receive an automated message reporting Santa’s position and a reminder to call back later to talk to someone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perth Amboy Magnet carpentry teacher charged with criminal sexual contact</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/perth-amboy-magnet-carpentry-teacher-charged-criminal-sexual-contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 22:23:28 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/perth-amboy-magnet-carpentry-teacher-charged-criminal-sexual-contact/</guid>
      <description>Dec. 23 (ZFJ) — Edward White, 56, of Tinton Falls, N.J., was arrested on charges of inappropriately touching students on Dec. 13, announced Middlesex County Prosecutor Yolanda Ciccone and Chief Lawrence Cattano of the Perth Amboy Police Department.&#xA;In a statement on Dec. 14, a Thursday, Middlesex County Magnet Schools Superintendent Jorge E. Diaz said that the school district became aware of an “alleged incident involving a teacher and a student” on Dec.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J.P. Stevens High School closed Monday, other schools delayed due to flooding</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/jps-edison-public-schools-storm-flooding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 23:24:37 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/jps-edison-public-schools-storm-flooding/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Dec. 18 (ZFJ) — J.P. Stevens High School was closed on Monday, Dec. 18, due to flooding and road closures while several other North Edison schools opened late.&#xA;John Adams Middle School, James Madison Primary School, James Madison Intermediate School, and FDR Preschool had delayed openings. JPS was also going to open delayed until officials decided to close it for the day. Other Edison schools continued their days on their regular schedules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edison releases inspection reports on animal shelter deficiencies</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/edison-animal-shelter-inspection-reports/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 14:23:14 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/edison-animal-shelter-inspection-reports/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Dec. 10 (ZFJ) — Edison has released two veterinarians’ inspection reports on the condition of its animal shelter and a memorandum about the township’s response from early November.&#xA;The reports highlight problems relating to health, overcrowding, and management and recommend immediate action.&#xA;The Edison Animal Shelter serves Metuchen, Piscataway, Dunellen, Highland Park, and Edison.&#xA;DR. CHIOSI’S REPORT&#xA;Joseph R. Chiosi, doctor of veterinary medicine, of Sayrebrook Veterinary Hospital in Sayreville conducted an inspection on July 20, 2023, after performing exams and administering vaccines for adopters’ pets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edison police arrest Maryland attempted murder suspect after car chase</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/edison-police-arrest-attempted-murder-suspect-car-chase/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 23:30:41 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/edison-police-arrest-attempted-murder-suspect-car-chase/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Dec. 6 (ZFJ) — A suspect wanted for attempted murder in Maryland was arrested by Edison police after an hour-long motor vehicle pursuit on Sunday, Dec. 3.&#xA;At 20:13 on Sunday, Edison police dispatch received a Sirius XM alert that a stolen white 2019 Subaru Outback with Maryland license plates had entered the township near U.S. Highway 1 and Main Street.&#xA;While near 2900 Woodbridge Avenue, Edison Police Officer Phil Smith saw the vehicle traveling at a high speed and began tailing it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police: South Plainfield man shot three of his family members, called 911</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/south-plainfield-condo-complex-shooting-affidavit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 01:44:10 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/south-plainfield-condo-complex-shooting-affidavit/</guid>
      <description>SOUTH PLAINFIELD, N.J., Nov. 30 (ZFJ) — Authorities have accused Om Brahmbhatt, 23, of fatally shooting three of his family members on Monday at the Traditions condominium complex.&#xA;The Middlesex County Prosecutor’s Office has charged Brahmbhatt with three counts of first-degree murder and three counts of second-degree possession of a weapon for an unlawful purpose.&#xA;According to an affidavit submitted by the police to establish probable cause for an arrest warrant, South Plainfield Police Department officers responded to a 911 call on Monday, Nov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man charged for South Plainfield condo complex triple killing</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/south-plainfield-condo-complex-triple-shooting-arrest/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 22:55:02 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/south-plainfield-condo-complex-triple-shooting-arrest/</guid>
      <description>SOUTH PLAINFIELD, N.J., Nov. 28 (ZFJ) — A South Plainfield man has been arrested and charged in connection with the Coppola Drive shooting on Monday, Nov. 27, announced Middlesex County Prosecutor Yolanda Ciccone and Chief Peter Papa of the South Plainfield Police Department.&#xA;Om Brahmbhatt, 23, was arrested without incident and charged with three counts of first-degree murder and three counts of second-degree possession of a weapon for an unlawful purpose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court hears arguments on constitutionality of domestic violence gun ban</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/domestic-violence-gun-ban-oral-argument-supreme-court/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 18:39:28 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/domestic-violence-gun-ban-oral-argument-supreme-court/</guid>
      <description>Nov. 12 (ZFJ) — The Supreme Court heard arguments on whether a federal ban on firearms possession by people under domestic violence restraining orders violates the Second Amendment in the case United States v. Rahimi (22-915) on Tuesday, Nov. 7.&#xA;The statute in question, 18 U.S.C. § 922(g)(8), prohibits people who are under a restraining order from possessing guns. The court order must include a finding that the person is a credible threat to an “intimate partner or child” or explicitly prohibit any physical force against them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democrats sweep Edison council as White, Lugo, Patel win board of education</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/2023-edison-local-elections-council-boe/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 19:29:05 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/2023-edison-local-elections-council-boe/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Nov. 8 (ZFJ) — The Democrats won the four available seats on the Edison Township Council while Virginia White, Christopher Lugo, and Anjana R. Patel secured three spots on the Edison Board of Education, according to unofficial results from the Middlesex County Clerk for the Nov. 7 general election.&#xA;Richard Brescher, Joseph A. Coyle, and Ajay V. Patil won reelection to the town council along with newcomer Asaf Shmuel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School bus crashes into Edison home, no serious injuries</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/school-bus-crashes-into-edison-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 02:29:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/school-bus-crashes-into-edison-home/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Oct. 19 (ZFJ) — A school bus with 28 John Adams Middle School students on board crashed into an Edison home on Rahway Road in the morning on Wednesday, Oct. 18.&#xA;The bus, operated by contracted route provider Joy Transport, collided with the house’s garage, which sustained heavy damage. The house has been condemned by township inspectors for being structurally unsound.&#xA;The cause of the crash is believed to be a brake failure, said Edison Police Chief Thomas Bryan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grand jury clears Edison cops for April 2022 fatal shooting</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/grand-jury-no-charges-edison-police-deadly-force-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 15:28:26 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/grand-jury-no-charges-edison-police-deadly-force-2022/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Oct. 15 (ZFJ) — A state grand jury declined to criminally charge two Edison police officers who shot Merrill Rambarose, 49, of Edison on April 12, 2022.&#xA;Witness interviews, photographs, video footage of the shooting, and autopsy results were presented to the grand jury, which concluded deliberations on Sept. 25 and voted “no bill”—meaning Officers Daniel Bradley and Joseph Elqumos will not have criminal charges filed against them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raritan Valley EMS rebrands to Edison EMS</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/rvrems-rebranding-edison-ems/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 00:50:41 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/rvrems-rebranding-edison-ems/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Oct. 7 (ZFJ) — Edison Emergency Medical Services has officially rebranded from Raritan Valley Regional EMS, the agency announced in a Sept. 28 Instagram post.&#xA;Edison EMS is the non-profit volunteer first aid squad serving Edison and its surrounding areas for free.&#xA;RVREMS was formed in 2009 when Edison First Aid &amp;amp; Rescue Squad #1, Edison First Aid Squad #2, and Clara Barton First Aid Squad merged.&#xA;Edison EMS continues to operate out of the original stations, which have been renamed to Edison EMS Station 1, 2, and 3, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEMA to conduct nationwide emergency alert test</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/fema-emergency-alert-test-october-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 16:55:31 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/fema-emergency-alert-test-october-2023/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Oct. 2 (ZFJ) — The federal government will test two national emergency alert systems on Wednesday, Oct. 4, starting at about 14:20 (2:20 p.m.) EDT.&#xA;The Federal Emergency Management Agency, in conjunction with the Federal Communications Commission, will conduct the two-part test.&#xA;The first portion will test Wireless Emergency Alerts, which are directed at cell phones.&#xA;For 30 minutes, cell towers will broadcast the message “THIS IS A TEST of the National Wireless Emergency Alert System.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ requires schools to provide students grades 6-12 free menstrual products</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/nj-schools-6-12-must-provide-free-menstrual-products/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 00:49:28 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/nj-schools-6-12-must-provide-free-menstrual-products/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Sept. 10 (ZFJ) — School districts in New Jersey are now required to provide menstrual products for free in public schools that teach students of any grade from six through twelve.&#xA;Applicable schools will have to provide tampons and sanitary napkins (pads) in at least half of all their female and gender-neutral bathrooms. The state government will shoulder the costs for doing so.&#xA;The law addresses period poverty—one in four students in the U.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ: Menlo Park, Paramus veterans homes violated civil rights with inadequate medical care</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/doj-menlo-park-veterans-home-civil-rights-investigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 23:38:12 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/doj-menlo-park-veterans-home-civil-rights-investigation/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Sept. 12 (ZFJ) — State-run veterans homes at Menlo Park and Paramus have failed to adequately respond to the COVID-19 pandemic and provide medical care to their residents, announced the Justice Department on Thursday, Sept. 7.&#xA;The feds said that the conditions at the veterans homes, which provide long-term nursing care to veterans and their families and are under the New Jersey Department of Military and Veterans Affairs (DMAVA), violate the Fourteenth Amendment right to reasonable safety when in the state’s care.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC authorities identify two new 9/11 victims</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/nyc-identifies-two-new-9-11-victims/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 21:05:42 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/nyc-identifies-two-new-9-11-victims/</guid>
      <description>Sept. 11 (ZFJ) — The 1,648th and 1,649th victims from the World Trade Center attacks on Sept. 11, 2001, have been identified, announced the New York City Office of Chief Medical Examiner on Friday, Sept. 8.&#xA;These two victims are the first new identifications of 9/11 victims since September 2021. About 1,104 victims, or 40% of the 2,753 who died, remain unidentified.&#xA;This year, the OCME also identified 60 human remains connected to previously identified individuals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cecilia Birge appointed Princeton High principal</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/princeton-high-school-new-principal-birge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 20:39:45 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/princeton-high-school-new-principal-birge/</guid>
      <description>Sept. 10 (ZFJ) — Cecilia Xie Birge was appointed principal of Princeton High School on Thursday, Aug. 31.&#xA;The Princeton Board of Education voted unanimously for her at a special meeting. Board member Michele Tuck-Ponder was not present.&#xA;“With Cecilia’s appointment tonight, we are turning a page and we are looking with excitement to the future,” said Dafna Kendal, president of the school board.&#xA;Birge thanked the board and search committee for entrusting her with the position and recognized the school staff’s work for Princeton High.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edison middle school teacher charged with possession of child pornography</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/edison-middle-school-teacher-charged-child-porn-possession/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 22:01:14 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/edison-middle-school-teacher-charged-child-porn-possession/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Aug. 30 (ZFJ) — Edison middle school teacher Julius Coaccioli, 55, was arrested and charged with third-degree possession of child pornography on Wednesday, Aug. 30, announced Middlesex County Prosecutor Yolanda Ciccone and Woodbridge Police Department Director Robert Hubner.&#xA;Coaccioli taught science at Woodrow Wilson Middle School at the time of his arrest. According to public payroll records, he has worked for the Edison Board of Education since September 1992.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US federal district court judge rules AI art not copyrightable</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/dc-district-judge-ai-art-not-copyrightable/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 14:45:56 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/dc-district-judge-ai-art-not-copyrightable/</guid>
      <description>Aug. 23 (ZFJ) — AI art generated “absent human involvement” is not eligible for copyright, ruled U.S. District Judge Beryl A. Howell on Aug. 18, Friday.&#xA;In her ruling for the federal district court in Washington, D.C., Howell upheld the U.S. Copyright Office’s denial of registration to computer scientist Stephen Thaler for the work he calls A Recent Entrance to Paradise.&#xA;BACKGROUND&#xA;Thaler, the plaintiff, owns an AI called the “Creativity Machine” that can generate visual works of art.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pittsburgh synagogue shooter sentenced to death</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/pittsburgh-synagogue-shooter-death-sentence/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 23:54:57 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/pittsburgh-synagogue-shooter-death-sentence/</guid>
      <description>Aug. 7 (ZFJ) — Robert Bowers, 50, was sentenced to death by U.S. District Judge Robert J. Colville on Thursday, Aug. 3, for killing 11 congregants, wounding two others, and injuring five police officers at the Tree of Life Synagogue in Pittsburgh.&#xA;“I have nothing specific that I care to say to Mr. Bowers,” Colville said, according to The Associated Press. “I am however convinced there is nothing I could say to him that might be meaningful.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backup driver pleads guilty for first death caused by fully autonomous car</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/backup-driver-pleads-guilty-fully-autonomous-car-first-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 23:50:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/backup-driver-pleads-guilty-fully-autonomous-car-first-death/</guid>
      <description>Aug. 3 (ZFJ) — Rafaela Vasquez, 49, pled guilty to endangerment on Friday, July 28, for failing to stop a fully self-driving car from hitting and killing a 49-year-old woman.&#xA;Maricopa County Superior Court Judge David W. Garbarino sentenced her to three years of supervised probation. Her charge will be designated a misdemeanor once she completes her sentence.&#xA;On March 18, 2018, Vasquez was the backup driver for a test vehicle belonging to Uber’s Advanced Technologies Group (ATG).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Edward Aldarelli appointed Edison schools superintendent</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/aldarelli-appointed-edison-superintendent/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 23:10:52 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/aldarelli-appointed-edison-superintendent/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., July 29 (ZFJ) — Dr. Edward Aldarelli was appointed superintendent of Edison Township Public Schools on Thursday, July 27.&#xA;The Edison Board of Education voted unanimously for him after four hours of candidate interviewing at a special meeting.&#xA;“Definitely, no doubt, absolutely yes,” said Board President Shannon Peng, topping off board member Mohin Patel’s “absolutely yes” and Jerry Shi’s “absolutely, absolutely yes.”&#xA;Aldarelli was “overwhelmed” that the board chose him to lead the district, which has over 16,000 students.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Middlesex County man admits to threatening attack on synagogue</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/middlesex-man-threat-synagogue-guilty-plea/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 00:01:49 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/middlesex-man-threat-synagogue-guilty-plea/</guid>
      <description>July 16 (ZFJ) – A Middlesex County man admitted to threatening to attack a synagogue and Jewish people via the internet.&#xA;19-year-old Omar Alkattoul pleaded guilty to one count of transmitting a threat in interstate and foreign commerce on Wednesday, July 12, regarding a crime committed around November 1, 2021.&#xA;Alkattoul used social media to share a link of his manifesto titled “When Swords Collide.” The document detailed his plans to attack a synagogue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US completes destruction of its declared chemical weapons stockpile</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/us-destroys-chemical-weapons-stockpile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 19:34:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/us-destroys-chemical-weapons-stockpile/</guid>
      <description>July 10 (ZFJ) — The last possessor state, America, announced that it finished destroying its declared chemical weapons stockpile on Friday, July 7, marking the first time an international body verified the destruction of an entire category of declared weapons of mass destruction.&#xA;The stockpile was declared to the Organisation for the Prohibition of Chemical Weapons, the international body responsible for implementing the Chemical Weapons Convention. The 1997 arms control treaty prohibits its 193 members from developing or stockpiling chemical weapons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court strikes down affirmative action in college admissions</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/supreme-court-ruling-affirmative-action-harvard-admissions-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 23:05:33 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/supreme-court-ruling-affirmative-action-harvard-admissions-case/</guid>
      <description>July 3 (ZFJ) — Affirmative action in college admissions violates the Equal Protection Clause of the Fourteenth Amendment, ruled the Supreme Court in Students for Fair Admissions v. Harvard (20-1199) and SFFA v. University of North Carolina (21-707) on Thursday, June 29. The EPC prohibits racial discrimination by the government.&#xA;Reversing the lower courts’ decisions, the Court struck down the admissions programs used by Harvard and UNC by a 6-2 and 6-3 vote, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian wildfire smoke descends on US East Coast</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/canadian-wildfire-smoke-descends-on-us-east-coast/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 23:01:10 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/canadian-wildfire-smoke-descends-on-us-east-coast/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., June 7 (ZFJ) — Smoke from Canadian wildfires drifted into the eastern and central U.S., tinting the sky orange and triggering air quality alerts on Wednesday.&#xA;Canadian authorities are battling “one of the worst wildfire seasons on record,” said Steven Guilbeault, Canadian minister of environment and climate change. The country is currently facing over 400 wildfires, with over half out of control, according to the Canadian Interagency Forest Fire Centre.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court limits federal authority over wetlands with stricter test</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/supreme-court-limits-federal-wetlands-authority-sackett/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 15:08:10 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/supreme-court-limits-federal-wetlands-authority-sackett/</guid>
      <description>May 28 (ZFJ) — The federal government can only regulate wetlands with “a continuous surface connection” to adjacent “waters of the United States” under the Clean Water Act (1972), ruled the Supreme Court on Thursday, May 25, in Sackett v. EPA (21-454).&#xA;The CWA is the primary federal law regulating water pollution and prohibits the “discharge of any pollutant,” including “chemical wastes,” “rock,” and “sand,” into “navigable waters,” defined as “the waters of the United States, including the territorial seas.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
