<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sports on The Zombie Fridge Journal</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/sports/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sports on The Zombie Fridge Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 00:05:02 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/sports/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>JP Stevens football makes history, upsets Bound Brook in season opener</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/sports/2024/jps-football-win-losing-streak-broken-bound-brook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 00:05:02 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/sports/2024/jps-football-win-losing-streak-broken-bound-brook/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Sept. 21 (ZFJ) — Call it a miracle, or maybe even divine intervention.&#xA;On Friday, Sept. 6, the John P. Stevens High School (Edison, NJ) varsity football team defeated cross-county rival Bound Brook by a score of 22-21, putting an end to an infamous losing streak that had extended back to November of the 2018-2019 season.&#xA;“I’m feeling great, man,” said JPS senior quarterback Marquise Webb to Central Jersey Sports Radio after the game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maryland cruises past UConn in season-opening football blowout</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/sports/2024/maryland-defeats-connecticut-opening-football/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 14:09:41 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/sports/2024/maryland-defeats-connecticut-opening-football/</guid>
      <description>COLLEGE PARK, Md., Sept. 1 (ZFJ) — The Maryland Terrapins cruised to a dominant 50-7 victory over the UConn Huskies at SECU Stadium on Saturday, Aug. 31, coming together in a full offensive and defensive effort to begin the 2024 campaign on a high note.&#xA;“Great team win, and great start to the 2024 season,” began Head Coach Michael Locksley during the team’s postgame press conference. “We were able to do it today with all three phases contributing to the win.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edison Board of Education retires #24 for Edison High athletes in honor of Coach Jim Muldowney</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/sports/2024/edison-boe-retires-ehs-athletics-jersey-number-24-muldowney/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 20:44:14 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/sports/2024/edison-boe-retires-ehs-athletics-jersey-number-24-muldowney/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Aug. 29 (ZFJ) — The Edison Board of Education retired the use of jersey number 24 for all Edison High School athletic teams in honor of late baseball coach and athletic director James “Diamond Jim” Muldowney at the Aug. 20 combined caucus and public meeting.&#xA;Muldowney graduated from Edison High in 1973 and became a teacher from 1981-2000. He then served as the school’s athletic director from 2000-2008 and the district’s supervisor of physical education and health from 2008-2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jim Muldowney, former Edison High baseball coach and athletic director, dies at 68</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/sports/2024/obituary-jim-muldowney-ehs-baseball-coach-athletic-director/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 22:22:44 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/sports/2024/obituary-jim-muldowney-ehs-baseball-coach-athletic-director/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., June 8 (ZFJ) — James “Diamond Jim” Muldowney, 68, an Edison High School baseball coach and athletic director, died on Tuesday, May 21, after briefly battling cancer.&#xA;“Jim dedicated his life to the betterment of students and athletes, leaving an indelible mark on the community,” reads his obituary. He was a mentor to countless students and coaches alike.&#xA;Muldowney was born in Pennsylvania and raised in Edison. He graduated from Edison High in 1973 and lived in North Brunswick for 33 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kansas City Chiefs defeat San Francisco 49ers 25-22 in Super Bowl LVIII</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/sports/2024/super-bowl-lviii-chiefs-defeat-49ers-25-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 21:16:20 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/sports/2024/super-bowl-lviii-chiefs-defeat-49ers-25-22/</guid>
      <description>Feb. 14 (ZFJ) — The Kansas City Chiefs defeated the San Francisco 49ers 25-22 in Super Bowl LVIII on Sunday, Feb. 11.&#xA;Securing their third Super Bowl win in five years, the Chiefs have achieved a dynasty.&#xA;The first half of the game was characterized by many punts and a few fumbles. Momentum really picked up from the second half. Overall? Absolutely thrilling game.&#xA;The Chiefs won the coin toss and deferred.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghelsey Go tops 1,000 points in girls&#39; basketball</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/sports/2024/ghelsey-go-scores-thousandth-point-ehs-girls-basketball/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 20:31:34 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/sports/2024/ghelsey-go-scores-thousandth-point-ehs-girls-basketball/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Jan. 11 (ZFJ) — Senior Ghelsey Go has become the seventh girl and ninth player overall to score 1,000 points in basketball at Edison High School.&#xA;She scored 29 points in the varsity game against JFK on Saturday, Jan. 6, achieving the milestone after four years in high school basketball.&#xA;“I can’t even lie, when I scored the last points, my mind just went blank. I was like, what happens next, what’s going to happen next, and we still had a game to play, so I don’t think I really celebrated right away,” Go said.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
