<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Opinions on The Zombie Fridge Journal</title>
    <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/opinion/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Opinions on The Zombie Fridge Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 02:22:22 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://theZFJ.github.io/opinion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Boba shops are optimal for first dates</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/opinion/2025/boba-shops-optimal-first-dates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 02:22:22 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/opinion/2025/boba-shops-optimal-first-dates/</guid>
      <description>Civil discourse is critical for every democracy, and with Valentine’s Day tomorrow (today? I’m writing this at two hours past midnight), it’s about time we discussed an issue that really matters to society: the optimal location for a first date.&#xA;I have the answer. After extensive research and analysis consisting of musing in the cool wind while gazing at the full moon as well as the documented results of two practical tests by me and my associates, I have concluded that bubble tea shops are perfect for first dates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: Deadpool &amp; Wolverine delivers as delight</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/opinion/2024/deadpool-and-wolverine-movie-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 18:38:31 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/opinion/2024/deadpool-and-wolverine-movie-review/</guid>
      <description>April of 2019. It was a beautiful day outside. Birds were singing, flowers were blooming, and on days like these kids like us would be playing a game of cricket. But not today. We were huddled in a circle, discussing theories for the upcoming Avengers movie. I was the main speaker, cooking up some mind blowing theories (I copied them from MatPat[1]). There was some sort of magic in those movies you couldn’t find anywhere else.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: Five Nights at Freddy’s: A Fun Flick for Fans</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/opinion/2023/akira-rorschach-fnaf-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 01:52:12 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/opinion/2023/akira-rorschach-fnaf-review/</guid>
      <description>I don’t usually watch horror films (I get very scared), but the lunch table gang invited me to see the FNAF movie, so, of course, I made an exception this time. Also, I was intrigued after hearing mixed reviews from my classmates and decided I wanted to see it for myself.&#xA;I used to be terrified seeing the animatronics back in elementary school. That all went out the window after they released the Security Breach game a few years ago.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
