<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Science-and-Technologies on The Zombie Fridge Journal</title>
    <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Science-and-Technologies on The Zombie Fridge Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 23:01:06 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>US Approves Nation’s First Lab-Grown Meat, Cell Cultivated Chicken, for Sale</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2023/america-approves-first-lab-grown-meat-for-sale/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 23:01:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2023/america-approves-first-lab-grown-meat-for-sale/</guid>
      <description>June 24 (ZFJ) — Lab-grown meat companies UPSIDE Foods and GOOD Meat announced on Wednesday that they received the final Agriculture Department approval required to sell their chicken in the United States.
The Department of Agriculture Food Safety and Inspection Service issued grants of inspection for the companies’ manufacturing facilities: UPSIDE’s Engineering, Production, and Innovation Center and GOOD Meat’s demonstration plant in Alameda, California. GOOD Meat’s contract manufacturing partner JOINN Biologics also received a GOI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>66% Chance World Exceeds Warming Threshold Before 2027, WMO Says</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2023/66-chance-world-exceeds-warming-threshold-before-2027/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 21:32:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2023/66-chance-world-exceeds-warming-threshold-before-2027/</guid>
      <description>May 18 (ZFJ) — There is a 66% chance that the annual global surface temperature will exceed 1.5 degrees Celsius (2.7 degrees Fahrenheit) above pre-industrial levels before 2027, said the World Meteorological Organization on Wednesday.
The UN weather agency also predicted that there is a 98% chance that one of the next five years will be the warmest on record.
“These new highs will be fuelled almost completely by the rise of heat-trapping greenhouse gases in the atmosphere, but the anticipated development of the naturally-occurring El Niño event will also release heat from the tropical Pacific,” said Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
