<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Zombie Fridge Journal</title>
    <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Zombie Fridge Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 21:32:50 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://theZFJ.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>66% Chance World Exceeds Warming Threshold Before 2027, WMO Says</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2023/66-chance-world-exceeds-warming-threshold-before-2027/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 21:32:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2023/66-chance-world-exceeds-warming-threshold-before-2027/</guid>
      <description>May 18 — There is a 66% chance that the annual global surface temperature will exceed 1.5 degrees Celsius (2.7 degrees Fahrenheit) above pre-industrial levels before 2027, said the World Meteorological Organization on Wednesday.
The UN weather agency also predicted that there is a 98% chance that one of the next five years will be the warmest on record.
“These new highs will be fuelled almost completely by the rise of heat-trapping greenhouse gases in the atmosphere, but the anticipated development of the naturally-occurring El Niño event will also release heat from the tropical Pacific,” said Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[CENSORED VERSION] Return from Winter Break Brings Mixed Emotions</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/jan2022censorshipincident/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/jan2022censorshipincident/</guid>
      <description>Editor-in-chief Wu&amp;rsquo;s Note:
The article below is the original version of the article published 2022-01-07 in The Eagle&amp;rsquo;s Eye, archived by me, one of its writers. I proposed the article and received approval on New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve 2021 after the school district sent a community letter about the return to school during the largest surge in COVID-19 cases per day in the pandemic in the United States. I asked the Edison Board of Education questions at their public meeting on 2022-01-03 and interviewed various students for their opinions before winter break ended.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>The Zombie Fridge Journal is a student-run newspaper reporting on general affairs and based in the New York City metropolitan area.
Its personnel are amateurs, so this journalism project could crash and burn at any time. They do what they do for fun.
Editor-in-chief Wu decided to create it after the Jan 2022 Censorship Incident, but it took him over a year and several holiday breaks to set up the website because he greatly prefers napping to working.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
