<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Zombie Fridge Journal</title>
    <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Zombie Fridge Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 22:10:50 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://theZFJ.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>FDA approves two sickle cell disease gene therapies, one based on CRISPR</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/health-and-medicine/2023/fda-approves-sickle-cell-casgevy-crispr-lyfgenia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 22:10:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/health-and-medicine/2023/fda-approves-sickle-cell-casgevy-crispr-lyfgenia/</guid>
      <description>Dec. 30 (ZFJ) — The U.S. Food and Drug Administration approved two cell-based gene therapies, Casgevy and Lyfgenia, to treat sickle cell disease in patients 12 years and older, the agency announced on Dec. 8, 2023. Casgevy is the first FDA-approved treatment to use CRISPR/Cas9 gene-editing technology.
Sickle cell disease is a group of inherited blood disorders. It affects about 100,000 Americans, is most common in African Americans, and also affects Hispanic Americans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taylor Swift tops 2023 Spotify global streams</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/arts-and-entertainment/2023/2023-spotify-wrapped-trends-taylor-swift/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 01:28:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/arts-and-entertainment/2023/2023-spotify-wrapped-trends-taylor-swift/</guid>
      <description>Dec. 28 (ZFJ) — Taylor Swift became Spotify’s top global artist of 2023 with over 26.1 billion streams worldwide, announced the music streaming platform in its 2023 Wrapped campaign on Nov. 29.
She dethroned Bad Bunny, who’d held the title for the past three years. Coming in second place, he had a “standout year” with his new album nadie sabe lo que va a pasar mañana. The Weeknd, Drake, and Peso Pluma also made the top five.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Military air defense command NORAD tracks Santa in annual tradition</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/norad-tracks-santa-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 21:37:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/norad-tracks-santa-2023/</guid>
      <description>Dec. 24 (ZFJ) — NORAD, with 68 years of experience following Santa, is once again tracking the jolly good man.
Anyone interested can view Santa’s location on noradsanta.org or call in to the North American Aerospace Defense Command at 1-877-HI-NORAD. If they can’t reach a human on the line due to the volume of calls, they’ll receive an automated message reporting Santa’s position and a reminder to call back later to talk to someone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perth Amboy Magnet carpentry teacher charged with criminal sexual contact</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/perth-amboy-magnet-carpentry-teacher-charged-criminal-sexual-contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 22:23:28 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/perth-amboy-magnet-carpentry-teacher-charged-criminal-sexual-contact/</guid>
      <description>Dec. 23 (ZFJ) — Edward White, 56, of Tinton Falls, N.J., was arrested on charges of inappropriately touching students on Dec. 13, announced Middlesex County Prosecutor Yolanda Ciccone and Chief Lawrence Cattano of the Perth Amboy Police Department.
In a statement on Dec. 14, a Thursday, Middlesex County Magnet Schools Superintendent Jorge E. Diaz said that the school district became aware of an “alleged incident involving a teacher and a student” on Dec.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>J.P. Stevens High School closed Monday, other schools delayed due to flooding</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/jps-edison-public-schools-storm-flooding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 23:24:37 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/jps-edison-public-schools-storm-flooding/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Dec. 18 (ZFJ) — J.P. Stevens High School was closed on Monday, Dec. 18, due to flooding and road closures while several other North Edison schools opened late.
John Adams Middle School, James Madison Primary School, James Madison Intermediate School, and FDR Preschool had delayed openings. JPS was also going to open delayed until officials decided to close it for the day. Other Edison schools continued their days on their regular schedules.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fed holds interest rate steady for year end</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/business/2023/december-fomc-meeting-interest-rates-held/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 16:57:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/business/2023/december-fomc-meeting-interest-rates-held/</guid>
      <description>Dec. 17 (ZFJ) — The Fed maintained the target federal funds rate at 5.25-5.50% for the third time in a row on Wednesday, Dec. 13, noting that inflation has eased but is still elevated.
“Inflation has eased from its highs, and this has come without a significant increase in unemployment,” said Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell. “This is very good news. But inflation is still too high, ongoing progress in bringing it down is not assured, and the path forward is uncertain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Edison releases inspection reports on animal shelter deficiencies</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/edison-animal-shelter-inspection-reports/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 14:23:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/edison-animal-shelter-inspection-reports/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Dec. 10 (ZFJ) — Edison has released two veterinarians’ inspection reports on the condition of its animal shelter and a memorandum about the township’s response from early November.
The reports highlight problems relating to health, overcrowding, and management and recommend immediate action.
The Edison Animal Shelter serves Metuchen, Piscataway, Dunellen, Highland Park, and Edison.
DR. CHIOSI’S REPORT
Joseph R. Chiosi, doctor of veterinary medicine, of Sayrebrook Veterinary Hospital in Sayreville conducted an inspection on July 20, 2023, after performing exams and administering vaccines for adopters’ pets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Edison police arrest Maryland attempted murder suspect after car chase</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/edison-police-arrest-attempted-murder-suspect-car-chase/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 23:30:41 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/edison-police-arrest-attempted-murder-suspect-car-chase/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Dec. 6 (ZFJ) — A suspect wanted for attempted murder in Maryland was arrested by Edison police after an hour-long motor vehicle pursuit on Sunday, Dec. 3.
At 20:13 on Sunday, Edison police dispatch received a Sirius XM alert that a stolen white 2019 Subaru Outback with Maryland license plates had entered the township near U.S. Highway 1 and Main Street.
While near 2900 Woodbridge Avenue, Edison Police Officer Phil Smith saw the vehicle traveling at a high speed and began tailing it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global temperature briefly exceeds 2 C above pre-industrial average</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2023/first-time-global-temperature-anomaly-exceeds-two-celsius/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 14:01:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2023/first-time-global-temperature-anomaly-exceeds-two-celsius/</guid>
      <description>Dec. 2 (ZFJ) — Earth’s temperature exceeded 2 degrees Celsius above pre-industrial levels on Nov. 17-18, according to the European Union’s Copernicus Climate Change Service (C3S).
Nov. 17 marked the first day in the ERA5 dataset, the European Centre for Medium Range Weather Forecasts’ climate record, that global temperatures exceeded 2 C above the average temperature before the extensive use of fossil fuels.
Nov. 17 exceeded the 1850-1900 average by 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Police: South Plainfield man shot three of his family members, called 911</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/south-plainfield-condo-complex-shooting-affidavit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 01:44:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/south-plainfield-condo-complex-shooting-affidavit/</guid>
      <description>SOUTH PLAINFIELD, N.J., Nov. 30 (ZFJ) — Authorities have accused Om Brahmbhatt, 23, of fatally shooting three of his family members on Monday at the Traditions condominium complex.
The Middlesex County Prosecutor’s Office has charged Brahmbhatt with three counts of first-degree murder and three counts of second-degree possession of a weapon for an unlawful purpose.
According to an affidavit submitted by the police to establish probable cause for an arrest warrant, South Plainfield Police Department officers responded to a 911 call on Monday, Nov.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Man charged for South Plainfield condo complex triple killing</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/south-plainfield-condo-complex-triple-shooting-arrest/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 22:55:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/south-plainfield-condo-complex-triple-shooting-arrest/</guid>
      <description>SOUTH PLAINFIELD, N.J., Nov. 28 (ZFJ) — A South Plainfield man has been arrested and charged in connection with the Coppola Drive shooting on Monday, Nov. 27, announced Middlesex County Prosecutor Yolanda Ciccone and Chief Peter Papa of the South Plainfield Police Department.
Om Brahmbhatt, 23, was arrested without incident and charged with three counts of first-degree murder and three counts of second-degree possession of a weapon for an unlawful purpose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minecraft YouTuber Stampy Cat ends 11-year Lovely World series</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/arts-and-entertainment/2023/stampy-cat-ends-lovely-world-series-minecraft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 01:12:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/arts-and-entertainment/2023/stampy-cat-ends-lovely-world-series-minecraft/</guid>
      <description>Nov. 25 (ZFJ) — Minecraft YouTuber Stampy Cat uploaded the finale to his 11-year series, Stampy’s Lovely World, on Saturday, Oct. 21.
The 823rd episode marked the end of the series, which began on May 19, 2012 (only 10 days after Minecraft: Xbox 360 Edition released). He was a dominant personality in the Minecraft YouTube scene from 2013 to 2017 and pioneered the video format of storytelling using the blocky game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Actor strike ends with agreement on AI, compensation</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/arts-and-entertainment/2023/actor-strike-ends-sag-aftra-amptp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 12:01:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/arts-and-entertainment/2023/actor-strike-ends-sag-aftra-amptp/</guid>
      <description>Nov. 19 (ZFJ) — SAG-AFTRA ended its 118-day strike at 12:01 PT on Thursday, Nov. 9, after the union’s TV/Theatrical Negotiating Committee unanimously approved an agreement with provisions on artificial intelligence in films and actor compensation.
On Friday, Nov. 10, the SAG-AFTRA National Board approved the agreement with 86% of the vote. Union members now have until Tuesday, Dec. 5, to vote on ratifying the contract. SAG-AFTRA represents about 160,000 media professionals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court hears arguments on constitutionality of domestic violence gun ban</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/domestic-violence-gun-ban-oral-argument-supreme-court/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 18:39:28 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/domestic-violence-gun-ban-oral-argument-supreme-court/</guid>
      <description>Nov. 12 (ZFJ) — The Supreme Court heard arguments on whether a federal ban on firearms possession by people under domestic violence restraining orders violates the Second Amendment in the case United States v. Rahimi (22-915) on Tuesday, Nov. 7.
The statute in question, 18 U.S.C. § 922(g)(8), prohibits people who are under a restraining order from possessing guns. The court order must include a finding that the person is a credible threat to an “intimate partner or child” or explicitly prohibit any physical force against them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ørsted pulls out of two NJ offshore wind farm projects</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/business/2023/orsted-pulls-out-nj-first-two-wind-farms/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 11:25:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/business/2023/orsted-pulls-out-nj-first-two-wind-farms/</guid>
      <description>Nov. 10 (ZFJ) — Ørsted has pulled out of developing two offshore wind farms, set to have been New Jersey’s first ones, due to economic challenges, the company announced on Tuesday, Oct. 31.
“Macroeconomic factors have changed dramatically over a short period of time, with high inflation, rising interest rates, and supply chain bottlenecks impacting our long-term capital investments,” said David Hardy, group executive vice president and CEO of Ørsted Americas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democrats sweep Edison council as White, Lugo, Patel win board of education</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/2023-edison-local-elections-council-boe/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 19:29:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/2023-edison-local-elections-council-boe/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Nov. 8 (ZFJ) — The Democrats won the four available seats on the Edison Township Council while Virginia White, Christopher Lugo, and Anjana R. Patel secured three spots on the Edison Board of Education, according to unofficial results from the Middlesex County Clerk for the Nov. 7 general election.
Richard Brescher, Joseph A. Coyle, and Ajay V. Patil won reelection to the town council along with newcomer Asaf Shmuel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: Five Nights at Freddy’s: A Fun Flick for Fans</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/opinion/2023/akira-rorschach-fnaf-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 01:52:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/opinion/2023/akira-rorschach-fnaf-review/</guid>
      <description>I don’t usually watch horror films (I get very scared), but the lunch table gang invited me to see the FNAF movie, so, of course, I made an exception this time. Also, I was intrigued after hearing mixed reviews from my classmates and decided I wanted to see it for myself.
I used to be terrified seeing the animatronics back in elementary school. That all went out the window after they released the Security Breach game a few years ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fed holds interest rate steady for second time in a row</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/business/2023/fomc-november-1-interest-rate-steady-twice/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 21:33:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/business/2023/fomc-november-1-interest-rate-steady-twice/</guid>
      <description>Nov. 5 (ZFJ) — The Federal Reserve maintained the interest rate at 5.25-5.50% for the second time in a row on Wednesday, Nov. 1.
This rate was set on July 26 and held steady on Sept. 20. The Fed has been aggressively increasing the interest rate since it raised it from 0.00-0.25% to 0.25-0.50% in March 2022 in order to fight stubborn inflation.
Economic activity has been expanding at a strong pace, said Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>School bus crashes into Edison home, no serious injuries</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/school-bus-crashes-into-edison-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 02:29:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/school-bus-crashes-into-edison-home/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Oct. 19 (ZFJ) — A school bus with 28 John Adams Middle School students on board crashed into an Edison home on Rahway Road in the morning on Wednesday, Oct. 18.
The bus, operated by contracted route provider Joy Transport, collided with the house’s garage, which sustained heavy damage. The house has been condemned by township inspectors for being structurally unsound.
The cause of the crash is believed to be a brake failure, said Edison Police Chief Thomas Bryan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grand jury clears Edison cops for April 2022 fatal shooting</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/grand-jury-no-charges-edison-police-deadly-force-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 15:28:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/grand-jury-no-charges-edison-police-deadly-force-2022/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Oct. 15 (ZFJ) — A state grand jury declined to criminally charge two Edison police officers who shot Merrill Rambarose, 49, of Edison on April 12, 2022.
Witness interviews, photographs, video footage of the shooting, and autopsy results were presented to the grand jury, which concluded deliberations on Sept. 25 and voted “no bill”—meaning Officers Daniel Bradley and Joseph Elqumos will not have criminal charges filed against them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raritan Valley EMS rebrands to Edison EMS</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/rvrems-rebranding-edison-ems/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 00:50:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/rvrems-rebranding-edison-ems/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Oct. 7 (ZFJ) — Edison Emergency Medical Services has officially rebranded from Raritan Valley Regional EMS, the agency announced in a Sept. 28 Instagram post.
Edison EMS is the non-profit volunteer first aid squad serving Edison and its surrounding areas for free.
RVREMS was formed in 2009 when Edison First Aid &amp;amp; Rescue Squad #1, Edison First Aid Squad #2, and Clara Barton First Aid Squad merged.
Edison EMS continues to operate out of the original stations, which have been renamed to Edison EMS Station 1, 2, and 3, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FEMA to conduct nationwide emergency alert test</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/fema-emergency-alert-test-october-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 16:55:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/fema-emergency-alert-test-october-2023/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Oct. 2 (ZFJ) — The federal government will test two national emergency alert systems on Wednesday, Oct. 4, starting at about 14:20 (2:20 p.m.) EDT.
The Federal Emergency Management Agency, in conjunction with the Federal Communications Commission, will conduct the two-part test.
The first portion will test Wireless Emergency Alerts, which are directed at cell phones.
For 30 minutes, cell towers will broadcast the message “THIS IS A TEST of the National Wireless Emergency Alert System.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charles Martinet, voice of Super Mario, retires</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/arts-and-entertainment/2023/charles-martinet-mario-va-retires/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 23:13:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/arts-and-entertainment/2023/charles-martinet-mario-va-retires/</guid>
      <description>Sept. 23 (ZFJ) — Charles Martinet, known as the voice of Super Mario, Luigi, Wario, and Waluigi, is retiring from voice acting.
“It’s been such an honor, and such a joy, for so many years, that I look forward to continuing to bring that joy and help us all remember our innocence, and our happiness, and our joy, through great games,” Martinet said in a video message posted by Nintendo of America on Sept.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NJ requires schools to provide students grades 6-12 free menstrual products</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/nj-schools-6-12-must-provide-free-menstrual-products/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 00:49:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/nj-schools-6-12-must-provide-free-menstrual-products/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Sept. 10 (ZFJ) — School districts in New Jersey are now required to provide menstrual products for free in public schools that teach students of any grade from six through twelve.
Applicable schools will have to provide tampons and sanitary napkins (pads) in at least half of all their female and gender-neutral bathrooms. The state government will shoulder the costs for doing so.
The law addresses period poverty—one in four students in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fontaine comes to Genshin Impact</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/arts-and-entertainment/2023/genshin-impact-new-nation-fontaine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 23:54:09 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/arts-and-entertainment/2023/genshin-impact-new-nation-fontaine/</guid>
      <description>Sept. 17 (ZFJ) — Put on your top hats and button your shirts, because Teyvat’s new nation and realm of Hydro, Fontaine, has finally released! HoYoverse—the creators of Genshin Impact—has pulled back the curtain on a land brimming with court trials, performances, and magic shows.
Inside the walls of Fontaine&amp;rsquo;s city are multiple levels of homes, shops, and restaurants to explore. ZFJ/Kirby Kim
Inside the walls of Fontaine&amp;rsquo;s city are multiple levels of homes, shops, and restaurants to explore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DOJ: Menlo Park, Paramus veterans homes violated civil rights with inadequate medical care</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/doj-menlo-park-veterans-home-civil-rights-investigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 23:38:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/doj-menlo-park-veterans-home-civil-rights-investigation/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Sept. 12 (ZFJ) — State-run veterans homes at Menlo Park and Paramus have failed to adequately respond to the COVID-19 pandemic and provide medical care to their residents, announced the Justice Department on Thursday, Sept. 7.
The feds said that the conditions at the veterans homes, which provide long-term nursing care to veterans and their families and are under the New Jersey Department of Military and Veterans Affairs (DMAVA), violate the Fourteenth Amendment right to reasonable safety when in the state’s care.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NYC authorities identify two new 9/11 victims</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/nyc-identifies-two-new-9-11-victims/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 21:05:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/nyc-identifies-two-new-9-11-victims/</guid>
      <description>Sept. 11 (ZFJ) — The 1,648th and 1,649th victims from the World Trade Center attacks on Sept. 11, 2001, have been identified, announced the New York City Office of Chief Medical Examiner on Friday, Sept. 8.
These two victims are the first new identifications of 9/11 victims since September 2021. About 1,104 victims, or 40% of the 2,753 who died, remain unidentified.
This year, the OCME also identified 60 human remains connected to previously identified individuals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cecilia Birge appointed Princeton High principal</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/princeton-high-school-new-principal-birge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 20:39:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/princeton-high-school-new-principal-birge/</guid>
      <description>Sept. 10 (ZFJ) — Cecilia Xie Birge was appointed principal of Princeton High School on Thursday, Aug. 31.
The Princeton Board of Education voted unanimously for her at a special meeting. Board member Michele Tuck-Ponder was not present.
“With Cecilia’s appointment tonight, we are turning a page and we are looking with excitement to the future,” said Dafna Kendal, president of the school board.
Birge thanked the board and search committee for entrusting her with the position and recognized the school staff’s work for Princeton High.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Edison middle school teacher charged with possession of child pornography</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/edison-middle-school-teacher-charged-child-porn-possession/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 22:01:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/edison-middle-school-teacher-charged-child-porn-possession/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Aug. 30 (ZFJ) — Edison middle school teacher Julius Coaccioli, 55, was arrested and charged with third-degree possession of child pornography on Wednesday, Aug. 30, announced Middlesex County Prosecutor Yolanda Ciccone and Woodbridge Police Department Director Robert Hubner.
Coaccioli taught science at Woodrow Wilson Middle School at the time of his arrest. According to public payroll records, he has worked for the Edison Board of Education since September 1992.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US federal district court judge rules AI art not copyrightable</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/dc-district-judge-ai-art-not-copyrightable/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 14:45:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/dc-district-judge-ai-art-not-copyrightable/</guid>
      <description>Aug. 23 (ZFJ) — AI art generated “absent human involvement” is not eligible for copyright, ruled U.S. District Judge Beryl A. Howell on Aug. 18, Friday.
In her ruling for the federal district court in Washington, D.C., Howell upheld the U.S. Copyright Office’s denial of registration to computer scientist Stephen Thaler for the work he calls A Recent Entrance to Paradise.
BACKGROUND
Thaler, the plaintiff, owns an AI called the “Creativity Machine” that can generate visual works of art.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US, South Korea, and Japan agree to increase defense, economic cooperation at summit</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/foreign-affairs/asia-pacific/2023/us-kr-jp-summit-camp-david/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:18:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/foreign-affairs/asia-pacific/2023/us-kr-jp-summit-camp-david/</guid>
      <description>Aug. 21 (ZFJ) — President Joe Biden, South Korea’s President Yoon Suk Yeol, and Japan’s Prime Minister Fumio Kishida agreed to increase defense and economic cooperation among their countries at a Camp David summit on Friday, Aug. 18.
This meeting is the first-ever standalone summit between the leaders of Japan, South Korea, and the United States.
Japan and South Korea continue to have disputes over former Imperial Japan’s colonial rule from 1910-1945.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 2023 confirmed hottest month on record globally</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2023/july-2023-breaks-heat-records/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 12:18:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2023/july-2023-breaks-heat-records/</guid>
      <description>Aug. 14 (ZFJ) — July 2023 was the hottest month on record globally, confirmed the Copernicus Climate Change Service on Tuesday, Aug. 8.
The monthly average temperature worldwide was 16.95 degrees Celsius (62.51 degrees Fahrenheit), exceeding July 2019’s previous record of 16.63 C (61.93 F) and meeting the Paris Agreement threshold of 1.5 C (2.7 F) warming above preindustrial levels.
The 29 days from July 3-31 were the hottest days on record, exceeding the previous daily global mean surface air temperature record of 16.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taco Bell will fund your Taco Tuesday—unless you’re in NJ</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/business/2023/taco-bell-taco-tuesday-promo-nj-excluded/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 22:34:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/business/2023/taco-bell-taco-tuesday-promo-nj-excluded/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Aug. 12 (ZFJ) — To celebrate its trademark battle win, Taco Bell will fund Taco Tuesday celebrations in all U.S. states except New Jersey, the company announced on Tuesday, Aug. 8.
On Tuesday, Sept. 12, Taco Bell, partnering with DoorDash, will spend $5 million to cover orders from participating Mexican food vendors.
“Taco Tuesday belongs to all who make, sell, eat, and celebrate tacos, and this Free-For-All will not only thank taco fans who supported the cause, but also spotlight local restaurants and vendors who can now embrace Taco Tuesdays without fear of legal action,” said Taco Bell U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pittsburgh synagogue shooter sentenced to death</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/pittsburgh-synagogue-shooter-death-sentence/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 23:54:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/pittsburgh-synagogue-shooter-death-sentence/</guid>
      <description>Aug. 7 (ZFJ) — Robert Bowers, 50, was sentenced to death by U.S. District Judge Robert J. Colville on Thursday, Aug. 3, for killing 11 congregants, wounding two others, and injuring five police officers at the Tree of Life Synagogue in Pittsburgh.
“I have nothing specific that I care to say to Mr. Bowers,” Colville said, according to The Associated Press. “I am however convinced there is nothing I could say to him that might be meaningful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backup driver pleads guilty for first death caused by fully autonomous car</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/backup-driver-pleads-guilty-fully-autonomous-car-first-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 23:50:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/backup-driver-pleads-guilty-fully-autonomous-car-first-death/</guid>
      <description>Aug. 3 (ZFJ) — Rafaela Vasquez, 49, pled guilty to endangerment on Friday, July 28, for failing to stop a fully self-driving car from hitting and killing a 49-year-old woman.
Maricopa County Superior Court Judge David W. Garbarino sentenced her to three years of supervised probation. Her charge will be designated a misdemeanor once she completes her sentence.
On March 18, 2018, Vasquez was the backup driver for a test vehicle belonging to Uber’s Advanced Technologies Group (ATG).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Edward Aldarelli appointed Edison schools superintendent</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/aldarelli-appointed-edison-superintendent/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 23:10:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/aldarelli-appointed-edison-superintendent/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., July 29 (ZFJ) — Dr. Edward Aldarelli was appointed superintendent of Edison Township Public Schools on Thursday, July 27.
The Edison Board of Education voted unanimously for him after four hours of candidate interviewing at a special meeting.
“Definitely, no doubt, absolutely yes,” said Board President Shannon Peng, topping off board member Mohin Patel’s “absolutely yes” and Jerry Shi’s “absolutely, absolutely yes.”
Aldarelli was “overwhelmed” that the board chose him to lead the district, which has over 16,000 students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UN Security Council holds first meeting on AI</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2023/un-security-council-first-meeting-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 13:20:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2023/un-security-council-first-meeting-ai/</guid>
      <description>July 25 (ZFJ) — The rapid increase in malicious uses of artificial intelligence has sparked international concern. On July 18, the United Nations Security Council gathered to recognize what AI could bring to the table and what it has already taken away.
U.N. Secretary-General António Guterres opened the meeting by observing the influence ChatGPT has garnered. ChatGPT, an AI that emulates human interaction, has taken over the internet by storm, infiltrating college applications, political propaganda, jobs, and other areas of daily life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Navy commissions littoral combat ship USS Canberra in Australia</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/foreign-affairs/asia-pacific/2023/uss-canberra-commissioned-australia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 21:46:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/foreign-affairs/asia-pacific/2023/uss-canberra-commissioned-australia/</guid>
      <description>July 24 (ZFJ) — The U.S. Navy commissioned Independence-class littoral combat ship USS Canberra (LCS 30) at the Royal Australian Navy’s Fleet Base East in Sydney on Saturday, July 22, marking the first time a U.S. ship entered service at a foreign port.
It is the second American ship named for Australia’s capital. The first was a Baltimore-heavy class cruiser, renamed in honor of the Australian heavy cruiser HMAS Canberra, which was lost at the Battle of Savo Island in WWII when defending U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Middlesex County man admits to threatening attack on synagogue</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/middlesex-man-threat-synagogue-guilty-plea/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 00:01:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/middlesex-man-threat-synagogue-guilty-plea/</guid>
      <description>July 16 (ZFJ) – A Middlesex County man admitted to threatening to attack a synagogue and Jewish people via the internet.
19-year-old Omar Alkattoul pleaded guilty to one count of transmitting a threat in interstate and foreign commerce on Wednesday, July 12, regarding a crime committed around November 1, 2021.
Alkattoul used social media to share a link of his manifesto titled “When Swords Collide.” The document detailed his plans to attack a synagogue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“Limited evidence” for aspartame as “possible carcinogen,” says WHO cancer agency</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/health-and-medicine/2023/who-aspartame-possible-carcinogen-limited-evidence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 23:37:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/health-and-medicine/2023/who-aspartame-possible-carcinogen-limited-evidence/</guid>
      <description>July 16 (ZFJ) — The World Health Organization’s cancer research agency categorized non-sugar sweetener aspartame as “possibly carcinogenic to humans” (group 2B) based on “limited evidence” for causing cancer in humans on Friday, July 14. A WHO joint panel did not change its acceptable daily limit of 40 mg/kg body weight.
Aspartame is an artificial sweetener that has been widely used in foods and beverages since the 1980s as an alternative to sugar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FDA grants traditional approval to Eisai/Biogen Alzheimer’s drug Leqembi</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/health-and-medicine/2023/fda-traditional-approval-leqembi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 03:07:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/health-and-medicine/2023/fda-traditional-approval-leqembi/</guid>
      <description>July 12 (ZFJ) — The Food and Drug Administration granted traditional approval to Eisai and Biogen’s Leqembi (lecanemab-irmb) 100 mg/mL intravenous injection on July 6. It is the first Alzheimer’s drug to clear this regulatory hurdle and aims to slow the disease’s progression.
“Today’s action is the first verification that a drug targeting the underlying disease process of Alzheimer’s disease has shown clinical benefit in this devastating disease,” said Teresa Buracchio, acting director of the Office of Neuroscience in FDA’s Center for Drug Evaluation and Research.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US completes destruction of its declared chemical weapons stockpile</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/us-destroys-chemical-weapons-stockpile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 19:34:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/us-destroys-chemical-weapons-stockpile/</guid>
      <description>July 10 (ZFJ) — The last possessor state, America, announced that it finished destroying its declared chemical weapons stockpile on Friday, July 7, marking the first time an international body verified the destruction of an entire category of declared weapons of mass destruction.
The stockpile was declared to the Organisation for the Prohibition of Chemical Weapons, the international body responsible for implementing the Chemical Weapons Convention. The 1997 arms control treaty prohibits its 193 members from developing or stockpiling chemical weapons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court strikes down affirmative action in college admissions</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/supreme-court-ruling-affirmative-action-harvard-admissions-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 23:05:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/supreme-court-ruling-affirmative-action-harvard-admissions-case/</guid>
      <description>July 3 (ZFJ) — Affirmative action in college admissions violates the Equal Protection Clause of the Fourteenth Amendment, ruled the Supreme Court in Students for Fair Admissions v. Harvard (20-1199) and SFFA v. University of North Carolina (21-707) on Thursday, June 29. The EPC prohibits racial discrimination by the government.
Reversing the lower courts’ decisions, the Court struck down the admissions programs used by Harvard and UNC by a 6-2 and 6-3 vote, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indian prime minister secures work visa changes for skilled workers in US visit</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/foreign-affairs/asia-pacific/2023/modi-work-visas-america-visit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 21:47:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/foreign-affairs/asia-pacific/2023/modi-work-visas-america-visit/</guid>
      <description>June 26 (ZFJ) — Indian Prime Minister Narendra Modi, in his recent visit to the United States, and President Joe Biden announced a pilot for the expansion of capacity for H-1B and L-1 visas with the domestic renewal of temporary work visas.
The loosening of visa restrictions aims to increase the amount of skilled workers and students immigrating to the U.S. Currently, this pilot launch is only applicable to the H-1B and L-1 visas, which both admit skilled workers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US approves nation’s first lab-grown meat, cell-cultivated chicken, for sale</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2023/america-approves-first-lab-grown-meat-for-sale/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 23:01:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2023/america-approves-first-lab-grown-meat-for-sale/</guid>
      <description>June 24 (ZFJ) — Lab-grown meat companies UPSIDE Foods and GOOD Meat announced on Wednesday that they received the final Agriculture Department approval required to sell their chicken in the United States.
The Department of Agriculture Food Safety and Inspection Service issued grants of inspection for the companies’ manufacturing facilities: UPSIDE’s Engineering, Production, and Innovation Center and GOOD Meat’s demonstration plant in Alameda, California. GOOD Meat’s contract manufacturing partner JOINN Biologics also received a GOI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canadian wildfire smoke descends on US East Coast</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/canadian-wildfire-smoke-descends-on-us-east-coast/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 23:01:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/canadian-wildfire-smoke-descends-on-us-east-coast/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., June 7 (ZFJ) — Smoke from Canadian wildfires drifted into the eastern and central U.S., tinting the sky orange and triggering air quality alerts on Wednesday.
Canadian authorities are battling “one of the worst wildfire seasons on record,” said Steven Guilbeault, Canadian minister of environment and climate change. The country is currently facing over 400 wildfires, with over half out of control, according to the Canadian Interagency Forest Fire Centre.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court limits federal authority over wetlands with stricter test</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/supreme-court-limits-federal-wetlands-authority-sackett/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 15:08:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/supreme-court-limits-federal-wetlands-authority-sackett/</guid>
      <description>May 28 (ZFJ) — The federal government can only regulate wetlands with “a continuous surface connection” to adjacent “waters of the United States” under the Clean Water Act (1972), ruled the Supreme Court on Thursday, May 25, in Sackett v. EPA (21-454).
The CWA is the primary federal law regulating water pollution and prohibits the “discharge of any pollutant,” including “chemical wastes,” “rock,” and “sand,” into “navigable waters,” defined as “the waters of the United States, including the territorial seas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>66% chance world exceeds warming threshold before 2027, WMO says</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2023/66-chance-world-exceeds-warming-threshold-before-2027/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 21:32:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2023/66-chance-world-exceeds-warming-threshold-before-2027/</guid>
      <description>May 18 (ZFJ) — There is a 66% chance that the annual global surface temperature will exceed 1.5 degrees Celsius (2.7 degrees Fahrenheit) above pre-industrial levels before 2027, said the World Meteorological Organization on Wednesday.
The UN weather agency also predicted that there is a 98% chance that one of the next five years will be the warmest on record.
“These new highs will be fuelled almost completely by the rise of heat-trapping greenhouse gases in the atmosphere, but the anticipated development of the naturally-occurring El Niño event will also release heat from the tropical Pacific,” said Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/arts-and-entertainment/2024/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/arts-and-entertainment/2024/readme/</guid>
      <description>2024-entertainment </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/business/2024/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/business/2024/readme/</guid>
      <description>2024-business </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/readme/</guid>
      <description>2024-domestic-affairs </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/foreign-affairs/africa/2024/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/foreign-affairs/africa/2024/readme/</guid>
      <description>2024-africa </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/foreign-affairs/americas/2024/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/foreign-affairs/americas/2024/readme/</guid>
      <description>2024-americas </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/foreign-affairs/asia-pacific/2024/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/foreign-affairs/asia-pacific/2024/readme/</guid>
      <description>2024-asia-pacific </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/foreign-affairs/europe/2024/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/foreign-affairs/europe/2024/readme/</guid>
      <description>2024-europe </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/foreign-affairs/middle-east/2024/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/foreign-affairs/middle-east/2024/readme/</guid>
      <description>2024-middle-east </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/foreign-affairs/russia/2024/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/foreign-affairs/russia/2024/readme/</guid>
      <description>2024-russia </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/health-and-medicine/2024/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/health-and-medicine/2024/readme/</guid>
      <description>2024-health-and-medicine </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/opinion/2024/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/opinion/2024/readme/</guid>
      <description>2024-opinion </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/parallel-universe-reports/2024/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/parallel-universe-reports/2024/readme/</guid>
      <description>2024-parallel-universe-reports </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2024/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2024/readme/</guid>
      <description>2024-science-and-technology </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/sports/2024/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/sports/2024/readme/</guid>
      <description>2024-sports </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>The Zombie Fridge Journal is a student-run newspaper reporting on general affairs and based in the New York City metropolitan area.
Its personnel choose to run it for fun. It hasn&amp;rsquo;t crashed and burned yet, so that&amp;rsquo;s a good sign.
Editor-in-chief Wu decided to create it after his COVID-19 article was censored. It launched in May 2023.
The ZFJ operates independently of any school authorities.
Any opinions expressed are of their respective writers and not the ZFJ.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
