<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Zombie Fridge Journal</title>
    <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Zombie Fridge Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 21:45:05 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://theZFJ.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>NYC retires the MetroCard</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2026/nyc-metrocard-retirement/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 21:45:05 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2026/nyc-metrocard-retirement/</guid>
      <description>NEW YORK, Jan. 1 (ZFJ) — The MetroCard is retiring in favor of the OMNY tap and ride fare system.&#xA;Per the Metropolitan Transportation Authority (MTA), customers can no longer buy or refill MetroCards as of Thursday, Jan 1. Customers with valid MetroCards can transfer the value to an OMNY Card at a customer service center or use up the value before it expires.&#xA;The OMNY system allows riders to use their contactless credit or debit cards or a physical OMNY Card to pay for subway and bus fares.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge rules government targeted pro-Palestinian foreign students for their speech</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/madc-trump-administration-first-amendment-pro-palestinian-targeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:21:14 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/madc-trump-administration-first-amendment-pro-palestinian-targeting/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON, Dec. 28 (ZFJ) — The federal government has been unconstitutionally targeting pro-Palestinian foreign students for deportation for protected speech, ruled a district judge on Sept. 30, 2025.&#xA;U.S. District Judge William G. Young, a Ronald Reagan nominee, came to the conclusion that Secretaries Kristi Noem and Marco Rubio of the departments of Homeland Security and State “acted in concert to misuse the sweeping powers of their respective offices to target non-citizen pro-Palestinians for deportation primarily on account of their First Amendment protected political speech” after a nine day bench trial in Massachusetts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All Washington Metro lines return to automatic train operation</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/wmata-systemwide-ato-return/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 19:12:11 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/wmata-systemwide-ato-return/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON, Dec. 28 (ZFJ) — All Washington Metrorail lines returned to automatic train operation (ATO) this year for the first time since 2009.&#xA;The Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (WMATA) returned ATO to the Green and Yellow lines on May 23 and Blue, Orange, and Silver lines on June 15 after “rigorous internal training and testing and concurrence from the Washington Metrorail Safety Commission.” The Red line already returned to ATO in December 2024.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub CEO resigns, leadership integrated more into Microsoft CoreAI</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/business/2025/github-ceo-resignation-microsoft-independence-coreai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 04:52:56 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/business/2025/github-ceo-resignation-microsoft-independence-coreai/</guid>
      <description>Dec. 27 (ZFJ) — GitHub CEO Thomas Dohmke resigned on Aug. 11, with the platform’s leadership now more integrated into Microsoft’s CoreAI team.&#xA;In an internal memo sent to employees of the code repository service, Dohmke announced his decision to leave GitHub to become a startup founder again. He said that “GitHub and its leadership team will continue its mission as part of Microsoft’s CoreAI organization, with more details shared soon” and added that he’ll be staying through the end of 2025 to help with transitioning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore County now cooperating with ICE</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/baltimore-county-ice-cooperation-mou/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 04:27:43 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/baltimore-county-ice-cooperation-mou/</guid>
      <description>COLLEGE PARK, Md., Dec. 27 (ZFJ) — Baltimore County has signed a memorandum of understanding (MOU) with U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE) to cooperate on immigration enforcement.&#xA;On Oct. 31, the U.S. Department of Justice (DOJ) announced Baltimore County’s removal from the department’s list of “sanctuary jurisdictions.”&#xA;“Despite restrictions from state leadership, Baltimore County has shown a willingness to cooperate with federal immigration enforcement,” said U.S. Associate Attorney General Stanley Woodward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human remains in College Park prompt homicide investigation</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/college-park-human-remains-lake-artemesia-homicide-investigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 04:10:40 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/college-park-human-remains-lake-artemesia-homicide-investigation/</guid>
      <description>COLLEGE PARK, Md., Dec. 27 (ZFJ) — Human remains found in a park in College Park on Nov. 3 have prompted a homicide investigation.&#xA;The Prince George’s County Police Department was assisting the D.C. Metropolitan Police Department and FBI Cross Border Task Force with a missing persons investigation when it searched Indian Creek Stream Valley Park and found human remains.&#xA;The remains were sent to the Maryland Office of the Chief Medical Examiner, which ruled the case a homicide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metuchen resident arrested by ICE at immigration hearing</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/kalkan-metuchen-resident-arrest-ice-newark/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 03:55:47 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/kalkan-metuchen-resident-arrest-ice-newark/</guid>
      <description>METUCHEN, N.J., Dec. 27 (ZFJ) — Metuchen resident Sener Kalkan was arrested by U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE), said borough Mayor Jonathan Busch on social media.&#xA;Busch said that Kalkan, who is married to Metuchen native Jennifer Poandl, “appeared in Newark for a scheduled immigration hearing as part of his ongoing legal process” in early December.&#xA;Kalkan attended the hearing, passed his scheduled interview, received a future court date, and then went out for lunch with his wife.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State suspends Edison BOE member Anjana Patel for 30 days for ethics violation</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/edison-boe-anjana-patel-state-ethics-suspension-30-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 03:36:04 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/edison-boe-anjana-patel-state-ethics-suspension-30-days/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Dec. 27 (ZFJ) — Anjana Patel, a member of the Edison Board of Education (EBOE), received a 30 day suspension from the state on Dec. 12 for an ethics violation.&#xA;The state School Ethics Commission (SEC) found on Oct. 28 that Patel violated the School Ethics Act by failing to file her Personal/Relative and Financial Disclosure statements on time.&#xA;Patel was elected to the board of education in the 2023 general election as part of the Students First team and was sworn in as a board member starting January 2024.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE reports death of Delaney Hall detainee</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/brutus-ice-delaney-hall-detainee-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 03:05:55 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/brutus-ice-delaney-hall-detainee-death/</guid>
      <description>NEWARK, N.J., Dec. 27 (ZFJ) — Jean Wilson Brutus, 41, died in the custody of U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE) in Newark, N.J, on Dec. 12, from “suspected natural causes.”&#xA;ICE says in a press release that they arrested Brutus on Dec. 11 and held him in the Delaney Hall Detention Facility in Newark, where he experienced a medical emergency. Local EMS was called and took him to University Hospital, also in Newark, where he was pronounced dead the next day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adamn Killa visits UMD</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/arts-and-entertainment/2025/adamn-killa-umd-homecoming-festival/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 13:12:52 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/arts-and-entertainment/2025/adamn-killa-umd-homecoming-festival/</guid>
      <description>COLLEGE PARK, Md., Nov. 12 (ZFJ) — Rapper Adamn Killa visited the University of Maryland, College Park, during homecoming festivities on Oct. 31.&#xA;The Chicago rapper, whose real name is Adam Kelly, has gone viral on social media. His popular content includes shorts where he says “if you a ___ baddie, this is for you” (inserting many adjectives in the blank space) and does a dance where he moves his clasped hands around his head in a circle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Joshi wins landslide reelection for Edison mayor</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/2025-edison-mayor-election/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 11:34:28 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/2025-edison-mayor-election/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Nov. 5 (ZFJ) — Sam Joshi won reelection for Edison mayor by a landslide in the general election on Tuesday, Nov. 4.&#xA;The Democrat garnered 71.51% of the vote, putting him ahead of independent candidate David Tingle by about 12,000 votes.&#xA;“Since first announcing my candidacy for Mayor four years ago, I was determined to make decisions based on putting the public first,” wrote Joshi in a victory post on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democrats win Edison Town Council seats</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/2025-edison-town-council-election/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 23:46:33 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/2025-edison-town-council-election/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Nov. 4 (ZFJ) — The Edison Town Council election saw a Democrat sweep, with Robert J. Kentos, Biral Patel, and Kelli Dima all securing seats on Tuesday, Nov. 4.&#xA;The Democrat candidates outpaced the Republican candidates by a margin of over 10,000 votes.&#xA;While the Democrats had three candidates, the Republican Party only had two nominations, and Elizabeth Conway was on David Tingle’s team, People’s Choice 2025.&#xA;Patel had been a member of the Edison Board of Education from 2021 to 2024, serving as board president in 2024.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Students First team wins Edison Board of Education election</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/2025-edison-boe-election/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 23:25:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/2025-edison-boe-election/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Nov. 4 (ZFJ) — Vishal Patel, Russell J. Azzarello, and Xiaohan “Shannon” Peng won the three available seats on the Edison Board of Education on Tuesday, Nov. 4.&#xA;Column 2, the Students First team, led by a margin of about 2,000-4,000 more votes than Column 3, the Shaping Edison’s Future team.&#xA;Patel and Peng are incumbent members of the board. Patel is the current board vice president. Azzarello dropped out of running for Edison town council as a Republican candidate to join the board race instead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Juvenile arrested for false North Brunswick poll bomb threat</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/2025-election-north-brunswick-juvenile-bomb-threat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 22:28:13 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/2025-election-north-brunswick-juvenile-bomb-threat/</guid>
      <description>NORTH BRUNSWICK, N.J., Nov. 4 (ZFJ) — A juvenile has been arrested for texting a false bomb threat to a North Brunswick poll on Tuesday, Nov. 4.&#xA;At about 8:15 a.m. today, the North Brunswick Police Department began receiving several reports of a bomb threat at Livingston Park Elementary School via text message, according to a statement from the Middlesex County Prosecutor’s Office.&#xA;North Brunswick police officers and Middlesex County Sheriff’s Department explosive detection K-9 officers responded to the polling location and cleared it of any bombs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>29 arrested in immigration raid at Edison warehouse</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/immigration-raid-edison-smart-logistics-and-freight-solutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 21:22:18 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/immigration-raid-edison-smart-logistics-and-freight-solutions/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Nov. 1 (ZFJ) — Federal immigration authorities arrested 29 people in a raid on a warehouse in Edison on Aug. 20.&#xA;The raid occurred at the Smart Supply Chain Logistics and Freight Solutions warehouse at 45 Patrick Avenue.&#xA;The arrest figure comes from the Edison mayor’s office, which distributed a statement to media organizations. The ZFJ was unable to obtain the statement firsthand despite repeated emails, phone calls, and an in-person visit to town hall, and is thus referencing other outlets’ reporting here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>46 arrested in Avenel warehouse immigration raid</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/immigration-raid-avenel-warehouse-savino-del-bene/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 21:19:39 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/immigration-raid-avenel-warehouse-savino-del-bene/</guid>
      <description>AVENEL, N.J., Oct. 31 (ZFJ) — Federal immigration authorities arrested 46 people in a raid on a warehouse in the Avenel section of Woodbridge on Wednesday, Oct. 29.&#xA;The raid occurred at the warehouse of Italian-based logistics company Savino Del Bene located at 34 Engelhard Avenue, according to Cosecha New Jersey.&#xA;“The operation is part of DHS’ ongoing efforts to ensure compliance with customs and immigration regulations, safeguard the integrity of the supply chain, and verify that warehouse operators are adhering to all applicable security requirements,” said a U.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: James Gunn aims for bullseye with Peacemaker S2</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/opinion/2025/peacemaker-s2-review-james-gunn-bullseye/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 21:54:13 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/opinion/2025/peacemaker-s2-review-james-gunn-bullseye/</guid>
      <description>EDITOR&amp;rsquo;S NOTE: This review contains spoilers for Peacemaker season 2.&#xA;After the release of this summer’s Superman (2025), DC fans all over the world rejoiced. The confusing managerial mess that was the DCEU would no longer haunt their hopes and dreams. The new DCU, led by former Marvel director James Gunn, would be a clean slate, a fresh new beginning.&#xA;Despite the clean slate, Gunn couldn’t help but integrate his own projects that were set in the DCEU into the DCU, namely Peacemaker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court allows ICE to stop, detain based on race</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/supreme-court-shadow-docket-ice-stop-detain-race-california/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 18:17:12 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/supreme-court-shadow-docket-ice-stop-detain-race-california/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON, Sept. 28 (ZFJ) — A judge’s order prohibiting immigration agents from stopping and detaining people based on race was overturned by the Supreme Court on Sept. 8.&#xA;U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE) agents have been conducting roving patrols in Los Angeles since this summer to fulfill arrest quotas as part of President Donald Trump’s mass deportation campaign.&#xA;In response to a lawsuit by multiple ICE detainees and advocacy organizations against the federal government, U.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge rules Trump LA military deployment violated federal law</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/federal-district-judge-trump-la-military-deployment-illegal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 23:33:28 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/federal-district-judge-trump-la-military-deployment-illegal/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON, Sept. 22 (ZFJ) — A federal district judge in California ruled on Sept. 2 that President Donald Trump’s use of the California National Guard and U.S. Marines in Los Angeles violated a federal law restricting the use of the military for domestic law enforcement.&#xA;Raising concerns about Trump’s potential use of the military elsewhere in the nation, U.S. District Judge Charles R. Breyer found that Trump’s use of the soldiers violated the Posse Comitatus Act, which prohibits the use of the military for civilian law enforcement without authorization from Congress or the Constitution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Museum of American History opens gunboat Philadelphia restoration exhibit</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/arts-and-entertainment/2025/smithsonian-american-history-opens-gunboat-philadelphia-restoration-exhibit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 00:40:10 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/arts-and-entertainment/2025/smithsonian-american-history-opens-gunboat-philadelphia-restoration-exhibit/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON, Aug. 31 (ZFJ) — The Smithsonian National Museum of American History (NMAH) opened an exhibit of the restoration of the Revolutionary War-era gunboat Philadelphia on Friday, Aug. 22.&#xA;Viewing windows at &amp;ldquo;The Gunboat Philadelphia Preservation Project&amp;rdquo; exhibit allow visitors to observe the vessel&amp;rsquo;s underwater restoration in real time, conducted by a team of underwater archaeologists and maritime conservators from Texas A&amp;amp;M University&amp;rsquo;s Nautical Archaeology Program (under contract with the Smithsonian).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump orders National Guard, federal police to create specialized public order units</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/trump-dc-crime-emergency-national-guard-creation-public-order-units/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 03:30:36 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/trump-dc-crime-emergency-national-guard-creation-public-order-units/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON, Aug. 28 (ZFJ) — President Donald Trump ordered all state National Guard forces as well as certain federal law enforcement agencies to create specialized public order units in an expansion of his declared D.C. crime emergency on Monday, Aug. 25.&#xA;“PUBLIC SAFETY AND ORDER” UNITS&#xA;In section 2(d)(i) of his executive order, Additional Measures to Address the Crime Emergency in the District of Columbia, Trump requires that Secretary of Defense Pete Hegseth to “immediately create and begin training, manning, hiring, and equipping a specialized unit” within the D.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patrolling DC National Guard soldiers now armed with rifles, pistols</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/dc-national-guard-armed-m4-rifle-m17-pistol-secdef-hegseth/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 03:15:57 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/dc-national-guard-armed-m4-rifle-m17-pistol-secdef-hegseth/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON, Aug. 28 (ZFJ) — National Guard soldiers patrolling D.C. as part of President Donald Trump’s federal intervention and declared crime emergency are now armed with rifles and pistols.&#xA;Media reports indicated that Secretary of Defense Pete Hegseth ordered that the guardsmen be armed in a directive announced by the Pentagon on Friday, Aug. 22. Prior to the order, the guardsmen were not armed, and the Pentagon declined to comment further on the topic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three more states to deploy National Guard to DC</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/mississippi-tennessee-louisiana-deploy-national-guard-dc-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 23:35:59 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/mississippi-tennessee-louisiana-deploy-national-guard-dc-trump/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON, Aug. 18 (ZFJ) — Mississippi, Tennessee, and Louisiana have pledged to send National Guard troops to D.C. for policing at the request of President Donald Trump.&#xA;Trump has declared a state of emergency due to crime in the nation’s capital and used it as the basis to federalize the district’s civilian Metropolitan Police Department and deploy guard soldiers and federal agents to the streets. An article by the U.S. Department of Defense (DOD) says there are 810 D.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three states pledge to send National Guard troops to DC</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/west-virginia-south-carolina-ohio-deploy-national-guard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 23:39:51 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/west-virginia-south-carolina-ohio-deploy-national-guard/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON, Aug. 16 (ZFJ) — West Virginia, South Carolina, and Ohio have pledged to send National Guard troops to Washington, D.C., for policing at the request of President Donald Trump.&#xA;Trump has declared a state of emergency due to crime in the nation’s capital and used it as the basis to federalize the district’s civilian Metropolitan Police Department and deploy National Guard soldiers and federal agents to the streets. Currently, 800 D.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC sues over federal takeover of Metropolitan Police</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/dc-metropolitan-police-sues-federal-takeover-doj-bondi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 21:08:14 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/dc-metropolitan-police-sues-federal-takeover-doj-bondi/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON, Aug. 16 (ZFJ) — D.C. officials are suing federal authorities over their federalization of the district&amp;rsquo;s Metropolitan Police Department (MPD).&#xA;Washington officials contend that the federal government is exceeding its authority under Section 740 of the Home Rule Act, which allows the president to take temporary control of the MPD under a state of emergency.&#xA;On Thursday, Aug. 14, MPD Chief Pamela A. Smith issued an executive order that directed police officers to share information about people not in their custody (such as during traffic stops) with immigration authorities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House initiates review of Smithsonian museums for “Americanism”</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/white-house-initiates-review-smithsonian-museums-americanism/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 21:11:26 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/white-house-initiates-review-smithsonian-museums-americanism/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON, Aug. 15 (ZFJ) — The White House has initiated a review of Smithsonian Institution museums to ensure content complies with President Donald Trump’s view of American history.&#xA;In a letter to Smithsonian Secretary Lonnie G. Bunch III released Tuesday, Aug. 12, White House officials invoke the March presidential executive order Restoring Truth and Sanity to American History to perform a “comprehensive internal review” of museum materials.&#xA;“This initiative aims to ensure alignment with the President’s directive to celebrate American exceptionalism, remove divisive or partisan narratives, and restore confidence in our shared cultural institutions,” reads the letter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump federalizes DC police, deploys National Guard, federal agents</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/trump-crime-federal-control-dc-metropolitan-police-national-guard/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 23:23:11 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/trump-crime-federal-control-dc-metropolitan-police-national-guard/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON, Aug. 13 (ZFJ) — President Donald Trump federalized the capital’s Metropolitan Police Department (MPD), deployed 800 D.C. National Guard soldiers, and ordered federal agents to patrol the streets in response to his claims that crime in the city is out of control on Monday, Aug. 11.&#xA;The District of Columbia is primarily under federal control and has limited local governance under the Home Rule Act. Section 740 of this law allows for the president to federalize the MPD under a state of emergency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grand jury clears Fort Lee cop in fatal shooting of woman in mental health crisis</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/grand-jury-clears-fort-lee-police-victoria-lee-mental-health-crisis-fatal-shooting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 05:50:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/grand-jury-clears-fort-lee-police-victoria-lee-mental-health-crisis-fatal-shooting/</guid>
      <description>TRENTON, N.J., Aug. 12 (ZFJ) — A state grand jury voted not to criminally charge Fort Lee Police Officer Tony Pickens, Jr., with the fatal shooting of Victoria G. Lee, 25, of Fort Lee, during a mental health crisis on July 28, 2024.&#xA;Per state law, the N.J. Attorney General’s Office (OAG) is required to investigate any deaths that occur during law enforcement encounters, so this case was investigated by OAG’s Office of Public Integrity and Accountability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kushal Aluru, Rutgers student and JPS alumnus, dies at 20</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/obituary-kushal-aluru-jps-rutgers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 19:40:45 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/obituary-kushal-aluru-jps-rutgers/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., July 24 (ZFJ) — Kushal Aluru, 20, a Rutgers student and J.P. Stevens High School alumnus, died on Tuesday, July 22, 2025.&#xA;Aluru was majoring in cell biology and neuroscience and minoring in chemistry at Rutgers University, New Brunswick. He had a stated interest in neurobiology and glial functions, conducting research in the lab of Professor Peng Jiang since 2023, and intended on pursuing a combined medical and doctorate degree program to become a physician and scientist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court ends nationwide injunctions in ruling on birthright citizenship cases</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/supreme-court-ends-nationwide-injunction-birthright-citizenship/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 00:51:38 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/supreme-court-ends-nationwide-injunction-birthright-citizenship/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON, July 18 (ZFJ) — Nationwide injunctions exceed the authority of lower court judges, ruled the Supreme Court in three cases concerning birthright citizenship on June 27, 2025.&#xA;The Court struck down nationwide injunctions by a 6-3 vote in the cases Trump v. CASA, Inc. (24A884), Trump v. Washington (24A885), and Trump v. New Jersey (24A886).&#xA;The Court, which heard the cases consolidated on the emergency docket, only considered the question of nationwide injunctions and issued no ruling on the birthright citizenship order central to the lawsuits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>21 arrested in immigration raid at Edison warehouse</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/edison-immigration-raid-cbp-alba-spirits-warehouse-heller/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 02:54:34 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/edison-immigration-raid-cbp-alba-spirits-warehouse-heller/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., July 10 (ZFJ) — Federal immigration authorities arrested 21 people in a raid on an Edison warehouse on Tuesday, July 8.&#xA;The raid occurred at the Alba Wine and Spirits Warehouse, located at 360 Saw Mill Pond Road in the Heller Industrial Parks section of the town.&#xA;Immigrant advocates were notified of the raid via calls to their rapid response lines. They showed up to the warehouse, warned incoming workers of the authorities’ presence and to stay away, and streamed the raid live on Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three dead after destructive storm in Central Jersey</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/july-3-central-jersey-destructive-storm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 23:57:45 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/july-3-central-jersey-destructive-storm/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., July 4 (ZFJ) — A destructive storm tore through Central Jersey on Thursday, July 3, leaving trees felled, wires downed, and three dead.&#xA;The thunderstorm suddenly rolled in at around 6:00 p.m. and lasted until 6:30 p.m. The National Weather Service (NWS) issued a severe thunderstorm warning and advised that winds could reach up to a “DESTRUCTIVE” 80 miles per hour.&#xA;Severe Thunderstorm Warning continues for South Plainfield NJ, Carteret NJ and North Plainfield NJ until 6:30 PM EDT.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ Transit rail service sees rampant cancellations during heat wave</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/nj-transit-nec-heat-wave-june-23-35-service-impact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 21:07:51 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/nj-transit-nec-heat-wave-june-23-35-service-impact/</guid>
      <description>TRENTON, N.J., June 29 (ZFJ) — NJ Transit rail service saw many cancellations and delays during the heat wave from Monday, June 23, to Wednesday, June 25.&#xA;The East Coast endured an early heat wave that reached 100 degrees at its worst. The National Weather Service reported a new record of 98 F (37 C) in Trenton and a tied record of 103 F (39 C) in Newark on the hottest day of the heat wave—Tuesday, June 24.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: An Initially Blind Review of Live Action How to Train Your Dragon</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/opinion/2025/how-to-train-your-dragon-live-action-movie-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 05:27:43 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/opinion/2025/how-to-train-your-dragon-live-action-movie-review/</guid>
      <description>I have never watched How to Train Your Dragon—an act of sacrilege until advertisements of its live action remake started bombarding my feed, and the shots I were seeing looked good. Interesting, at least.&#xA;To the theatre I went, with no expectations on plot or animation—just the hope to find a good remake.&#xA;I did, in fact, find a good movie. A great movie, even.&#xA;PART ONE: It’s a Good Movie</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington Metro begins longer weekend hours, Red and Silver Line changes</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/wmata-metro-service-improvements-june-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 23:29:50 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/wmata-metro-service-improvements-june-22/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON, June 22 (ZFJ) — Washington Metro’s longer weekend hours, Red and Silver Line changes, and new system map took effect on Sunday, June 22.&#xA;Metrorail will open an hour earlier at 6:00 a.m. on Saturdays and Sundays and close an hour later at 2:00 a.m. on Fridays and Saturdays.&#xA;Starting Monday, June 23, Red Line trains will run more frequently, arriving at least every four, instead of five, minutes “during the busiest portions of weekday rush hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Joshi’s ticket sweeps Edison Democratic primary</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/edison-primary-june-2025-sam-joshi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 23:24:31 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/edison-primary-june-2025-sam-joshi/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., June 12 (ZFJ) — Sam Joshi and his team of town council candidates swept the Democratic primary election on Tuesday, June 10.&#xA;Nearing the end of his first term, incumbent Edison Mayor Sam Joshi secured 6,000-7,000 more votes than his challengers, Lav Patel and incumbent Councilman Richard Brescher.&#xA;“Thank you 🙏 everything we do is for the residents of Edison,” Joshi posted on social media after polls closed. “On to the general election in November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edison Board of Education abolishes Policy 5756</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/2025-05-20-edison-boe-abolish-policy-5756-second-reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 14:58:57 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/2025-05-20-edison-boe-abolish-policy-5756-second-reading/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., May 26 (ZFJ) — The Edison Board of Education abolished Policy 5756, the transgender students policy, during a marathon action meeting on Tuesday, May 20.&#xA;Policy 5756 was issued by the N.J. Department of Education as guidance to local school districts. It directs schools to accept a student’s asserted gender identity and, controversially, eliminates an “affirmative duty” (in other words, an obligation) for staff members to notify parents of the student’s new gender identity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four arrested for riot in pro-Palestinian protest at Rutgers Hillel</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/rutgers-hillel-pro-palestinian-protest-april-29-arrests/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 21:32:26 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/rutgers-hillel-pro-palestinian-protest-april-29-arrests/</guid>
      <description>NEW BRUNSWICK, N.J., May 23 (ZFJ) — Three Rutgers students and one Cranford man unaffiliated with the university were charged with rioting and other offenses during a pro-Palestinian demonstration at Rutgers Hillel on April 29, 2025.&#xA;On that day, Rutgers Hillel, located on the College Avenue campus, held a roundtable with U.S. Rep. Josh Gottheimer to, according to a press release from the congressman, “speak with students about the alarming rise in antisemitism on college campuses across the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US deports Maryland man in “administrative error” to El Salvador</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/us-mistakenly-deports-maryland-man-abrego-garcia-el-salvador/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 05:22:09 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/us-mistakenly-deports-maryland-man-abrego-garcia-el-salvador/</guid>
      <description>GREENBELT, Md., April 19 (ZFJ) — U.S. immigration authorities have erroneously deported Kilmar Armando Abrego Garcia of Maryland, who was protected from removal by an immigration judge, to an El Salvador mega-prison.&#xA;Abrego Garcia’s case was brought before U.S. District Judge Paula Xinis at the Maryland federal court’s division in Greenbelt.&#xA;Xinis wrote in her memorandum opinion that Abrego Garcia came from Los Nogales, El Salvador, and illegally entered the U.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>“Hands Off” protesters nationwide express frustration with Trump</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/hands-off-protests-2025-04-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 18:48:06 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/hands-off-protests-2025-04-05/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON, April 7 (ZFJ) — Americans took to their public spaces in over 1,300 demonstrations nationwide to protest the Trump administration on Saturday, April 5.&#xA;Various scenes from the Hands Off demonstration at the Sylvan Theater in Washington. ZFJ/Alvin Wu The organization Hands Off!, named to tell Trump and Musk “hands off” the government and partnered with numerous advocacy groups and labor unions, called for a “National Day of Action” on Saturday to demand “an end to the authoritarian overreach by Trump and Musk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keasbey man charged with shooting murder of Edison man</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/edison-shooting-murder-kirilenko/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 01:25:13 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/edison-shooting-murder-kirilenko/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Feb. 23 (ZFJ) — Igor Kirilenko, 61, of Keasbey, N.J., has been charged with the murder of Gregory Ginzburg, 72, of Edison on Sunday, Feb. 16.&#xA;On Feb. 16, at 6:39 p.m., Edison police responded to Clive Hills Road following a 911 call from Ginzburg saying that Kirilenko was in his house with a firearm. Dispatch heard a loud noise, believed to be a gunshot, during the call.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OPINION: Boba shops are optimal for first dates</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/opinion/2025/boba-shops-optimal-first-dates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 02:22:22 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/opinion/2025/boba-shops-optimal-first-dates/</guid>
      <description>Civil discourse is critical for every democracy, and with Valentine’s Day tomorrow (today? I’m writing this at two hours past midnight), it’s about time we discussed an issue that really matters to society: the optimal location for a first date.&#xA;I have the answer. After extensive research and analysis consisting of musing in the cool wind while gazing at the full moon as well as the documented results of two practical tests by me and my associates, I have concluded that bubble tea shops are perfect for first dates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOGE shuts down entire government</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/parallel-universe-reports/2025/doge-shuts-down-entire-government/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 22:23:15 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/parallel-universe-reports/2025/doge-shuts-down-entire-government/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON, Feb. 9 (ZFJ) — The Department of Government Efficiency (DOGE), under the fearless leadership of billionaire Elon Musk, has ordered the shutdown of the entire federal government of the U.S. on the grounds that it is the grossest inefficiency of all time.&#xA;After “extensive research and analysis” by a highly qualified team of college undergrads handpicked from Musk’s companies SpaceX and X, DOGE reached the conclusion that the government was nothing more than a “shockingly massive inefficiency,” according to an X post by the budget-slashing commission.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok briefly banned in the US</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/tiktok-us-ban-divestiture-resurrection/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 22:21:17 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/tiktok-us-ban-divestiture-resurrection/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON, Jan. 27 (ZFJ) — TikTok was briefly banned in the United States from late night Saturday, Jan. 18, to Sunday, Jan. 19, as a result of a law requiring TikTok to divest itself of its American operations.&#xA;TikTok is a social media platform for short videos with over 170 million American users and over one billion worldwide users. In 2023, American TikTok users uploaded over 5.5 billion videos, which were viewed over 13 trillion times globally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two new giant pandas debut at the Smithsonian’s National Zoo</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/national-zoo-two-giant-pandas-bao-li-qing-bao/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 02:06:45 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/national-zoo-two-giant-pandas-bao-li-qing-bao/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON, Jan. 25 (ZFJ) — Two new giant pandas made their public debut at the Smithsonian’s National Zoo and Conservation Biology Institute (NZCBI) on Friday, Jan. 24.&#xA;NZCBI Director Brandie Smith unveiled pandas Bao Li and Qing Bao in a ceremonial opening of the Asia Trail exhibit on Friday.&#xA;“For over 50 years, giant pandas have been an integral part of the fabric and culture of Washington, D.C., thanks in large part to the support of the communities that live and work in the District,” Smith said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump moves to withdraw US from World Health Organization</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/trump-day-1-executive-orders-who-withdrawal/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 02:00:13 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/trump-day-1-executive-orders-who-withdrawal/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON, Jan. 23 (ZFJ) — President Donald Trump moved to withdraw the United States from membership in the World Health Organization (WHO) in a Day 1 executive order.&#xA;In the order, Trump said the withdrawal was due to the WHO’s mishandling of the COVID-19 pandemic in 2020 and China’s influence over the United Nations global public health agency.&#xA;“The United States noticed its withdrawal from the World Health Organization (WHO) in 2020 due to the organization’s mishandling of the COVID-19 pandemic that arose out of Wuhan, China, and other global health crises, its failure to adopt urgently needed reforms, and its inability to demonstrate independence from the inappropriate political influence of WHO member states,” reads the order.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump executive order implements Department of Government Efficiency</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/trump-day-1-executive-orders-implement-doge/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 01:49:43 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/trump-day-1-executive-orders-implement-doge/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON, Jan. 23 (ZFJ) — President Donald Trump implemented the Department of Government Efficiency (DOGE) by executive order on the first day of his presidency.&#xA;The order renames the U.S. Digital Service, a technology unit within the Executive Office of the President, to the U.S. DOGE Service (USDS).&#xA;It also creates the U.S. DOGE Service Temporary Organization within the USDS, “dedicated to advancing the President’s 18-month DOGE agenda” and terminating on July 4, 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden commutes sentences of almost all federal death row inmates</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/biden-federal-death-row-commutations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 19:00:22 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/biden-federal-death-row-commutations/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON, Jan. 21 (ZFJ) — President Joe Biden commuted the sentences of 37 of 40 federal inmates from execution to life in prison without the possibility of parole on Dec. 23, 2024.&#xA;The Justice Department, on July 1, 2021, imposed a temporary moratorium on federal executions pending a review of federal policies.&#xA;“These commutations are consistent with the moratorium my Administration has imposed on federal executions, in cases other than terrorism and hate-motivated mass murder,” said Biden in a statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Tech invests big in nuclear</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/business/2025/big-tech-nuclear-investments/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 23:24:29 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/business/2025/big-tech-nuclear-investments/</guid>
      <description>Jan. 20 (ZFJ) — Microsoft, Google, and Amazon are investing in nuclear energy as the race to develop artificial intelligence technologies heats up.&#xA;AI technologies, which are currently rapidly gaining traction, demand significant computational power to train and operate. Data centers house the hardware for them and are consuming increasingly more energy.&#xA;According to a December 2024 report from Lawrence Berkeley National Laboratory, a U.S. Department of Energy research facility, total American data center electricity usage increased from 58 TWh in 2014 to 176 TWh in 2023.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo Switch 2 to release 2025</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/arts-and-entertainment/2025/nintendo-switch-2-to-release-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 17:50:24 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/arts-and-entertainment/2025/nintendo-switch-2-to-release-2025/</guid>
      <description>Jan. 17 (ZFJ) — The Nintendo Switch 2 will be released in 2025, according to an announcement from the video game company on Thursday, Jan. 16.&#xA;Nintendo offered a look at the highly-anticipated successor to the Nintendo Switch in a trailer that rocketed to over 14 million views within 17 hours and became the top trending video on YouTube.&#xA;Video: Trailer released on Thursday, Jan. 16, for the Nintendo Switch 2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shi voted Edison Board of Education president at reorganization meeting</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/edison-boe-reorganization-shi-president-vishal-vp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 00:13:56 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/edison-boe-reorganization-shi-president-vishal-vp/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Jan. 10 (ZFJ) — Jerry Shi was voted president of the Edison Board of Education and Vishal Patel was voted vice president at the Jan. 2 reorganization meeting as the winners of November’s elections were sworn in.&#xA;Clips from the Edison Board of Education Jan. 2 reorganization meeting. Includes oaths of office, board president and vice president votes, board member comment, and public comment. EDISON BOARD OF EDUCATION/Livestream The meeting began with Ronak Patel, Ralph Errico, and Shi taking the oath of office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edison council abruptly adjourns meeting during public comment</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/edison-town-council-dec-23-adjourn-public-comment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 17:30:23 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2025/edison-town-council-dec-23-adjourn-public-comment/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Jan. 10 (ZFJ) — The Edison Town Council adjourned their Dec. 23 combined meeting in the middle of public comment following a statement by Leroy Truth accusing Mayor Sam Joshi of rape and calling for an investigation.&#xA;Truth is a YouTuber who runs the channel Leroy Truth Investigations. His stated purpose is “to expose government corruption and hold corrupt government officials accountable to the full extent of the law,” according to the channel’s about section.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edison Town Council ejects man for holding American flag</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-town-council-ejects-man-public-comment-american-flag/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 20:43:45 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-town-council-ejects-man-public-comment-american-flag/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Dec. 31 (ZFJ) — The Edison Town Council ejected a man from the council chambers for holding an American flag during public comment at the Nov. 25 combined meeting. The council also passed two ordinances to limit public comment time and grant the council president broad authority to restrict “disorderly” behavior at the dais.&#xA;Two ordinances related to the council’s public comment were on the agenda that night. The first, O.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Water restored to most South Edison homes after main break</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-water-main-break-restoration-progress/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2024 19:12:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-water-main-break-restoration-progress/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Dec. 28 (ZFJ) — Water has been restored to most residences affected by the water main break on Thursday, Dec. 26, according to Mayor Sam Joshi.&#xA;This incident has been one of Edison’s largest water main breaks, impacting about 20,000 residents.&#xA;In a statement posted to social media yesterday afternoon, Joshi said that 99% of impacted water supplies have been restored. The boil advisory will remain in effect until lab results come back safe, which he says can take up to 48 hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ penalizes M&amp;U International for Raritan River chemical spill</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/nj-dep-penalizes-mu-international-raritan-river-chemical-spill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2024 18:07:17 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/nj-dep-penalizes-mu-international-raritan-river-chemical-spill/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Dec. 28 (ZFJ) — New Jersey authorities issued a notice of violation to M&amp;amp;U International on Monday, Dec. 23, for an unpermitted discharge in connection with a chemical spill that entered the Raritan River.&#xA;According to M&amp;amp;U International’s website, the company is a supplier of “synthetic and natural aromatic chemicals, food additives and essential oils.” Their facility in Branchburg, N.J., repackages these chemicals and is located within the watershed and upstream of New Jersey American Water (NJAW)’s surface water intake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UMD hearing and speech sciences lecturer Dr. Dominique Mwepu dies at 53</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/obituary-dr-dominique-mwepu-umd-linguistics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2024 03:48:51 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/obituary-dr-dominique-mwepu-umd-linguistics/</guid>
      <description>COLLEGE PARK, Md., Dec. 28 (ZFJ) — Dr. Dominique Mwepu, 53, of Gaithersburg, Md., a lecturer for the Department of Hearing and Speech Sciences at the University of Maryland, College Park, died on Sept. 30, 2024.&#xA;The Montgomery County Police Department reported that he had been fatally struck by a car.&#xA;“He was a beloved husband, father, friend, known for his incredible sense of humor, always quick with a joke and able to bring laughter to even the most difficult moments,” reads his obituary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Edison water main breaks</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-water-main-break-2024-12-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 20:44:04 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-water-main-break-2024-12-26/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Dec. 26 (ZFJ) — A 20-inch water main broke near M Lane and Woodbridge Avenue at about midnight today, Thursday, Dec. 26.&#xA;Residents served by Edison Water Utility along Woodbridge Avenue, Route 27, Route 1, and areas up to Talmadge are experiencing little to no water pressure.&#xA;A boil water advisory has been in effect since 3:10 p.m.&#xA;Emergency repair crews have been working on isolating the break, according to Mayor Sam Joshi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State links Raritan River water taste, odor issues to chemical leak, says no public health threat</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/raritan-system-taste-odor-issues-branchburg-fragrance-leak/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 03:21:05 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/raritan-system-taste-odor-issues-branchburg-fragrance-leak/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Dec. 26 (ZFJ) — The state has linked a change in the taste and odor of water supplied from the Raritan River to a leak from a facility that packages fragrances and flavoring. Authorities say that there is no public health threat.&#xA;On Monday, Dec. 23, New Jersey American Water (NJAW) announced that initial investigation results from the N.J. Department of Environmental Protection (DEP) found that the water issues were caused by a Dec.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UMD announces annual fall break from 2025</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/umd-fall-break-fall-2025-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 02:37:07 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/umd-fall-break-fall-2025-start/</guid>
      <description>COLLEGE PARK, Md., Dec. 25 (ZFJ) — Students at the University of Maryland, College Park, will have an annual two-day fall break starting in the fall 2025 semester, announced President Darryll J. Pines in a campus wide email on Dec. 2.&#xA;The break, the result of a “years-long effort,” will take place on the second Monday of each October—Indigenous People’s Day/Columbus Day—and Tuesday.&#xA;Staff and faculty will observe Indigenous People’s Day/Columbus Day on the Monday of fall break.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police bust drug trafficking ring run by Rutgers students</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/ru-pharm-middlesex-county-drug-trafficking-ring-bust/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 23:15:04 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/ru-pharm-middlesex-county-drug-trafficking-ring-bust/</guid>
      <description>NEW BRUNSWICK, N.J., Dec. 19 (ZFJ) — Seven people have been arrested in connection with a drug trafficking ring involving Rutgers University students, announced the Middlesex County Prosecutor’s Office on Dec. 5.&#xA;Operation RU Pharm was an undercover narcotics operation led by the Middlesex County Prosecutor’s Office Narcotics Task Force and assisted by the Rutgers University Police Department, New Brunswick Police Department, and Somerset County Prosecutor’s Office.&#xA;The operation, lasting several months, uncovered “a closed and private social media network” that Rutgers students used to buy and sell narcotics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korean president declares martial law, overruled by parliament</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/foreign-affairs/asia-pacific/2024/south-korea-president-yoon-martial-law-national-assembly/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 21:57:13 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/foreign-affairs/asia-pacific/2024/south-korea-president-yoon-martial-law-national-assembly/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON, Dec. 5 (ZFJ) — South Korean President Yoon Suk Yeol declared martial law on the night of Tuesday, Dec. 3, only for it to be overruled by the National Assembly several hours later.&#xA;In an unannounced press conference at 10:23 p.m. on Tuesday, Yoon accused the opposition Democratic Party of “an obvious anti-state act that plots insurrection” for attempting to impeach multiple government officials and cutting public safety budgets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cold front to bring rain and snow to Northeast</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/snow-rain-cold-northeast-early-december/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 00:48:59 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/snow-rain-cold-northeast-early-december/</guid>
      <description>COLLEGE PARK, Md., Dec. 4 (ZFJ) — Bundle up, folks. A cold front is en route to the Northeast and is expected to bring rain and snow, strong winds, and freezing temperatures on Wednesday and Thursday.&#xA;“Beginning tomorrow, the passage of the Arctic cold front will lead to an outbreak of snow squalls containing intense bursts of snow and gusty winds upwards of 50 mph in the Upper Midwest and Great Lakes, which spread southeastward into the Central Appalachians and Northeast by Thursday,” according to the short range forecast issued by the National Weather Service’s Weather Prediction Center on Tuesday, Dec.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edison police arrest four for half-million armed FedEx perfume robbery</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-police-fedex-armed-robbery-four-arrested-half-million-perfume-cologne/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 23:06:24 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-police-fedex-armed-robbery-four-arrested-half-million-perfume-cologne/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Nov. 27 (ZFJ) — Four individuals have been arrested for a high-profile gunpoint robbery of over $500,000 worth of perfume and cologne from a FedEx truck, announced Edison police on Sept. 26.&#xA;The incident occurred on Sept. 5 when, according to police, the individuals threatened the FedEx truck driver with a firearm and forced him to drive to a nearby parking lot. There, the driver was bound while the robbers unloaded numerous cases of the fragrances before fleeing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UMD power outage affects heart of campus</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/umd-power-outage-2024-11-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 11:44:21 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/umd-power-outage-2024-11-25/</guid>
      <description>COLLEGE PARK, Md., Nov. 25 (ZFJ) — A power outage is affecting University of Maryland, College Park, buildings around McKeldin Mall.&#xA;A University of Maryland Police Department advisory sent out at 11:27 a.m. reports that Facilities Management is responding to a multiple building power outage.&#xA;Classes in the following buildings were initially cancelled until at least 2:00 p.m. A later campuswide email sent at 2:37 p.m. announced that classes would not meet in the affected buildings for the rest of the day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last British coal power plant shuts down</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/foreign-affairs/europe/2024/last-british-coal-plant-shuts-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 02:54:23 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/foreign-affairs/europe/2024/last-british-coal-plant-shuts-down/</guid>
      <description>Nov. 24 (ZFJ) — The United Kingdom’s last coal power plant shut down on Sept. 30, ending over 140 years of coal energy in the nation and making it the first major economy to completely phase out coal power.&#xA;The Ratcliffe-on-Soar Power Station, owned by Uniper, is located near Nottingham. It began generating power in 1967 and officially ended generation at midnight on Sept. 30.&#xA;Coal was responsible for 40% of the U.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Edison middle school teacher sentenced to 8 years for child pornography, stalking</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-middle-school-teacher-julius-coaccioli-sentencing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 01:06:02 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-middle-school-teacher-julius-coaccioli-sentencing/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Nov. 24 (ZFJ) — Julius Coaccioli, formerly a teacher at Woodrow Wilson Middle School in Edison’s school district, was sentenced to eight years in prison on Aug. 26.&#xA;Coaccioli reached a plea agreement with prosecutors and pleaded guilty to possession of child sexual abuse material in the second degree and stalking in the fourth degree.&#xA;Judge Thomas Abode of the Middlesex County Superior Court sentenced him to concurrent terms of eight years in jail for the possession charge and 18 months for the stalking charge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Jersey American Water issues water conservation notice</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/nj-american-water-conservation-notice-drought/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 20:34:24 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/nj-american-water-conservation-notice-drought/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Nov. 23 (ZFJ) — New Jersey American Water issued a statewide conservation notice and asked residents to limit all nonessential water usage on Nov. 13.&#xA;This action came immediately after the N.J. Department of Environmental Protection (DEP) elevated the statewide drought status to a drought warning on Nov. 13, allowing the state government to closely manage water supplies. A combination of high temperatures and low precipitation have contributed to the present dry conditions affecting the whole Northeast and over half of the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ declares statewide drought warning as wildfires rage, water supplies dwindle</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/nj-elevates-status-drought-warning-wildfire-response/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 17:44:10 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/nj-elevates-status-drought-warning-wildfire-response/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Nov. 15 (ZFJ) — The New Jersey government elevated the drought watch status to a drought warning on Wednesday, Nov. 13, as wildfires rage and water supplies dwindle.&#xA;Over half of the United States is currently facing drought conditions. A record-breaking dry spell is impacting the whole Northeast, with all of N.J. and Delaware, eastern Pennsylvania, New York City, and southern New York under at least moderate drought conditions, according to the U.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Andy Kim elected US senator for New Jersey</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/election-2024-andy-kim-us-senator-nj/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 00:48:24 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/election-2024-andy-kim-us-senator-nj/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Nov. 9 (ZFJ) — Congressman Andy Kim, a Democrat, was elected U.S. senator for New Jersey, making him the first Korean-American senator.&#xA;Kim led Curtis Bashaw, the Republican candidate, by more than 300,000 votes.&#xA;Kim thanked his team and supporters in a victory speech at his campaign headquarters in the DoubleTree Hotel in Cherry Hill on election night. He observed that his family had lived in this hotel for several weeks when they first moved to N.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patel, Errico, Shi decisively win Edison Board of Education election</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/election-2024-column-1-edison-board-of-education/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 00:44:34 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/election-2024-column-1-edison-board-of-education/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Nov. 8 (ZFJ) — Column 1—Ronak Patel, Ralph Errico, and Jingwei “Jerry” Shi—won the three available seats on the Edison Board of Education by a landslide.&#xA;Column 1, the Students First team, outpaced Column 3, the Champions for Students team, by about 6,000-7,000 votes.&#xA;Shi reprises his role after coming in fourth place for three seats in last year’s board election. He previously served on the board from 2014 with a term as president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump defeats Kamala Harris to become 47th U.S. president</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/election-2024-donald-trump-47th-us-president-kamala-harris-defeat/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 17:56:32 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/election-2024-donald-trump-47th-us-president-kamala-harris-defeat/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON, Nov. 6 (ZFJ) — Former President Donald Trump has defeated Vice President Kamala Harris to become the 47th U.S. president.&#xA;The Associated Press called the race for Trump at 5:34 a.m. on Wednesday, Nov. 6, after he won Wisconsin’s 10 electoral votes, putting him at 277 electoral votes to Harris’ 224. He is also leading the popular vote by around 4.8 million votes.&#xA;The electoral vote count at 5:55 p.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In reversal, Edison Board of Education votes against abolishing transgender students policy</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-board-of-education-votes-against-abolishment-policy-5756-oct-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 23:52:51 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-board-of-education-votes-against-abolishment-policy-5756-oct-29/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Nov. 3 (ZFJ) — The Edison Board of Education voted 6-3 against abolishing Policy 5756, which concerns transgender students, in a second reading during a marathon action meeting lasting five hours on Tuesday, Oct. 29, in which many members of the public spoke in support of the policy.&#xA;The board previously voted 5-3 in favor of abolishment after Vishal Patel made a motion on the floor to do so.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edison Board of Education votes to abolish transgender students policy</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-board-of-education-policy-5756-transgender-abolish-motion-vote/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 14:41:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-board-of-education-policy-5756-transgender-abolish-motion-vote/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Oct. 19 (ZFJ) — The Edison Board of Education voted 5-3 to abolish Policy 5756, which concerns transgender students, at their action meeting on Monday, Sept. 30. Since they didn’t properly follow the procedure to abolish a policy, it is still in effect.&#xA;The abolishment was not on the publicly posted agenda for the night and arose from a motion made from the floor.&#xA;This move follows the abolishment of Policy 5756 by many other school districts in N.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024 New Jersey voter registration and mail-in ballot information guide</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/2024-nj-voter-registration-mail-in-ballot-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 18:20:49 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/2024-nj-voter-registration-mail-in-ballot-guide/</guid>
      <description>Oct. 14 (ZFJ) — The deadline to register to vote for the general election in New Jersey is Tuesday, Oct. 15 (21 days before election day on Tuesday, Nov. 5).&#xA;As of press time, that’s tomorrow, so don’t delay any longer if you haven’t registered yet!&#xA;Anyone who is a U.S. citizen, at least 17 years old, a resident of their county for 30 days before the election, and not convicted of a crime is eligible to register to vote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UMD pro-Palestinian protest proceeds peacefully on October 7</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/umd-sjp-oct-7-pro-palestinian-demonstration-vigil-mckeldin-mall/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 12:47:34 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/umd-sjp-oct-7-pro-palestinian-demonstration-vigil-mckeldin-mall/</guid>
      <description>COLLEGE PARK, Md., Oct. 13 (ZFJ) — A vigil held by UMD Students for Justice in Palestine (SJP) on McKeldin Mall on Monday, Oct. 7, took place without incident.&#xA;On Sept. 1, the University of Maryland, College Park, attempted to limit all demonstrations on campus on Oct. 7 after thousands of people wrote objecting to SJP’s permit to protest on that day. The significance of Oct. 7, 2023, is that it was the day when Hamas militants stormed into nearby Israeli towns from the blockaded Gaza Strip to kill and take hostage hundreds of civilians.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge orders UMD to allow October 7 demonstrations</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/federal-injunction-umd-oct-7-sjp-vigil-proceeding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 01:46:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/federal-injunction-umd-oct-7-sjp-vigil-proceeding/</guid>
      <description>COLLEGE PARK, Md., Oct. 5 (ZFJ) — A federal judge ordered the University of Maryland, College Park, to allow UMD Students for Justice in Palestine (SJP) to proceed with their demonstration on Monday, Oct. 7.&#xA;On Sept. 1, after significant outcry over UMD granting a permit to SJP to use McKeldin Mall for an “interfaith vigil,” the university announced that demonstrations would be prohibited on campus on Oct. 7, and that a “university-sponsored Day of Dialogue” would be held instead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pedestrian fatally struck by car in Gaithersburg</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/gaithersburg-md-fatal-pedestrian-collision-dominique-mwepu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 17:32:33 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/gaithersburg-md-fatal-pedestrian-collision-dominique-mwepu/</guid>
      <description>COLLEGE PARK, Md., Oct. 5 (ZFJ) — Dr. Dominique Mwepu, 53, was fatally struck by a car on Monday, Sept. 30, according to the Montgomery County Police Department.&#xA;At about 7:55 p.m., county police officers from the 5th district and fire rescue personnel responded to reports of a collision involving a blue Honda Prelude and a pedestrian at the intersection of Frederick Road and High Point Drive.&#xA;Mwepu sustained life-threatening injuries and was pronounced dead on the scene.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JP Stevens football makes history, upsets Bound Brook in season opener</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/sports/2024/jps-football-win-losing-streak-broken-bound-brook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 00:05:02 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/sports/2024/jps-football-win-losing-streak-broken-bound-brook/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Sept. 21 (ZFJ) — Call it a miracle, or maybe even divine intervention.&#xA;On Friday, Sept. 6, the John P. Stevens High School (Edison, NJ) varsity football team defeated cross-county rival Bound Brook by a score of 22-21, putting an end to an infamous losing streak that had extended back to November of the 2018-2019 season.&#xA;“I’m feeling great, man,” said JPS senior quarterback Marquise Webb to Central Jersey Sports Radio after the game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UMD limits demonstrations on Oct. 7 after controversy over planned pro-Palestinian protest</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/university-of-maryland-oct-7-mckeldin-mall-demonstrations-limited-sjp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 23:42:14 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/university-of-maryland-oct-7-mckeldin-mall-demonstrations-limited-sjp/</guid>
      <description>COLLEGE PARK, Md., Sept. 6 (ZFJ) — The University of Maryland, College Park, will not allow any student group protests on Oct. 7, 2024, following controversy over a pro-Palestinian protest planned for that date.&#xA;The University System of Maryland said in a press release on Sunday, Sept. 1, that special campus events—those requiring approval or permitting—will be suspended only on Oct. 7 in favor of a “university-sponsored Day of Dialogue” to promote reflection instead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maryland cruises past UConn in season-opening football blowout</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/sports/2024/maryland-defeats-connecticut-opening-football/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 14:09:41 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/sports/2024/maryland-defeats-connecticut-opening-football/</guid>
      <description>COLLEGE PARK, Md., Sept. 1 (ZFJ) — The Maryland Terrapins cruised to a dominant 50-7 victory over the UConn Huskies at SECU Stadium on Saturday, Aug. 31, coming together in a full offensive and defensive effort to begin the 2024 campaign on a high note.&#xA;“Great team win, and great start to the 2024 season,” began Head Coach Michael Locksley during the team’s postgame press conference. “We were able to do it today with all three phases contributing to the win.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edison Board of Education retires #24 for Edison High athletes in honor of Coach Jim Muldowney</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/sports/2024/edison-boe-retires-ehs-athletics-jersey-number-24-muldowney/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 20:44:14 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/sports/2024/edison-boe-retires-ehs-athletics-jersey-number-24-muldowney/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Aug. 29 (ZFJ) — The Edison Board of Education retired the use of jersey number 24 for all Edison High School athletic teams in honor of late baseball coach and athletic director James “Diamond Jim” Muldowney at the Aug. 20 combined caucus and public meeting.&#xA;Muldowney graduated from Edison High in 1973 and became a teacher from 1981-2000. He then served as the school’s athletic director from 2000-2008 and the district’s supervisor of physical education and health from 2008-2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Late August heat wave hits</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2024/2024-08-28-heat-wave/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 11:37:37 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2024/2024-08-28-heat-wave/</guid>
      <description>COLLEGE PARK, Md., Aug. 28 (ZFJ) — A heat wave has been descending on America on Wednesday, Aug. 28, placing over 77 million people under excessive heat warnings and heat advisories.&#xA;High temperatures are forecast to be 10-15 degrees above average for much of the Central to Southern Plains, east into the Mississippi Valley, Ohio Valley, Southeast, and Mid-Atlantic, wrote the National Weather Service’s Weather Prediction Center in a short range public discussion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ OAG revises use-of-force policy following controversial shooting</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/nj-oag-use-of-force-barricaded-suspect-revisions-mental-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 15:08:14 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/nj-oag-use-of-force-barricaded-suspect-revisions-mental-health/</guid>
      <description>Aug. 25 (ZFJ) — The New Jersey Office of the Attorney General (OAG) has revised its use-of-force policy to “increase the likelihood of peaceful resolutions to encounters between police and barricaded individuals,” Attorney General Matthew J. Platkin said in a statement.&#xA;The change in policy, which had last been changed in December 2020, comes weeks after the July 28 shooting of Victoria Lee, who was killed while threatening cops during a “mental breakdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metuchen police arrest Bayonne man for attempted murder, arson, stalking</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/metuchen-arsonist-stalker-arrest/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 14:32:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/metuchen-arsonist-stalker-arrest/</guid>
      <description>METUCHEN, N.J., Aug. 22 (ZFJ) — Walid Beshai, 36, of Bayonne, was arrested by Metuchen police at his residence on Wednesday, Aug. 14, in connection with a fire in the borough on June 27, 2024.&#xA;Patrol officers responded to the scene of a fire on June 27, 2024, at about 1:30 a.m., according to an affidavit of probable cause submitted to the court by police. Three residents were removed from a two-family residential structure, and a garage that contained one of the victim’s vehicles was actively on fire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Andy “Dean” DeNicola, J.P. Stevens band director for 50 years, dies at 72</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/obituary-andy-denicola-jps-band-director-50-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 23:20:46 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/obituary-andy-denicola-jps-band-director-50-years/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Aug. 11 (ZFJ) — Andrew “Dean” S. DeNicola, 55, band director at John P. Stevens High School for 50 years, died on May 20, 2024, after many years of battling heart disease.&#xA;“His devotion toward music, the band program, and his students was unparalleled, and anyone who had the pleasure of getting to know Andy knew he was having fun and living his life to the fullest,” wrote the Central Jersey Music Educators Association on Instagram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bodycam footage of fatal police-involved shooting during Fort Lee mental health call released</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/2024-07-28-fort-lee-fatal-police-involved-shooting-bodycam-footage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 15:48:25 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/2024-07-28-fort-lee-fatal-police-involved-shooting-bodycam-footage/</guid>
      <description>EDITOR&amp;rsquo;S NOTE: This news report contains graphic details of the police-involved shooting and vulgarities that could be offensive or disturbing to some readers.&#xA;Aug. 19 (ZFJ) — Body camera footage of the fatal shooting of Victoria G. Lee, 25, of Fort Lee, by Fort Lee Police Officer Tony Pickens, Jr., during a mental health call on July 28 was released by the N.J. Attorney General’s Office (OAG) on Friday, Aug.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>30-inch water main breaks on Woodbrook Drive</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-woodbrook-drive-30-in-water-main-break/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 15:51:50 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-woodbrook-drive-30-in-water-main-break/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Aug. 13 (ZFJ) — Someone just had the front of their house unexpectedly power washed. A 30-inch water main was broken by contractor work on Woodbrook Drive, said Edison Mayor Sam Joshi on social media on Monday, Aug. 12.&#xA;The water lines are operated by the Middlesex Water Company.&#xA;Residents shouldn’t have water flow disrupted because the broken line is separate from the ones used for residential distribution, according to Joshi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retired Edison Firefighter Raymond Tibok dies at 58</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/obituary-edison-retired-firefighter-raymond-tibok/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 14:28:32 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/obituary-edison-retired-firefighter-raymond-tibok/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Aug. 12 (ZFJ) — Retired Edison Firefighter Raymond Tibok, 58, of Edison, died peacefully on Thursday, Aug. 8, at JFK Medical Center.&#xA;He was born in Perth Amboy and a lifelong resident of Edison. He served Edison as a firefighter for 30 years before retiring in 2022.&#xA;Tibok graduated from John P. Stevens High School in 1984.&#xA;“He loved fishing, working on cars, and playing southern rock with his guitar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edison Firefighter Howard C. Tarlow dies at 47</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/obituary-edison-howard-c-tarlow-firefighter-local-1197-treasurer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 14:22:41 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/obituary-edison-howard-c-tarlow-firefighter-local-1197-treasurer/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Aug. 12 (ZFJ) — Edison Firefighter Howard Chaim Tarlow, 47, died on Wednesday, July 10, reported the Edison Firefighters Association, International Association of Fire Fighters (IAFF) Local 1197.&#xA;MyCentralJersey.com reported that township officials said that Tarlow died unexpectedly at home.&#xA;Tarlow began his career in fire services when he joined the Highland Park Volunteer Fire Department in 2008 “after expressing to a friend he wanted to give back to the community,” said IAFF Local 1197 on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edison police Lieutenant Donald Ship dies at 38</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/obituary-edison-police-lieutenant-donald-ship/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 22:31:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/obituary-edison-police-lieutenant-donald-ship/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Aug. 11 (ZFJ) — Edison police Lieutenant Donald Ship, 38, of Piscataway, died on Wednesday, July 10.&#xA;New Jersey 101.5 reported that Police Chief Thomas Bryan told them that Ship died at home following a “short illness.”&#xA;“Lieutenant Ship grew up in Edison and dedicated his entire life and career to giving back to the community that raised him,” said the Edison Police Department on social media.&#xA;Ship began his career in law enforcement as a Kean University police officer before he transferred to the Edison Police Department on Jan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed holds interest rates at July 31 meeting</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/business/2024/july-31-fomc-meeting-rates-held/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 23:48:43 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/business/2024/july-31-fomc-meeting-rates-held/</guid>
      <description>Aug. 8 (ZFJ) — The Federal Reserve maintained the target federal funds rate at 5.25-5.50% at the Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC)’s July 31 meeting.&#xA;This rate was set on July 26, 2023, and has been held steady since then. The Fed has been aggressively increasing the interest rate since raising it from 0.00-0.25% to 0.25-0.50% in March 2022 in order to fight stubborn inflation.&#xA;“The labor market has come into better balance and the unemployment rate remains low,” said Fed Chair Jerome Powell in his opening remarks at a press conference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>28 AP exams are going digital from May 2025</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/college-board-28-ap-exams-go-digital-may-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:11:57 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/college-board-28-ap-exams-go-digital-may-2025/</guid>
      <description>Aug. 1 (ZFJ) — The College Board has announced that, starting May 2025, 28 AP Exams will have their standard paper testing discontinued. Instead, these exams will be administered digitally through the Bluebook app. All schools and test centers will have to administer these exams digitally, though paper exams will still be available to select students approved by the College Board.&#xA;The acceleration to digital testing was done to further protect the integrity and security of AP exams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fort Lee police officer fatally shoots woman during mental health call</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/fort-lee-police-shooting-mental-health-call/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 18:38:31 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/fort-lee-police-shooting-mental-health-call/</guid>
      <description>July 30 (ZFJ) — A Fort Lee police officer responding to a mental health call fatally shot Victoria G. Lee, 26, of Fort Lee, on Sunday, July 28, according to the N.J. Attorney General’s Office (OAG).&#xA;OAG said in a press release that on Sunday, at about 1:25 a.m., Fort Lee police responded to “The Pinnacle” apartment complex on Main Street after receiving a 911 call from a man reporting that his sister was having a mental health crisis and needed to go to the hospital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One dead, one injured after Route 1 crash in Edison</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/july-28-edison-fatal-crash-motorcycles-bmw-suv/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 23:13:30 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/july-28-edison-fatal-crash-motorcycles-bmw-suv/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., July 30 (ZFJ) — One motorcyclist was killed and one motorcyclist was seriously injured in a crash at the intersection of Route 1 North and Old Post Road in Edison on Sunday, July 28.&#xA;On Sunday, at about 8:13 p.m., authorities responded to the intersection after receiving a report of a multi-vehicle crash, according to a press release from the Middlesex County Prosecutor’s Office.&#xA;Police located Alexander Teshima Chong, 44, of Belleville, who had been operating a motorcycle at the time of the collision.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Din Tai Fung makes East Coast debut in New York City</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/din-tai-fung-nyc-grand-opening/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 20:52:38 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/din-tai-fung-nyc-grand-opening/</guid>
      <description>July 26 (ZFJ) — After much anticipation—two years after its initial announcement—the renowned Taiwanese restaurant chain Din Tai Fung celebrated the grand opening of its first East Coast location in New York City on July 18, 2024. Besides being the first location on the East Coast, it is also the world’s largest Din Tai Fung. Located at 1633 Broadway, the restaurant occupies a vast 25,000-square-foot space, capable of accommodating up to 450 diners and 500 employees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: Deadpool &amp; Wolverine delivers as delight</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/opinion/2024/deadpool-and-wolverine-movie-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 18:38:31 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/opinion/2024/deadpool-and-wolverine-movie-review/</guid>
      <description>April of 2019. It was a beautiful day outside. Birds were singing, flowers were blooming, and on days like these kids like us would be playing a game of cricket. But not today. We were huddled in a circle, discussing theories for the upcoming Avengers movie. I was the main speaker, cooking up some mind blowing theories (I copied them from MatPat[1]). There was some sort of magic in those movies you couldn’t find anywhere else.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>June 2024 marks 12th month of global temperature reaching 1.5 C above pre-industrial</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2024/june-monthly-climate-bulletin-12th-consecutive-month-1.5-c-above/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 12:43:30 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2024/june-monthly-climate-bulletin-12th-consecutive-month-1.5-c-above/</guid>
      <description>July 27 (ZFJ) — At 1.50 C (2.7 F) above the estimated June average for 1850-1900, June 2024 has become the 12th consecutive month to reach or break the 1.5 C threshold set by the Paris Agreement, according to the European Union’s Copernicus Climate Change Service (C3S).&#xA;With a surface air temperature of 16.66 C (61.99 F), June 2024 was warmer globally than any previous June in C3S’ ERA5 data record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edison man charged for Millbrook Village stabbing</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-man-charged-fatal-stabbing-millbrook-village/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 16:15:02 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-man-charged-fatal-stabbing-millbrook-village/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., July 26 (ZFJ) — Joan Franklin Polanco, 37, of Edison, has been charged in connection with the fatal stabbing that occurred in Edison on Sunday, July 21, 2024, announced Middlesex County Prosecutor Yolanda Ciccone and Chief Thomas Bryan of the Edison Police Department.&#xA;On July 21, Edison police responded to a call for a welfare check of the victim, according to a criminal complaint and affidavit. Shortly after, at about 4:37 p.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edison High assistant principal accused of threatening Muslim students</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/cair-nj-edison-high-school-assistant-principal-msa-iftar-audio-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 19:25:48 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/cair-nj-edison-high-school-assistant-principal-msa-iftar-audio-recording/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., July 24 (ZFJ) — Muslim students from Edison High School are alleging that one of the school’s assistant principals intimidated them over their club’s annual iftar event during a February meeting.&#xA;Iftar is the breaking of the daily fast during the holy Islamic month of Ramadan. The New Jersey chapter of the Council on American-Islamic Relations (CAIR-NJ), a Muslim civil rights group, says that Assistant Principal Nicole Himmelstein met with eight board members of the school’s Moon and Stars Association (MSA) following their request to hold a joint iftar event and invite students from Piscataway and North Brunswick.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flavors and Fun: 2024 Dream Food Fest</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/dream-food-fest-2024-american-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 19:42:31 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/dream-food-fest-2024-american-dream/</guid>
      <description>EAST RUTHERFORD, N.J., ZFJ (July 19) — The Dream Food Fest has again returned to New Jersey this summer. Hosted in partnership with the American Dream Mall, the food festival was held from July 12-15 in Lot 26 of the mall in East Rutherford, N.J., gathering 120 street food vendors—including Tojo&amp;rsquo;s Kitchen, Cozy Tea Loft, and Dumpling N&amp;rsquo; Dips—selling a variety of cuisines from around the glove: Korean corn dogs, Neapolitan pizza, Jamaican jerk chicken, and much more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump shot at Pennsylvania rally</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/trump-shot-assassination-attempt-pennsylvania-rally/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 22:04:09 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/trump-shot-assassination-attempt-pennsylvania-rally/</guid>
      <description>July 14 (ZFJ) — Former President Donald Trump was shot in the upper right ear in an assassination attempt while he was at a rally in Butler, Pennsylvania, on Saturday, July 13.&#xA;At about 6:15 p.m., several minutes after Trump began addressing the audience, a shooter fired towards the stage “from an elevated position outside of the rally venue,” said Anthony Guglielmi, chief of communications for the U.S. Secret Service, in a statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T1 emerges as the inaugural League of Legends champions of the Esports World Cup 2024</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/arts-and-entertainment/2024/t1-league-of-legends-esports-world-cup-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 14:58:01 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/arts-and-entertainment/2024/t1-league-of-legends-esports-world-cup-2024/</guid>
      <description>July 12 (ZFJ) — T1 became the first-ever League of Legends champions in the inaugural Esports World Cup (EWC) after emerging victorious against Top Esports (TES) 3-1 in the grand finals on Sunday, July 7, at the Qiddiya Arena.&#xA;The EWC is an annual international gaming tournament organized by the Esports World Cup Foundation, succeeding the previous Gamers8 festival. This year, the EWC 2024 is being held in Riyadh, Saudi Arabia, spanning from July 3 to August 25.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perth Amboy man charged with first-degree murder</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/june-30-perth-amboy-first-degree-murder-domestic-violence/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 15:46:18 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/june-30-perth-amboy-first-degree-murder-domestic-violence/</guid>
      <description>July 9 (ZFJ) — Raymond Maldonado, 34, of Perth Amboy has been charged in connection with a June 30 homicide in Perth Amboy, announced authorities on July 1.&#xA;According to a criminal complaint, on June 30, at about 1:12 p.m., the Perth Amboy Police Department received a 911 call from a relative who said that she went to the victim’s home to check on her and found her unresponsive on the living room floor with bruising and blood around her face.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German city temporarily renames itself after Taylor Swift</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/foreign-affairs/europe/2024/gelsenkirchen-temporary-rename-swiftkirchen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 01:10:28 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/foreign-affairs/europe/2024/gelsenkirchen-temporary-rename-swiftkirchen/</guid>
      <description>July 9 (ZFJ) — Gelsenkirchen has temporarily renamed itself to Swiftkirchen ahead of Taylor Swift’s concerts there, announced the German city on July 2.&#xA;Swift will be performing in three concerts at the VELTINS-Arena from July 17-19 as part of her Eras Tour.&#xA;Local Swiftie Aleshanee Westhoff of Emmerich started a petition for this change, which Mayor Karin Welge thought was “a great idea.”&#xA;The Swiftkirchen sign. CITY OF GELSENKIRCHEN/Handout</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two officers shot, one suspect deceased after Woodbridge hotel shooting</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/woodbridge-fords-raritan-hotel-shooting-suspect-deceased-nypd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 11:42:52 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/woodbridge-fords-raritan-hotel-shooting-suspect-deceased-nypd/</guid>
      <description>WOODBRIDGE, N.J., July 3 (ZFJ) — Two officers were shot and one suspect was killed at the Raritan Hotel on King Georges Post Road in the Fords section of Woodbridge on June 13, according to the N.J. Attorney General’s Office.&#xA;On June 12, Edison police officers using an automated license plate reader found that a vehicle sought by New York City authorities in connection with a shooting that left its victim with life-threatening injuries was in the area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oak Tree Pond receives American Revolutionary War historical marker</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/oak-tree-pond-sign-dedication-battle-of-short-hills/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 23:19:38 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/oak-tree-pond-sign-dedication-battle-of-short-hills/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., July 2 (ZFJ) — Edison unveiled a new sign commemorating the Battle of Short Hills at Oak Tree Pond Historic Park on Wednesday, June 26.&#xA;The sign, installed 250 years after the American Revolutionary War battle, was a gift from the Middlesex County Board of County Commissioners.&#xA;The Short Hills Battlefield Historic District was placed on the National Register of Historic Places in 2014 by the U.S. Department of the Interior.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College Board has sent free score send AP score reports</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/2024-college-board-ap-free-score-sends-sent/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:06:28 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/2024-college-board-ap-free-score-sends-sent/</guid>
      <description>July 2 (ZFJ) — This one’s mainly for the class of 2024, with some exceptions, I suppose. If you used your free AP score report send, those have been sent out now.&#xA;The AP Students dashboard, under “View Past Score Sends,” indicates that reports were sent out on June 30.&#xA;So what? Well, you may be able to view all of your AP scores, including those from this year’s exams, on your college’s unofficial transcript—a minor boon to students like me who prefer not to stay their curiosity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edison opens its first splash park</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-opens-first-splash-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 22:22:07 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-opens-first-splash-park/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., July 1 (ZFJ) — Edison’s first splash park is now open to the public at Papaianni Park, announced Mayor Sam Joshi.&#xA;The opening was kicked off with a first ever youth league pep rally on June 29, and the park was made available to the general public the following day.&#xA;In keeping with inventor Thomas Edison’s history with the township, the splash pad is shaped like a lightbulb. The park also features a 20 foot replica of the Edison light tower, globes, and water guns shaped like classic film cameras.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edison police opens Menlo Park Mall substation</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-police-menlo-park-mall-substation-may-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 00:25:43 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-police-menlo-park-mall-substation-may-2024/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., June 30 (ZFJ) — Edison police opened a substation in Menlo Park Mall on May 24. It is located in the former Jos A. Bank store between Barnes &amp;amp; Noble and a parking garage.&#xA;Police officials celebrated the opening, which Deputy Chief Robert Dudash said had been “a brainchild of the police department and the mall for a lot of years now.”&#xA;“This substation will actually enhance our services to the public and to the mall,” said Chief Thomas Bryan at the ribbon cutting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College Board makes changes to all four AP Physics exams starting from 2024-2025</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/college-board-ap-physics-updates-2024-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 18:01:17 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/college-board-ap-physics-updates-2024-2025/</guid>
      <description>June 19 (ZFJ) — Starting from 2024-2025, College Board will revise the course content and exams for its four AP Physics courses for better alignment with corresponding introductory college courses and better communication of the knowledge required for the exams.&#xA;One of the most notable course updates for AP Physics 1 is the addition of a new unit: Fluids, which was previously part of AP Physics 2. As such, Fluids will no longer be part of the AP Physics 2 curriculum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jim Muldowney, former Edison High baseball coach and athletic director, dies at 68</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/sports/2024/obituary-jim-muldowney-ehs-baseball-coach-athletic-director/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 22:22:44 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/sports/2024/obituary-jim-muldowney-ehs-baseball-coach-athletic-director/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., June 8 (ZFJ) — James “Diamond Jim” Muldowney, 68, an Edison High School baseball coach and athletic director, died on Tuesday, May 21, after briefly battling cancer.&#xA;“Jim dedicated his life to the betterment of students and athletes, leaving an indelible mark on the community,” reads his obituary. He was a mentor to countless students and coaches alike.&#xA;Muldowney was born in Pennsylvania and raised in Edison. He graduated from Edison High in 1973 and lived in North Brunswick for 33 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo to announce Switch’s successor within current fiscal year</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/arts-and-entertainment/2024/nintendo-switch-successor-announcement-fy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 09:45:38 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/arts-and-entertainment/2024/nintendo-switch-successor-announcement-fy-2025/</guid>
      <description>May 21 (ZFJ) — Nintendo will announce the successor to its Switch console by the end of the current fiscal year—so, by March 31, 2025.&#xA;The confirmation came from Nintendo President Shuntaro Furukawa in an X post on the same day the company released its fiscal year 2024 (year ending March 31, 2024) earnings report.&#xA;This is Furukawa, President of Nintendo. We will make an announcement about the successor to Nintendo Switch within this fiscal year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Plainfield man arrested for vandalism of Rutgers Center for Islamic Life</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/fbi-arrest-somerset-county-man-cilru-vandalism-eid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 22:19:37 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/fbi-arrest-somerset-county-man-cilru-vandalism-eid/</guid>
      <description>NEW BRUNSWICK, N.J., April 22 (ZFJ) — Jacob Beacher, 24, of North Plainfield, has been charged with a federal hate crime for breaking into the Center for Islamic Life at Rutgers University (CILRU) on 122 College Avenue in New Brunswick, announced federal authorities on Monday, April 22.&#xA;Beacher, not affiliated with Rutgers, was arrested this morning and federally charged with one count of intentional or attempted obstruction of religious practice and one count of making false statements to federal authorities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube requires creators to disclose use of AI in realistic content</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/business/2024/youtube-ai-generated-content-disclosures-policy-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:44:42 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/business/2024/youtube-ai-generated-content-disclosures-policy-tool/</guid>
      <description>April 14 (ZFJ) — YouTube is requiring creators to disclose when realistic-appearing content—anything that can easily be mistaken for a real person, place, scene, or event—has been generated or altered using artificial intelligence, announced the video platform on March 18.&#xA;Examples provided by YouTube of content requiring disclosure include digitally replacing a person’s face, synthetically generating a person’s face, making it appear as if a real building caught fire, altering a real cityscape to appear differently, and realistically showing a fictional tornado moving toward a real town.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPA finalizes toughest-ever emissions standards for model years 2027-2032</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/epa-toughest-ever-emissions-standards-electric-vehicles/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 16:36:02 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/epa-toughest-ever-emissions-standards-electric-vehicles/</guid>
      <description>April 14 (ZFJ) — The Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) finalized the toughest emissions standards yet for light and medium-duty vehicles of model years (MY) 2027-2032, announced the agency on March 20.&#xA;The agency projects that the updated standards in Multi Pollutant Emissions Standards for Model Years 2027 and Later Light-Duty and Medium-Duty Vehicles will avoid 7.2 billion tons of carbon emissions between 2027-2055 and provide almost $100 billion of net benefits to society, including improved air quality and reduced annual fuel and maintenance costs for drivers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA approves Dexcom’s Stelo, the first over-the-counter continuous glucose monitor</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/health-and-medicine/2024/fda-dexcom-stelo-first-ever-otc-continuous-glucose-monitor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 20:53:17 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/health-and-medicine/2024/fda-dexcom-stelo-first-ever-otc-continuous-glucose-monitor/</guid>
      <description>April 14 (ZFJ) — The Food and Drug Administration cleared the Dexcom Stelo Glucose Biosensor System, the first continuous glucose monitor (CGM) approved for use without a prescription in America, for marketing on March 5.&#xA;Stelo is an integrated CGM (iCGM) intended for anyone 18 years and older who doesn’t use insulin, such as diabetic individuals treating their condition with oral medications or people without diabetes who want to see how diet and exercise impact their blood sugar levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woodbridge Center mall sold to new management</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/woodbridge-center-sold-new-management-mayor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 17:21:26 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/woodbridge-center-sold-new-management-mayor/</guid>
      <description>WOODBRIDGE, N.J., April 4 (ZFJ) — Woodbridge Center has been sold to new management, announced Woodbridge Mayor John E. McCormac in his State of the Township address on Feb. 23.&#xA;“Woodbridge Center, like major malls across America, has struggled because of the internet and the ease of buying directly online,” he said. “It has done an admirable job of diversifying outside of basic retail by attracting new tenants, but it has just not been enough.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rutgers Center for Islamic Life broken into, vandalized on Eid</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/rutgers-center-islamic-life-vandalized-eid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:33:13 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/rutgers-center-islamic-life-vandalized-eid/</guid>
      <description>NEW BRUNSWICK, N.J., April 14 (ZFJ) — The Center for Islamic Life at Rutgers University (CILRU) was broken into and vandalized on Eid.&#xA;The Center reported on Instagram that art pieces with Quranic verses, windows, TVs, printers, artwork, and the Palestinian flag were damaged.&#xA;“This reprehensible act, occurring on our sacred day, is undoubtedly fueled by Islamophobia is clearly a hate crime targeting our Muslim population at Rutgers,” the Center wrote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man sentenced to life in prison without parole for 2018 Edison Speedway gas station murder</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-speedway-gas-station-murderer-sentenced-life-no-parole/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 13:04:01 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-speedway-gas-station-murderer-sentenced-life-no-parole/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., April 4 (ZFJ) — Marcus Wright, 27, of Beaufort, South Carolina, was sentenced to life in prison without parole for the murder of an Edison Speedway gas station employee that occurred on Dec. 20, 2018, announced Middlesex County Prosecutor Yolanda Ciccone.&#xA;Wright was convicted on Sept. 12, 2023, of the murder of John Bertram, 38, of the Fords section of Woodbridge; armed robbery; conspiracy to commit armed robbery; and possession of a weapon for an unlawful purpose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magnitude 4.8 earthquake 7 km north of Whitehouse Station strikes NJ</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/usgs-earthquake-nj-4.8-whitehouse-station/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 11:51:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/usgs-earthquake-nj-4.8-whitehouse-station/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., April 5 (ZFJ) — A magnitude 4.8 earthquake struck seven kilometers north of Whitehouse Station, New Jersey, at 10:23 a.m. on Friday, April 5, according to the United States Geological Survey (USGS).&#xA;Wow! A M4.8 struck in New Jersey this morning around 10:30 am local time. Shaking was widely felt from Maine to Washington D.C. Did you feel this earthquake? Share your experience here: https://t.co/xdohQbzpcq https://t.co/ADcDLsTp8b pic.twitter.com/bAjEbSgvwc&#xA;&amp;mdash; USGS Earthquakes (@USGS_Quakes) April 5, 2024 ZFJ reporters and residents in Edison, about 25-35 miles out from the epicenter, reported feeling their houses shaking for about 10 seconds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Brunswick police make gun trafficking arrest after five-month investigation</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/south-brunswick-police-gun-trafficking-arrest-wayne-bagley/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 16:18:13 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/south-brunswick-police-gun-trafficking-arrest-wayne-bagley/</guid>
      <description>April 4 (ZFJ) — Wayne Bagley, 68, of South Brunswick was arrested following a five-month investigation, announced South Brunswick Police Chief Raymond Hayducka on Tuesday, March 5.&#xA;According to Hayducka, the joint effort by the South Brunswick Police Department, ATF, and the Middlesex County Prosecutor’s Office revealed that Bagley traveled to other states, purchased handguns at gun shows, and transported the firearms back to New Jersey for resale. Over the course of the investigation, he traveled to West Virginia, North Carolina, and Pennsylvania.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comcast approved to provide internet services to Edison</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/comcast-internet-approved-edison-bpu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 14:30:30 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/comcast-internet-approved-edison-bpu/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., April 4 (ZFJ) — Comcast has been approved to provide internet services to Edison, announced the company on March 20, 2024.&#xA;The New Jersey Board of Public Utilities granted its application for a system-wide franchise to operate in Edison, allowing it to offer its Xfinity and Comcast Business services to the township.&#xA;Residents will have access to all of Xfinity’s internet products. According to the company’s website, costs range from a starting price of $20 a month for a 150 mbps connection to a starting price of $85 a month for a 1,200 mbps connection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edison Board of Education announces measures to tackle substance abuse</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-boe-substance-abuse-committee-vape-detectors/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 01:13:01 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-boe-substance-abuse-committee-vape-detectors/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., April 3 (ZFJ) — Edison Board of Education President Biral Patel announced measures to tackle substance abuse in schools at the Feb. 27 action meeting.&#xA;“It has been brought to our attention that issues persist, especially in two of our high schools,” Patel said in prepared remarks during the meeting. “To have an enforcement so everyone feels safe, updating policies are very important so administrators have the tools to address the issues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inman Avenue railroad crossing gates malfunction</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/inman-avenue-railroad-crossing-gates-malfunction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 00:24:06 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/inman-avenue-railroad-crossing-gates-malfunction/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., March 31 (ZFJ) — The railroad crossing gates on Inman Avenue, nearby CVS Pharmacy and the Westgate neighborhood, malfunctioned on Saturday, March 30.&#xA;Two ZFJ reporters were buying doughnuts (Boston Kreme remains our forever beloved) when they noticed the crossing’s lights flashing and alarm ringing despite no train being in sight. Upon closer inspection, they saw one gate on the Westgate side stuck in the closed position.&#xA;A police officer on the scene told The ZFJ that they called the rail company at about 5:00 p.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edison Town Council unanimously rejects marijuana zone expansion</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-council-unanimously-rejects-marijuana-zone-expansion/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 11:01:27 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-council-unanimously-rejects-marijuana-zone-expansion/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., March 14 (ZFJ) — Edison councilmen unanimously rejected an ordinance that would have expanded the zones in which cannabis establishments would be permitted at their regular meeting on Wednesday, Feb. 28.&#xA;The ordinance was first introduced at the Feb. 15 combined council meeting, where all councilmen except Richard Brescher and Ajay Patil voted in support of it. It went up for final adoption on Feb. 28.&#xA;Map of the general area where cannabis establishments are currently permitted (in green) and zone expansions proposed by O.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edison Town Council introduces ordinance to expand permissible marijuana establishment areas</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-council-ordinance-introduced-marijuana-zoning-districts-expansion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 00:00:42 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-council-ordinance-introduced-marijuana-zoning-districts-expansion/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Feb. 26 (ZFJ) — Edison Township held a combined council meeting on Feb. 15 that discussed a proposed ordinance that would expand the areas in which cannabis establishments can be approved in.&#xA;The ordinance&amp;rsquo;s public hearing and final adoption was scheduled to be on Wednesday, Feb. 28, but the Municipal Clerk&amp;rsquo;s Office informed The ZFJ in a phone call on Monday, Feb. 26, that it was going to be removed from the council&amp;rsquo;s agenda.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One juvenile arrested for Menlo Park Mall fight</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/one-juvenile-fight-menlo-park-mall-presidents-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 22:23:52 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/one-juvenile-fight-menlo-park-mall-presidents-day/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Feb. 21 (ZFJ) — One juvenile was arrested in connection with a fight that occurred at Menlo Park Mall on Monday, Feb. 19.&#xA;At about 5:30 p.m., Edison police received a call reporting that shots had been fired at the mall, said Police Chief Tom Bryan in a phone call.&#xA;Based on the emergency call, police assumed that there was an active shooter, so they organized a large response.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Six arrested at Menlo Park Mall, two guns recovered</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/four-juveniles-two-adults-arrested-menlo-park-mall-two-guns/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 22:23:11 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/four-juveniles-two-adults-arrested-menlo-park-mall-two-guns/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Feb. 21 (ZFJ) — Four juveniles and two adults were arrested by Edison police at Menlo Park Mall on Saturday, Feb. 17.&#xA;At about 9:30 p.m., an individual called 911 and said that they were being chased by a group of kids, Edison Police Chief Tom Bryan said in a phone call.&#xA;The police apprehended the suspects behind the McDonald’s right beside the mall.&#xA;They were in possession of two firearms, one of which was stolen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glen Rock Starbucks&#39; sign vandalized with red paint, police investigating as bias crime</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/glen-rock-starbucks-vandalism-red-paint-police-bias-crime/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 23:24:18 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/glen-rock-starbucks-vandalism-red-paint-police-bias-crime/</guid>
      <description>Feb. 20 (ZFJ) — Glen Rock police are investigating vandalism of the Glen Rock Starbucks’ sign as a bias incident.&#xA;At 8:05 a.m. on Monday, Feb. 19, the manager of the Starbucks at 224 Rock Road in the borough’s Central Business District notified police that red paint had been splashed over the café’s sign at the corner of Rock Road and Glen Avenue.&#xA;The responding officer also found stickers on the sign with messages related to the Israel-Hamas war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metuchen Planning Board approves drive-thru marijuana dispensary plan</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/metuchen-planning-board-dasco-marijuana-drive-thru-approval/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 18:44:17 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/metuchen-planning-board-dasco-marijuana-drive-thru-approval/</guid>
      <description>METUCHEN, N.J., Feb. 18 (ZFJ) — The Metuchen Planning Board adopted a resolution at its reorganization meeting on Jan. 4 to approve Dasco Solutions’ drive-thru marijuana dispensary plan.&#xA;Dasco intends to convert a 3,037 square foot former bank building at 700 Middlesex Avenue into a cannabis dispensary. It presented its proposal to the board on Nov. 2, 2023, and the resolution reflects the board’s actions on that date.&#xA;RESOLUTION 23-1368 VOTE RESULTS</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kansas City Chiefs defeat San Francisco 49ers 25-22 in Super Bowl LVIII</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/sports/2024/super-bowl-lviii-chiefs-defeat-49ers-25-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 21:16:20 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/sports/2024/super-bowl-lviii-chiefs-defeat-49ers-25-22/</guid>
      <description>Feb. 14 (ZFJ) — The Kansas City Chiefs defeated the San Francisco 49ers 25-22 in Super Bowl LVIII on Sunday, Feb. 11.&#xA;Securing their third Super Bowl win in five years, the Chiefs have achieved a dynasty.&#xA;The first half of the game was characterized by many punts and a few fumbles. Momentum really picked up from the second half. Overall? Absolutely thrilling game.&#xA;The Chiefs won the coin toss and deferred.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint European Torus researchers announce nuclear fusion energy record</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2024/jet-tokamak-nuclear-fusion-record-69-mj/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 23:46:16 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2024/jet-tokamak-nuclear-fusion-record-69-mj/</guid>
      <description>Feb. 8 (ZFJ) — Joint European Torus (JET) researchers announced on Thursday, Feb. 8, that their tokamak set a new world record of 69.26 megajoules released in controlled nuclear fusion energy on Oct. 3, 2023, at 19:14 GMT.&#xA;The record, equivalent to the energy released from burning two kilograms of coal, was set during a single pulse of JET over six seconds with only 0.21 milligrams of fuel. JET’s previous record from 2022 was 59 MJ.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recovered firearm in Union Catholic High School leads to lockdowns, student arrested</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/union-catholic-high-school-gun-lockdowns-arrest/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 22:41:56 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/union-catholic-high-school-gun-lockdowns-arrest/</guid>
      <description>SCOTCH PLAINS, N.J., Feb. 7 (ZFJ) — The discovery of a firearm in Union Catholic High School on Monday, Jan. 22, resulted in lockdowns at nearby schools and the arrest of one student.&#xA;The Scotch Plains Police Department said in a press release that it received a call at about 10:45 a.m. from a Union Catholic administrator concerning a handgun that had been recovered in the school.&#xA;The school was placed on lockdown, and Scotch Plains police officers recovered the weapon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Music Group pulls music from TikTok after licensing agreement expires</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/business/2024/universal-music-group-tiktok-license-expired-music-pulled/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 01:00:23 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/business/2024/universal-music-group-tiktok-license-expired-music-pulled/</guid>
      <description>Feb. 6 (ZFJ) — Universal Music Group, the world’s largest music corporation, has pulled all of its music from TikTok following the expiration of its previous licensing agreement on Jan. 31 after renewal talks collapsed.&#xA;That means that any TikToks containing music from Taylor Swift, Bad Bunny, The Weeknd, Drake, Harry Styles, and many, many more artists have had their audio muted. Until a new licensing agreement is finalized, TikTok users won’t be able to add any music from Universal’s catalog to their videos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gas odor prompts evacuation at J.P. Stevens High School</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/jps-suspected-gas-leak-evacuation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 17:05:19 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/jps-suspected-gas-leak-evacuation/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Feb. 1 (ZFJ) — A suspected gas leak resulted in the evacuation of J.P. Stevens High School students and staff on Thursday, Feb. 1, according to the school district.&#xA;An odor of gas near the art and music wing and in the back of the building caused the evacuation, which, according to a ZFJ reporter, began around the start of third period.&#xA;The Edison Fire Department and Elizabethtown Gas Company concluded that a construction crew hit an inactive gas line that still had residual gas remaining in it, resulting in the odor, according to a statement by Edison Township Public Schools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YESTERcades of Metuchen to open on Friday, Feb. 2</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/yestercades-announces-metuchen-opening-date/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 23:34:31 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/yestercades-announces-metuchen-opening-date/</guid>
      <description>METUCHEN, N.J., Jan. 30 (ZFJ) — YESTERcades of Metuchen will have its ribbon cutting and opening on Friday, Feb. 2, at 4:00 p.m., according to its announcement on social media.&#xA;Patrons are asked not to line up outside the building at 442 Main Street, Metuchen, before 3:30 p.m.&#xA;YESTERcades is a retro video game venue known for its focus on “golden age” arcade classics.&#xA;The arcade has at least 82 games moved into the Metuchen building, according to a social media post.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edison’s first Asian American police officer, Joseph Vincent Luistro, dies after battling ALS</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-police-joseph-vincent-luistro-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 01:14:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-police-joseph-vincent-luistro-death/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Jan. 21 (ZFJ) — Sgt. Joseph Vincent Luistro, 55, Edison Township’s first Asian American and Filipino American police officer, died on Thursday, Jan. 18, after battling ALS.&#xA;“Sergeant Luistro touched the lives of many with his selfless spirit,” said the Edison Police Department, calling him a “trailblazer” for his role in “actively fostering inclusivity in law enforcement careers.”&#xA;Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis, also known as Lou Gehrig’s disease, is a neurological disorder in which motor neurons progressively die, causing loss of control of muscle movement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not a Game Theory: MatPat announces upcoming retirement from YouTube</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/arts-and-entertainment/2024/matpat-game-theorists-youtube-retirement/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 15:17:48 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/arts-and-entertainment/2024/matpat-game-theorists-youtube-retirement/</guid>
      <description>Jan. 16 (ZFJ) — “It’s not clickbait,” MatPat begins, in a video uploaded on Tuesday, Jan. 9. The title: “Goodbye Internet.”&#xA;The video announces that MatPat’s last video on The Game Theorists, a channel centered around detangling the storylines of countless games, will be uploaded on March 9. Since its first theory, posted on April 18, 2011, Matthew “MatPat” Patrick has been the lead face of the channel, recounting theories around popular game franchises such as Five Nights at Freddy’s and Pokémon and ending each episode with his iconic, “But that’s just a theory—a Game Theory!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Scott indefinitely ends decade-long YouTube series</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/arts-and-entertainment/2024/tom-scott-youtube-retirement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 22:45:53 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/arts-and-entertainment/2024/tom-scott-youtube-retirement/</guid>
      <description>Jan. 14 (ZFJ) — Sixteen hours into 2024, informational YouTuber Tom Scott uploaded the final video of his Things You Might Not Know series, which spanned exactly ten years with weekly uploads after its start in 2014.&#xA;From his first video—“Breakfast: Fortified With Iron,” posted on June 6, 2006—to his first (and likely last) video of the new year, Tom Scott has taken his place in YouTube as an educational entertainer, introducing new facts and experiences to an audience now consisting of more than six million subscribers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edison police charge van driver with leaving disabled person in vehicle overnight</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-police-private-van-driver-neglect-disabled-person/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 22:20:37 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/edison-police-private-van-driver-neglect-disabled-person/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Jan. 13 (ZFJ) — Winnie Raini, 53, of Edison, has been charged with leaving an adult female with a developmental disability in a van overnight while employed as a private transportation driver, announced Middlesex County Prosecutor Yolanda Ciccone and Chief Thomas Bryan of the Edison Police Department.&#xA;Authorities began investigating allegations of neglect on Jan. 3, according to the criminal complaint against Raini.&#xA;According to the aide for the developmentally delayed female, the woman is transported by van back to her residence twice a week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghelsey Go tops 1,000 points in girls&#39; basketball</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/sports/2024/ghelsey-go-scores-thousandth-point-ehs-girls-basketball/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 20:31:34 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/sports/2024/ghelsey-go-scores-thousandth-point-ehs-girls-basketball/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Jan. 11 (ZFJ) — Senior Ghelsey Go has become the seventh girl and ninth player overall to score 1,000 points in basketball at Edison High School.&#xA;She scored 29 points in the varsity game against JFK on Saturday, Jan. 6, achieving the milestone after four years in high school basketball.&#xA;“I can’t even lie, when I scored the last points, my mind just went blank. I was like, what happens next, what’s going to happen next, and we still had a game to play, so I don’t think I really celebrated right away,” Go said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2023 confirmed hottest year on record, global temperature close to 1.5 C limit</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2024/c3s-2023-hottest-year-on-record-1.5-celsius-limit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 16:49:36 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2024/c3s-2023-hottest-year-on-record-1.5-celsius-limit/</guid>
      <description>Jan. 9 (ZFJ) — Scientists have confirmed 2023, which saw multiple record-breaking conditions, as the hottest year on record.&#xA;The year was characterized by many extreme weather events occurring globally, including heat waves, floods, droughts, and wildfires.&#xA;The Copernicus Climate Change Service (C3S), part of the European Union’s space program, reported the data in its Global Climate Highlights 2023 report, which is based mainly on its ERA5 reanalysis dataset, which goes back to 1940.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edison Board of Education and Township Council swear in new officials</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/2024-edison-council-boe-reorganization/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 01:44:05 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/2024-edison-council-boe-reorganization/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Jan. 6 (ZFJ) — The Edison Board of Education held its reorganization meeting on Tuesday, Jan. 2, while the Edison Township Council held it on Thursday, Jan. 4.&#xA;The candidates who won the general election on Nov. 7, 2023, were sworn in as elected officials at these meetings.&#xA;EDISON BOARD OF EDUCATION REORGANIZATION MEETING&#xA;Virginia White, first elected in 2020, and newcomers Christopher Lugo and Anjana R. Patel were sworn in as board of education members.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buses with migrants bound for New York arrive at NJ Transit stations</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/nyc-nj-migrant-buses-transit-stations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 17:47:05 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2024/nyc-nj-migrant-buses-transit-stations/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Jan. 1 (ZFJ) — Buses carrying migrants bound for New York City have been arriving at multiple NJ Transit stations, said local authorities across the state.&#xA;The Jersey City Office of Emergency Management said on X (formerly Twitter) that about 10 buses from Texas and one from Louisiana with approximately 397 migrants arrived at train stations in Secaucus, Fanwood, Edison, Trenton, and Jersey City since Saturday, Dec. 30.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New York Times sues Microsoft, OpenAI for using its news articles to train their AI</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/business/2023/nyt-openai-microsoft-copyright-civil-complaint/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 22:33:22 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/business/2023/nyt-openai-microsoft-copyright-civil-complaint/</guid>
      <description>NEW YORK, Dec. 31 (ZFJ) — The New York Times filed a federal copyright infringement lawsuit on Dec. 27 against Microsoft and OpenAI for using its news articles unauthorized to train generative artificial intelligence models.&#xA;The Times says it initiated negotiations with Microsoft and OpenAI in April 2023, but no licensing agreement, like in the case of The Associated Press, was reached, leading to the lawsuit.&#xA;“Defendants insist that their conduct is protected as ‘fair use’ because their unlicensed use of copyrighted content to train GenAI models serves a new ‘transformative’ purpose,” wrote The Times in its civil complaint.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA approves two sickle cell disease gene therapies, one based on CRISPR</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/health-and-medicine/2023/fda-approves-sickle-cell-casgevy-crispr-lyfgenia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 22:10:50 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/health-and-medicine/2023/fda-approves-sickle-cell-casgevy-crispr-lyfgenia/</guid>
      <description>Dec. 30 (ZFJ) — The U.S. Food and Drug Administration approved two cell-based gene therapies, Casgevy and Lyfgenia, to treat sickle cell disease in patients 12 years and older, the agency announced on Dec. 8, 2023. Casgevy is the first FDA-approved treatment to use CRISPR/Cas9 gene-editing technology.&#xA;Sickle cell disease is a group of inherited blood disorders. It affects about 100,000 Americans, is most common in African Americans, and also affects Hispanic Americans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taylor Swift tops 2023 Spotify global streams</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/arts-and-entertainment/2023/2023-spotify-wrapped-trends-taylor-swift/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 01:28:49 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/arts-and-entertainment/2023/2023-spotify-wrapped-trends-taylor-swift/</guid>
      <description>Dec. 28 (ZFJ) — Taylor Swift became Spotify’s top global artist of 2023 with over 26.1 billion streams worldwide, announced the music streaming platform in its 2023 Wrapped campaign on Nov. 29.&#xA;She dethroned Bad Bunny, who’d held the title for the past three years. Coming in second place, he had a “standout year” with his new album nadie sabe lo que va a pasar mañana. The Weeknd, Drake, and Peso Pluma also made the top five.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military air defense command NORAD tracks Santa in annual tradition</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/norad-tracks-santa-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 21:37:04 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/norad-tracks-santa-2023/</guid>
      <description>Dec. 24 (ZFJ) — NORAD, with 68 years of experience following Santa, is once again tracking the jolly good man.&#xA;Anyone interested can view Santa’s location on noradsanta.org or call in to the North American Aerospace Defense Command at 1-877-HI-NORAD. If they can’t reach a human on the line due to the volume of calls, they’ll receive an automated message reporting Santa’s position and a reminder to call back later to talk to someone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perth Amboy Magnet carpentry teacher charged with criminal sexual contact</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/perth-amboy-magnet-carpentry-teacher-charged-criminal-sexual-contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 22:23:28 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/perth-amboy-magnet-carpentry-teacher-charged-criminal-sexual-contact/</guid>
      <description>Dec. 23 (ZFJ) — Edward White, 56, of Tinton Falls, N.J., was arrested on charges of inappropriately touching students on Dec. 13, announced Middlesex County Prosecutor Yolanda Ciccone and Chief Lawrence Cattano of the Perth Amboy Police Department.&#xA;In a statement on Dec. 14, a Thursday, Middlesex County Magnet Schools Superintendent Jorge E. Diaz said that the school district became aware of an “alleged incident involving a teacher and a student” on Dec.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J.P. Stevens High School closed Monday, other schools delayed due to flooding</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/jps-edison-public-schools-storm-flooding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 23:24:37 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/jps-edison-public-schools-storm-flooding/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Dec. 18 (ZFJ) — J.P. Stevens High School was closed on Monday, Dec. 18, due to flooding and road closures while several other North Edison schools opened late.&#xA;John Adams Middle School, James Madison Primary School, James Madison Intermediate School, and FDR Preschool had delayed openings. JPS was also going to open delayed until officials decided to close it for the day. Other Edison schools continued their days on their regular schedules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed holds interest rate steady for year end</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/business/2023/december-fomc-meeting-interest-rates-held/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 16:57:51 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/business/2023/december-fomc-meeting-interest-rates-held/</guid>
      <description>Dec. 17 (ZFJ) — The Fed maintained the target federal funds rate at 5.25-5.50% for the third time in a row on Wednesday, Dec. 13, noting that inflation has eased but is still elevated.&#xA;“Inflation has eased from its highs, and this has come without a significant increase in unemployment,” said Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell. “This is very good news. But inflation is still too high, ongoing progress in bringing it down is not assured, and the path forward is uncertain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edison releases inspection reports on animal shelter deficiencies</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/edison-animal-shelter-inspection-reports/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 14:23:14 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/edison-animal-shelter-inspection-reports/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Dec. 10 (ZFJ) — Edison has released two veterinarians’ inspection reports on the condition of its animal shelter and a memorandum about the township’s response from early November.&#xA;The reports highlight problems relating to health, overcrowding, and management and recommend immediate action.&#xA;The Edison Animal Shelter serves Metuchen, Piscataway, Dunellen, Highland Park, and Edison.&#xA;DR. CHIOSI’S REPORT&#xA;Joseph R. Chiosi, doctor of veterinary medicine, of Sayrebrook Veterinary Hospital in Sayreville conducted an inspection on July 20, 2023, after performing exams and administering vaccines for adopters’ pets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edison police arrest Maryland attempted murder suspect after car chase</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/edison-police-arrest-attempted-murder-suspect-car-chase/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 23:30:41 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/edison-police-arrest-attempted-murder-suspect-car-chase/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Dec. 6 (ZFJ) — A suspect wanted for attempted murder in Maryland was arrested by Edison police after an hour-long motor vehicle pursuit on Sunday, Dec. 3.&#xA;At 20:13 on Sunday, Edison police dispatch received a Sirius XM alert that a stolen white 2019 Subaru Outback with Maryland license plates had entered the township near U.S. Highway 1 and Main Street.&#xA;While near 2900 Woodbridge Avenue, Edison Police Officer Phil Smith saw the vehicle traveling at a high speed and began tailing it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global temperature briefly exceeds 2 C above pre-industrial average</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2023/first-time-global-temperature-anomaly-exceeds-two-celsius/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 14:01:09 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2023/first-time-global-temperature-anomaly-exceeds-two-celsius/</guid>
      <description>Dec. 2 (ZFJ) — Earth’s temperature exceeded 2 degrees Celsius above pre-industrial levels on Nov. 17-18, according to the European Union’s Copernicus Climate Change Service (C3S).&#xA;Nov. 17 marked the first day in the ERA5 dataset, the European Centre for Medium Range Weather Forecasts’ climate record, that global temperatures exceeded 2 C above the average temperature before the extensive use of fossil fuels.&#xA;Nov. 17 exceeded the 1850-1900 average by 2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police: South Plainfield man shot three of his family members, called 911</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/south-plainfield-condo-complex-shooting-affidavit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 01:44:10 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/south-plainfield-condo-complex-shooting-affidavit/</guid>
      <description>SOUTH PLAINFIELD, N.J., Nov. 30 (ZFJ) — Authorities have accused Om Brahmbhatt, 23, of fatally shooting three of his family members on Monday at the Traditions condominium complex.&#xA;The Middlesex County Prosecutor’s Office has charged Brahmbhatt with three counts of first-degree murder and three counts of second-degree possession of a weapon for an unlawful purpose.&#xA;According to an affidavit submitted by the police to establish probable cause for an arrest warrant, South Plainfield Police Department officers responded to a 911 call on Monday, Nov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man charged for South Plainfield condo complex triple killing</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/south-plainfield-condo-complex-triple-shooting-arrest/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 22:55:02 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/south-plainfield-condo-complex-triple-shooting-arrest/</guid>
      <description>SOUTH PLAINFIELD, N.J., Nov. 28 (ZFJ) — A South Plainfield man has been arrested and charged in connection with the Coppola Drive shooting on Monday, Nov. 27, announced Middlesex County Prosecutor Yolanda Ciccone and Chief Peter Papa of the South Plainfield Police Department.&#xA;Om Brahmbhatt, 23, was arrested without incident and charged with three counts of first-degree murder and three counts of second-degree possession of a weapon for an unlawful purpose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minecraft YouTuber Stampy Cat ends 11-year Lovely World series</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/arts-and-entertainment/2023/stampy-cat-ends-lovely-world-series-minecraft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 01:12:09 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/arts-and-entertainment/2023/stampy-cat-ends-lovely-world-series-minecraft/</guid>
      <description>Nov. 25 (ZFJ) — Minecraft YouTuber Stampy Cat uploaded the finale to his 11-year series, Stampy’s Lovely World, on Saturday, Oct. 21.&#xA;The 823rd episode marked the end of the series, which began on May 19, 2012 (only 10 days after Minecraft: Xbox 360 Edition released). He was a dominant personality in the Minecraft YouTube scene from 2013 to 2017 and pioneered the video format of storytelling using the blocky game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actor strike ends with agreement on AI, compensation</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/arts-and-entertainment/2023/actor-strike-ends-sag-aftra-amptp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 12:01:57 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/arts-and-entertainment/2023/actor-strike-ends-sag-aftra-amptp/</guid>
      <description>Nov. 19 (ZFJ) — SAG-AFTRA ended its 118-day strike at 12:01 PT on Thursday, Nov. 9, after the union’s TV/Theatrical Negotiating Committee unanimously approved an agreement with provisions on artificial intelligence in films and actor compensation.&#xA;On Friday, Nov. 10, the SAG-AFTRA National Board approved the agreement with 86% of the vote. Union members now have until Tuesday, Dec. 5, to vote on ratifying the contract. SAG-AFTRA represents about 160,000 media professionals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court hears arguments on constitutionality of domestic violence gun ban</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/domestic-violence-gun-ban-oral-argument-supreme-court/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 18:39:28 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/domestic-violence-gun-ban-oral-argument-supreme-court/</guid>
      <description>Nov. 12 (ZFJ) — The Supreme Court heard arguments on whether a federal ban on firearms possession by people under domestic violence restraining orders violates the Second Amendment in the case United States v. Rahimi (22-915) on Tuesday, Nov. 7.&#xA;The statute in question, 18 U.S.C. § 922(g)(8), prohibits people who are under a restraining order from possessing guns. The court order must include a finding that the person is a credible threat to an “intimate partner or child” or explicitly prohibit any physical force against them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ørsted pulls out of two NJ offshore wind farm projects</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/business/2023/orsted-pulls-out-nj-first-two-wind-farms/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 11:25:19 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/business/2023/orsted-pulls-out-nj-first-two-wind-farms/</guid>
      <description>Nov. 10 (ZFJ) — Ørsted has pulled out of developing two offshore wind farms, set to have been New Jersey’s first ones, due to economic challenges, the company announced on Tuesday, Oct. 31.&#xA;“Macroeconomic factors have changed dramatically over a short period of time, with high inflation, rising interest rates, and supply chain bottlenecks impacting our long-term capital investments,” said David Hardy, group executive vice president and CEO of Ørsted Americas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democrats sweep Edison council as White, Lugo, Patel win board of education</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/2023-edison-local-elections-council-boe/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 19:29:05 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/2023-edison-local-elections-council-boe/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Nov. 8 (ZFJ) — The Democrats won the four available seats on the Edison Township Council while Virginia White, Christopher Lugo, and Anjana R. Patel secured three spots on the Edison Board of Education, according to unofficial results from the Middlesex County Clerk for the Nov. 7 general election.&#xA;Richard Brescher, Joseph A. Coyle, and Ajay V. Patil won reelection to the town council along with newcomer Asaf Shmuel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: Five Nights at Freddy’s: A Fun Flick for Fans</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/opinion/2023/akira-rorschach-fnaf-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 01:52:12 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/opinion/2023/akira-rorschach-fnaf-review/</guid>
      <description>I don’t usually watch horror films (I get very scared), but the lunch table gang invited me to see the FNAF movie, so, of course, I made an exception this time. Also, I was intrigued after hearing mixed reviews from my classmates and decided I wanted to see it for myself.&#xA;I used to be terrified seeing the animatronics back in elementary school. That all went out the window after they released the Security Breach game a few years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed holds interest rate steady for second time in a row</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/business/2023/fomc-november-1-interest-rate-steady-twice/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 21:33:18 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/business/2023/fomc-november-1-interest-rate-steady-twice/</guid>
      <description>Nov. 5 (ZFJ) — The Federal Reserve maintained the interest rate at 5.25-5.50% for the second time in a row on Wednesday, Nov. 1.&#xA;This rate was set on July 26 and held steady on Sept. 20. The Fed has been aggressively increasing the interest rate since it raised it from 0.00-0.25% to 0.25-0.50% in March 2022 in order to fight stubborn inflation.&#xA;Economic activity has been expanding at a strong pace, said Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School bus crashes into Edison home, no serious injuries</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/school-bus-crashes-into-edison-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 02:29:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/school-bus-crashes-into-edison-home/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Oct. 19 (ZFJ) — A school bus with 28 John Adams Middle School students on board crashed into an Edison home on Rahway Road in the morning on Wednesday, Oct. 18.&#xA;The bus, operated by contracted route provider Joy Transport, collided with the house’s garage, which sustained heavy damage. The house has been condemned by township inspectors for being structurally unsound.&#xA;The cause of the crash is believed to be a brake failure, said Edison Police Chief Thomas Bryan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grand jury clears Edison cops for April 2022 fatal shooting</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/grand-jury-no-charges-edison-police-deadly-force-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 15:28:26 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/grand-jury-no-charges-edison-police-deadly-force-2022/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Oct. 15 (ZFJ) — A state grand jury declined to criminally charge two Edison police officers who shot Merrill Rambarose, 49, of Edison on April 12, 2022.&#xA;Witness interviews, photographs, video footage of the shooting, and autopsy results were presented to the grand jury, which concluded deliberations on Sept. 25 and voted “no bill”—meaning Officers Daniel Bradley and Joseph Elqumos will not have criminal charges filed against them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raritan Valley EMS rebrands to Edison EMS</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/rvrems-rebranding-edison-ems/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 00:50:41 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/rvrems-rebranding-edison-ems/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Oct. 7 (ZFJ) — Edison Emergency Medical Services has officially rebranded from Raritan Valley Regional EMS, the agency announced in a Sept. 28 Instagram post.&#xA;Edison EMS is the non-profit volunteer first aid squad serving Edison and its surrounding areas for free.&#xA;RVREMS was formed in 2009 when Edison First Aid &amp;amp; Rescue Squad #1, Edison First Aid Squad #2, and Clara Barton First Aid Squad merged.&#xA;Edison EMS continues to operate out of the original stations, which have been renamed to Edison EMS Station 1, 2, and 3, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEMA to conduct nationwide emergency alert test</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/fema-emergency-alert-test-october-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 16:55:31 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/fema-emergency-alert-test-october-2023/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Oct. 2 (ZFJ) — The federal government will test two national emergency alert systems on Wednesday, Oct. 4, starting at about 14:20 (2:20 p.m.) EDT.&#xA;The Federal Emergency Management Agency, in conjunction with the Federal Communications Commission, will conduct the two-part test.&#xA;The first portion will test Wireless Emergency Alerts, which are directed at cell phones.&#xA;For 30 minutes, cell towers will broadcast the message “THIS IS A TEST of the National Wireless Emergency Alert System.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charles Martinet, voice of Super Mario, retires</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/arts-and-entertainment/2023/charles-martinet-mario-va-retires/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 23:13:10 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/arts-and-entertainment/2023/charles-martinet-mario-va-retires/</guid>
      <description>Sept. 23 (ZFJ) — Charles Martinet, known as the voice of Super Mario, Luigi, Wario, and Waluigi, is retiring from voice acting.&#xA;“It’s been such an honor, and such a joy, for so many years, that I look forward to continuing to bring that joy and help us all remember our innocence, and our happiness, and our joy, through great games,” Martinet said in a video message posted by Nintendo of America on Sept.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ requires schools to provide students grades 6-12 free menstrual products</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/nj-schools-6-12-must-provide-free-menstrual-products/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 00:49:28 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/nj-schools-6-12-must-provide-free-menstrual-products/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Sept. 10 (ZFJ) — School districts in New Jersey are now required to provide menstrual products for free in public schools that teach students of any grade from six through twelve.&#xA;Applicable schools will have to provide tampons and sanitary napkins (pads) in at least half of all their female and gender-neutral bathrooms. The state government will shoulder the costs for doing so.&#xA;The law addresses period poverty—one in four students in the U.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fontaine comes to Genshin Impact</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/arts-and-entertainment/2023/genshin-impact-new-nation-fontaine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 23:54:09 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/arts-and-entertainment/2023/genshin-impact-new-nation-fontaine/</guid>
      <description>Sept. 17 (ZFJ) — Put on your top hats and button your shirts, because Teyvat’s new nation and realm of Hydro, Fontaine, has finally released! HoYoverse—the creators of Genshin Impact—has pulled back the curtain on a land brimming with court trials, performances, and magic shows.&#xA;Inside the walls of Fontaine&amp;rsquo;s city are multiple levels of homes, shops, and restaurants to explore. ZFJ/Zoe Wu&#xA;Inside the walls of Fontaine&amp;rsquo;s city are multiple levels of homes, shops, and restaurants to explore.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ: Menlo Park, Paramus veterans homes violated civil rights with inadequate medical care</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/doj-menlo-park-veterans-home-civil-rights-investigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 23:38:12 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/doj-menlo-park-veterans-home-civil-rights-investigation/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Sept. 12 (ZFJ) — State-run veterans homes at Menlo Park and Paramus have failed to adequately respond to the COVID-19 pandemic and provide medical care to their residents, announced the Justice Department on Thursday, Sept. 7.&#xA;The feds said that the conditions at the veterans homes, which provide long-term nursing care to veterans and their families and are under the New Jersey Department of Military and Veterans Affairs (DMAVA), violate the Fourteenth Amendment right to reasonable safety when in the state’s care.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC authorities identify two new 9/11 victims</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/nyc-identifies-two-new-9-11-victims/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 21:05:42 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/nyc-identifies-two-new-9-11-victims/</guid>
      <description>Sept. 11 (ZFJ) — The 1,648th and 1,649th victims from the World Trade Center attacks on Sept. 11, 2001, have been identified, announced the New York City Office of Chief Medical Examiner on Friday, Sept. 8.&#xA;These two victims are the first new identifications of 9/11 victims since September 2021. About 1,104 victims, or 40% of the 2,753 who died, remain unidentified.&#xA;This year, the OCME also identified 60 human remains connected to previously identified individuals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cecilia Birge appointed Princeton High principal</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/princeton-high-school-new-principal-birge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 20:39:45 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/princeton-high-school-new-principal-birge/</guid>
      <description>Sept. 10 (ZFJ) — Cecilia Xie Birge was appointed principal of Princeton High School on Thursday, Aug. 31.&#xA;The Princeton Board of Education voted unanimously for her at a special meeting. Board member Michele Tuck-Ponder was not present.&#xA;“With Cecilia’s appointment tonight, we are turning a page and we are looking with excitement to the future,” said Dafna Kendal, president of the school board.&#xA;Birge thanked the board and search committee for entrusting her with the position and recognized the school staff’s work for Princeton High.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edison middle school teacher charged with possession of child pornography</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/edison-middle-school-teacher-charged-child-porn-possession/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 22:01:14 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/edison-middle-school-teacher-charged-child-porn-possession/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Aug. 30 (ZFJ) — Edison middle school teacher Julius Coaccioli, 55, was arrested and charged with third-degree possession of child pornography on Wednesday, Aug. 30, announced Middlesex County Prosecutor Yolanda Ciccone and Woodbridge Police Department Director Robert Hubner.&#xA;Coaccioli taught science at Woodrow Wilson Middle School at the time of his arrest. According to public payroll records, he has worked for the Edison Board of Education since September 1992.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US federal district court judge rules AI art not copyrightable</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/dc-district-judge-ai-art-not-copyrightable/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 14:45:56 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/dc-district-judge-ai-art-not-copyrightable/</guid>
      <description>Aug. 23 (ZFJ) — AI art generated “absent human involvement” is not eligible for copyright, ruled U.S. District Judge Beryl A. Howell on Aug. 18, Friday.&#xA;In her ruling for the federal district court in Washington, D.C., Howell upheld the U.S. Copyright Office’s denial of registration to computer scientist Stephen Thaler for the work he calls A Recent Entrance to Paradise.&#xA;BACKGROUND&#xA;Thaler, the plaintiff, owns an AI called the “Creativity Machine” that can generate visual works of art.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US, South Korea, and Japan agree to increase defense, economic cooperation at summit</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/foreign-affairs/asia-pacific/2023/us-kr-jp-summit-camp-david/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:18:20 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/foreign-affairs/asia-pacific/2023/us-kr-jp-summit-camp-david/</guid>
      <description>Aug. 21 (ZFJ) — President Joe Biden, South Korea’s President Yoon Suk Yeol, and Japan’s Prime Minister Fumio Kishida agreed to increase defense and economic cooperation among their countries at a Camp David summit on Friday, Aug. 18.&#xA;This meeting is the first-ever standalone summit between the leaders of Japan, South Korea, and the United States.&#xA;Japan and South Korea continue to have disputes over former Imperial Japan’s colonial rule from 1910-1945.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>July 2023 confirmed hottest month on record globally</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2023/july-2023-breaks-heat-records/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 12:18:31 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2023/july-2023-breaks-heat-records/</guid>
      <description>Aug. 14 (ZFJ) — July 2023 was the hottest month on record globally, confirmed the Copernicus Climate Change Service on Tuesday, Aug. 8.&#xA;The monthly average temperature worldwide was 16.95 degrees Celsius (62.51 degrees Fahrenheit), exceeding July 2019’s previous record of 16.63 C (61.93 F) and meeting the Paris Agreement threshold of 1.5 C (2.7 F) warming above preindustrial levels.&#xA;The 29 days from July 3-31 were the hottest days on record, exceeding the previous daily global mean surface air temperature record of 16.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taco Bell will fund your Taco Tuesday—unless you’re in NJ</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/business/2023/taco-bell-taco-tuesday-promo-nj-excluded/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 22:34:27 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/business/2023/taco-bell-taco-tuesday-promo-nj-excluded/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., Aug. 12 (ZFJ) — To celebrate its trademark battle win, Taco Bell will fund Taco Tuesday celebrations in all U.S. states except New Jersey, the company announced on Tuesday, Aug. 8.&#xA;On Tuesday, Sept. 12, Taco Bell, partnering with DoorDash, will spend $5 million to cover orders from participating Mexican food vendors.&#xA;“Taco Tuesday belongs to all who make, sell, eat, and celebrate tacos, and this Free-For-All will not only thank taco fans who supported the cause, but also spotlight local restaurants and vendors who can now embrace Taco Tuesdays without fear of legal action,” said Taco Bell U.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pittsburgh synagogue shooter sentenced to death</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/pittsburgh-synagogue-shooter-death-sentence/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 23:54:57 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/pittsburgh-synagogue-shooter-death-sentence/</guid>
      <description>Aug. 7 (ZFJ) — Robert Bowers, 50, was sentenced to death by U.S. District Judge Robert J. Colville on Thursday, Aug. 3, for killing 11 congregants, wounding two others, and injuring five police officers at the Tree of Life Synagogue in Pittsburgh.&#xA;“I have nothing specific that I care to say to Mr. Bowers,” Colville said, according to The Associated Press. “I am however convinced there is nothing I could say to him that might be meaningful.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backup driver pleads guilty for first death caused by fully autonomous car</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/backup-driver-pleads-guilty-fully-autonomous-car-first-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 23:50:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/backup-driver-pleads-guilty-fully-autonomous-car-first-death/</guid>
      <description>Aug. 3 (ZFJ) — Rafaela Vasquez, 49, pled guilty to endangerment on Friday, July 28, for failing to stop a fully self-driving car from hitting and killing a 49-year-old woman.&#xA;Maricopa County Superior Court Judge David W. Garbarino sentenced her to three years of supervised probation. Her charge will be designated a misdemeanor once she completes her sentence.&#xA;On March 18, 2018, Vasquez was the backup driver for a test vehicle belonging to Uber’s Advanced Technologies Group (ATG).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Edward Aldarelli appointed Edison schools superintendent</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/aldarelli-appointed-edison-superintendent/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 23:10:52 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/aldarelli-appointed-edison-superintendent/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., July 29 (ZFJ) — Dr. Edward Aldarelli was appointed superintendent of Edison Township Public Schools on Thursday, July 27.&#xA;The Edison Board of Education voted unanimously for him after four hours of candidate interviewing at a special meeting.&#xA;“Definitely, no doubt, absolutely yes,” said Board President Shannon Peng, topping off board member Mohin Patel’s “absolutely yes” and Jerry Shi’s “absolutely, absolutely yes.”&#xA;Aldarelli was “overwhelmed” that the board chose him to lead the district, which has over 16,000 students.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN Security Council holds first meeting on AI</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2023/un-security-council-first-meeting-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 13:20:04 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2023/un-security-council-first-meeting-ai/</guid>
      <description>July 25 (ZFJ) — The rapid increase in malicious uses of artificial intelligence has sparked international concern. On July 18, the United Nations Security Council gathered to recognize what AI could bring to the table and what it has already taken away.&#xA;U.N. Secretary-General António Guterres opened the meeting by observing the influence ChatGPT has garnered. ChatGPT, an AI that emulates human interaction, has taken over the internet by storm, infiltrating college applications, political propaganda, jobs, and other areas of daily life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Navy commissions littoral combat ship USS Canberra in Australia</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/foreign-affairs/asia-pacific/2023/uss-canberra-commissioned-australia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 21:46:50 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/foreign-affairs/asia-pacific/2023/uss-canberra-commissioned-australia/</guid>
      <description>July 24 (ZFJ) — The U.S. Navy commissioned Independence-class littoral combat ship USS Canberra (LCS 30) at the Royal Australian Navy’s Fleet Base East in Sydney on Saturday, July 22, marking the first time a U.S. ship entered service at a foreign port.&#xA;It is the second American ship named for Australia’s capital. The first was a Baltimore-heavy class cruiser, renamed in honor of the Australian heavy cruiser HMAS Canberra, which was lost at the Battle of Savo Island in WWII when defending U.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Middlesex County man admits to threatening attack on synagogue</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/middlesex-man-threat-synagogue-guilty-plea/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 00:01:49 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/middlesex-man-threat-synagogue-guilty-plea/</guid>
      <description>July 16 (ZFJ) – A Middlesex County man admitted to threatening to attack a synagogue and Jewish people via the internet.&#xA;19-year-old Omar Alkattoul pleaded guilty to one count of transmitting a threat in interstate and foreign commerce on Wednesday, July 12, regarding a crime committed around November 1, 2021.&#xA;Alkattoul used social media to share a link of his manifesto titled “When Swords Collide.” The document detailed his plans to attack a synagogue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>“Limited evidence” for aspartame as “possible carcinogen,” says WHO cancer agency</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/health-and-medicine/2023/who-aspartame-possible-carcinogen-limited-evidence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 23:37:50 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/health-and-medicine/2023/who-aspartame-possible-carcinogen-limited-evidence/</guid>
      <description>July 16 (ZFJ) — The World Health Organization’s cancer research agency categorized non-sugar sweetener aspartame as “possibly carcinogenic to humans” (group 2B) based on “limited evidence” for causing cancer in humans on Friday, July 14. A WHO joint panel did not change its acceptable daily limit of 40 mg/kg body weight.&#xA;Aspartame is an artificial sweetener that has been widely used in foods and beverages since the 1980s as an alternative to sugar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA grants traditional approval to Eisai/Biogen Alzheimer’s drug Leqembi</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/health-and-medicine/2023/fda-traditional-approval-leqembi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 03:07:35 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/health-and-medicine/2023/fda-traditional-approval-leqembi/</guid>
      <description>July 12 (ZFJ) — The Food and Drug Administration granted traditional approval to Eisai and Biogen’s Leqembi (lecanemab-irmb) 100 mg/mL intravenous injection on July 6. It is the first Alzheimer’s drug to clear this regulatory hurdle and aims to slow the disease’s progression.&#xA;“Today’s action is the first verification that a drug targeting the underlying disease process of Alzheimer’s disease has shown clinical benefit in this devastating disease,” said Teresa Buracchio, acting director of the Office of Neuroscience in FDA’s Center for Drug Evaluation and Research.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US completes destruction of its declared chemical weapons stockpile</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/us-destroys-chemical-weapons-stockpile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 19:34:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/us-destroys-chemical-weapons-stockpile/</guid>
      <description>July 10 (ZFJ) — The last possessor state, America, announced that it finished destroying its declared chemical weapons stockpile on Friday, July 7, marking the first time an international body verified the destruction of an entire category of declared weapons of mass destruction.&#xA;The stockpile was declared to the Organisation for the Prohibition of Chemical Weapons, the international body responsible for implementing the Chemical Weapons Convention. The 1997 arms control treaty prohibits its 193 members from developing or stockpiling chemical weapons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court strikes down affirmative action in college admissions</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/supreme-court-ruling-affirmative-action-harvard-admissions-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 23:05:33 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/supreme-court-ruling-affirmative-action-harvard-admissions-case/</guid>
      <description>July 3 (ZFJ) — Affirmative action in college admissions violates the Equal Protection Clause of the Fourteenth Amendment, ruled the Supreme Court in Students for Fair Admissions v. Harvard (20-1199) and SFFA v. University of North Carolina (21-707) on Thursday, June 29. The EPC prohibits racial discrimination by the government.&#xA;Reversing the lower courts’ decisions, the Court struck down the admissions programs used by Harvard and UNC by a 6-2 and 6-3 vote, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian prime minister secures work visa changes for skilled workers in US visit</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/foreign-affairs/asia-pacific/2023/modi-work-visas-america-visit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 21:47:59 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/foreign-affairs/asia-pacific/2023/modi-work-visas-america-visit/</guid>
      <description>June 26 (ZFJ) — Indian Prime Minister Narendra Modi, in his recent visit to the United States, and President Joe Biden announced a pilot for the expansion of capacity for H-1B and L-1 visas with the domestic renewal of temporary work visas.&#xA;The loosening of visa restrictions aims to increase the amount of skilled workers and students immigrating to the U.S. Currently, this pilot launch is only applicable to the H-1B and L-1 visas, which both admit skilled workers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US approves nation’s first lab-grown meat, cell-cultivated chicken, for sale</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2023/america-approves-first-lab-grown-meat-for-sale/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 23:01:06 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2023/america-approves-first-lab-grown-meat-for-sale/</guid>
      <description>June 24 (ZFJ) — Lab-grown meat companies UPSIDE Foods and GOOD Meat announced on Wednesday that they received the final Agriculture Department approval required to sell their chicken in the United States.&#xA;The Department of Agriculture Food Safety and Inspection Service issued grants of inspection for the companies’ manufacturing facilities: UPSIDE’s Engineering, Production, and Innovation Center and GOOD Meat’s demonstration plant in Alameda, California. GOOD Meat’s contract manufacturing partner JOINN Biologics also received a GOI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian wildfire smoke descends on US East Coast</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/canadian-wildfire-smoke-descends-on-us-east-coast/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 23:01:10 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/canadian-wildfire-smoke-descends-on-us-east-coast/</guid>
      <description>EDISON, N.J., June 7 (ZFJ) — Smoke from Canadian wildfires drifted into the eastern and central U.S., tinting the sky orange and triggering air quality alerts on Wednesday.&#xA;Canadian authorities are battling “one of the worst wildfire seasons on record,” said Steven Guilbeault, Canadian minister of environment and climate change. The country is currently facing over 400 wildfires, with over half out of control, according to the Canadian Interagency Forest Fire Centre.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court limits federal authority over wetlands with stricter test</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/supreme-court-limits-federal-wetlands-authority-sackett/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 15:08:10 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/supreme-court-limits-federal-wetlands-authority-sackett/</guid>
      <description>May 28 (ZFJ) — The federal government can only regulate wetlands with “a continuous surface connection” to adjacent “waters of the United States” under the Clean Water Act (1972), ruled the Supreme Court on Thursday, May 25, in Sackett v. EPA (21-454).&#xA;The CWA is the primary federal law regulating water pollution and prohibits the “discharge of any pollutant,” including “chemical wastes,” “rock,” and “sand,” into “navigable waters,” defined as “the waters of the United States, including the territorial seas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>66% chance world exceeds warming threshold before 2027, WMO says</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2023/66-chance-world-exceeds-warming-threshold-before-2027/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 21:32:50 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/science-and-technology/2023/66-chance-world-exceeds-warming-threshold-before-2027/</guid>
      <description>May 18 (ZFJ) — There is a 66% chance that the annual global surface temperature will exceed 1.5 degrees Celsius (2.7 degrees Fahrenheit) above pre-industrial levels before 2027, said the World Meteorological Organization on Wednesday.&#xA;The UN weather agency also predicted that there is a 98% chance that one of the next five years will be the warmest on record.&#xA;“These new highs will be fuelled almost completely by the rise of heat-trapping greenhouse gases in the atmosphere, but the anticipated development of the naturally-occurring El Niño event will also release heat from the tropical Pacific,” said Dr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>The Zombie Fridge Journal is a student-run nonprofit(able) news site reporting on various shenanigans.&#xA;We cover a wide range of topics, but the core of our work centers on government and legal coverage. We hope to promote civil discourse about both relevant issues and undercovered problems.&#xA;Editor-in-chief Wu decided to create it after his COVID-19 article was censored in January 2022. Its first article was published on May 18, 2023.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
