<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Arjun Shah on The Zombie Fridge Journal</title>
    <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/staff/arjun-shah/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Arjun Shah on The Zombie Fridge Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 00:01:49 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://theZFJ.github.io/staff/arjun-shah/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Middlesex County man admits to threatening attack on synagogue</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/middlesex-man-threat-synagogue-guilty-plea/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 00:01:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/domestic-affairs/2023/middlesex-man-threat-synagogue-guilty-plea/</guid>
      <description>July 16 (ZFJ) – A Middlesex County man admitted to threatening to attack a synagogue and Jewish people via the internet.
19-year-old Omar Alkattoul pleaded guilty to one count of transmitting a threat in interstate and foreign commerce on Wednesday, July 12, regarding a crime committed around November 1, 2021.
Alkattoul used social media to share a link of his manifesto titled “When Swords Collide.” The document detailed his plans to attack a synagogue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indian prime minister secures work visa changes for skilled workers in US visit</title>
      <link>https://theZFJ.github.io/foreign-affairs/asia-pacific/2023/modi-work-visas-america-visit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 21:47:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theZFJ.github.io/foreign-affairs/asia-pacific/2023/modi-work-visas-america-visit/</guid>
      <description>June 26 (ZFJ) — Indian Prime Minister Narendra Modi, in his recent visit to the United States, and President Joe Biden announced a pilot for the expansion of capacity for H-1B and L-1 visas with the domestic renewal of temporary work visas.
The loosening of visa restrictions aims to increase the amount of skilled workers and students immigrating to the U.S. Currently, this pilot launch is only applicable to the H-1B and L-1 visas, which both admit skilled workers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
